<body>
<sentence>
 "This money has never been carried out of the company in cash, but it must have been transformed at one point into cash," he said.  "So from Frankfurt there is possibly a  <tag key="formation"/>  of bank accounts that will shed more light on this." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "I will be out of work shortly; that's why I want to leave," says Ruben Arabean, a 30-year-old engineer, married with two children.  As he waits in  <tag key="formation"/>  for his immigration visa at the Australian Embassy, he explains: "I want to live in a country where things are planned out, where the budget is approved at the beginning of the year, not at the end." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 My eyes were wide open in search of the unknown.  As I moved my platoon of 20-odd teen-agers through the jungle, I chose to walk third in the  <tag key="formation"/>  of march. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 In Quito, where buildings rocked and cracked but didn't collapse, automobile use is restricted and soldiers guard the gas stations.  At Quito's air force base, earthquake victims wait in  <tag key="formation"/>  for hours to hitch rides on cargo planes to the earthquake zone. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The columnist goes on: "If a person is kind, or generous, it's an event."  Her mail, she says, touches on sore spots ranging from poor manners in supermarket  <tag key="formation"/>  to talking during movies. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 So did People Magazine, AP and a dozen photographers.  Outside, a  <tag key="formation"/>  of customers waited to get in. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The head of an international bank in Singapore confirms that he sends his driver onto the streets every weekday at 5 a.m. with instructions not to return without a copy.  By getting out so early, the driver can be first in  <tag key="formation"/>  when the newsstands open. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Edward, just six months old, mostly sleeps and eats banana mush.  His mother mostly sits in  <tag key="formation"/>  and watches Kung Fu and wildlife films on the four closed-circuit television screens in the dingy reception area.  About 300 other black people who have come to register for one thing or another are also waiting and watching, and more are standing in an even longer line outside. 
</sentence>
</body>
