<body>
<sentence>
 It also will issue $23 million in credits on customers' local phone bills in the same period.  Some 1.3 million customers with 1.6 million telephone  <tag key="phone"/>  will be affected. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 But in recent years, some investment banks  among them Morgan Stanley & Co., Goldman, Sachs & Co. and Salomon Brothers Inc.  have become major currency traders as well.  Now the three firms, and perhaps others, are applying for direct  <tag key="phone"/>  to the New York Fed. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The issue of direct access raises significant policy and possibly legal questions: Does the Fed have authority to deal with entities beyond its regulatory control?  And if the Fed opens  <tag key="phone"/>  with some investment banks, must it then open its doors to all non-bank institutions? 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "Telecommunications will be a red hot spot for new small-business ideas," believes James R. Swartz, managing partner of Accel Partners, a venture capital firm.  One Accel investment, General Communications Corp., has developed telephone- <tag key="phone"/>  switching and transmissions devices which offer multiple uses of a single home telephone line, including simultaneous transmission of voices and pictures. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 For a monthly fee of about $12 (plus the price of each call), the answering service  actually a "dialing service"  will dial your desired number, call you back and patch you into the call.  A red light on the phone indicates when one of the service's 20 other customers is using the  <tag key="phone"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Regulators, who have set up a telephone hotline to help with the transition, said patients can either choose another federally qualified HMO or return to traditional fee-for-service Medicare benefits.  A federal compliance officer doubling as an operator on the 800 telephone number said Saturday, "We have six  <tag key="phone"/> , and they are never not ringing." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Such a trading strategy would ordinarily be a prescription for instant losses.  But the trader says he was merely following instructions from his client  a Fed dealer on the other end of a dedicated private telephone  <tag key="phone"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 In Atlanta, John L. Clendenin, BellSouth's chairman and chief executive, said the results "reflect strong growth in both our telephone operating companies and our non-regulated subsidiaries."  While also providing no details of the unregulated businesses, he said BellSouth telephone company units added a record 177,000 new access  <tag key="phone"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The restrictions are exasperating for manufacturers, who must contend with huge competitive pressures sparked by the technological changes.  The standard telephone has given way to a complex electronic device that has the potential to enable people, computers and office machines to communicate along the same  <tag key="phone"/>  at the same time. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The World Bank and IDA also approved $150 million in credits to India for urban development projects in the state of Uttar Pradesh.  Morocco will get a $125 million World Bank loan to help modernize and expand telecommunications facilities, including telephone  <tag key="phone"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 New products announced yesterday  a phone system called Spirit and an updated Merlin system  are part of a plan to overhaul the unit, said John A. "Gus" Blanchard, group vice president in charge of the unit.  The unit sells phones and phone switches to businesses with fewer than 80  <tag key="phone"/>  and was one of several businesses AT&T considered abandoning last fall. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The market for phone systems is fairly flat and intensely competitive; AT&T, International Business Machines Corp.'s Rolm unit and Northern Telecom Ltd. vie each year for the No. 1 spot and together control 60% to 70% of the market, according to analysts.  AT&T said its new Spirit system, which has been in controlled introduction in Southern California, is designed for non-office businesses and, in the larger model, can accommodate as many as 24  <tag key="phone"/>  and 48 phones.  Merlin II, the larger of the new Merlin systems, can accommodate as many as 32 lines and 72 phones. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 That Van Gogh painting sold for 290,000 times its original value.  The  <tag key="phone"/>  was quiet. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 A board of federal and state regulators last month voted to increase the subscriber- <tag key="phone"/>  charge by a total of $1.50 by April 1989.  The charge makes subscribers pay part of the fixed costs of the lines to homes and small businesses rather than adding these costs to long-distance service. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 So for Judge Schwartzberg, the practical considerations of finding space for files and people to do the filing are a top priority.  "We will have to add more copying machines, more telephone  <tag key="phone"/> , more clerical staff," he said. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Officials of each airline said only that they have held talks with the company about supplying Trintex subscribers with the ability to order airline tickets using personal computers.  Videotex systems distribute interactive information and other services, usually over telephone  <tag key="phone"/> , to users with personal computers. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 While 15 of the 16 largest software companies are on the East or West Coasts, WordPerfect is in Utah.  When most software companies complain about the cost of answering questions from users, WordPerfect provides a toll-free  <tag key="phone"/>  for its customers' calls. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 But Multimate has slipped recently at the same time as the Wang system has fallen out of favor.  One key to WordPerfect's growth was its toll-free help  <tag key="phone"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 One more twist: The yen thus raised were "swapped" into U.S. dollars for delivery to the Canadian government.  "We had several telephone conferences, and at the final bidding, we had people on the  <tag key="phone"/>  in Ottawa, and our people on in Toronto, New York, London and on a speakerphone in Tokyo," says a manager in the Tokyo head office. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 They do so by calling 976-CHAT in Los Angeles.  For $2 plus toll charges, callers are allowed to participate for about two and a half minutes in confusing conversations which alternate between efforts to figure out who is on the  <tag key="phone"/>  and the ramblings of teen-age minds. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 What is this? (a mother's voice) <tag key="phone"/>  A chat line? 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 In less than a minute I had a list of 33 books that met those criteria; in less than two minutes I had a six-page printout to take with me to the New Hanover County Library, which, incidentally, last month replaced its microfilm card catalog with computers and CD-ROM disks.  Of course, the Bowker system is designed primarily for commercial accounts, not for indolent researchers like myself, and as such it has options to allow bookstores and libraries to place orders electronically over the telephone  <tag key="phone"/>  with major book wholesalers. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 This, of course, induces long-distance carriers to look for a variety of other ways to reach their customers, including private microwave relays and fiber-optic cables.  In order to reduce the incentive for long-distance companies to bypass the local companies through alternative distribution systems, the FCC instituted a fixed monthly "subscriber  <tag key="phone"/>  charge" for residential and business subscribers. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 This charge, imposed in June 1985 at $1 a month, is now $2 a month for residential subscribers and $6 a month for multiline business customers.  The charge is de signed to make subscribers pay for part of the fixed costs of the  <tag key="phone"/>  to their homes or businesses rather than adding these costs to the costs of long-distance service. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Another hot new market: sophisticated gear for business and industry.  Canon U.S.A. Inc. aims at government, the media and real estate with its electronic still camera, which doesn't use film and can transmit pictures over telephone  <tag key="phone"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Commodore is hoping sales will come from the booming desktop-publishing markets, which is Apple's domain, as well as more specialized users in the music, video, and graphics-related professions.  For instance, by using the Amiga, advertising agencies could develop full-color story boards and send them over telephone  <tag key="phone"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Take information services.  Advances in technology since the time of the decree mean that computers can more easily communicate with each other over telephone  <tag key="phone"/>   that's especially important now that there are an estimated 12 million home computers in America, apart from the millions of office systems. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Only 40 firms currently display quotes on Seaq international, about two-thirds of its capacity.  But Mr. Nash said there are about a dozen entry requests that have been delayed by a lack of necessary telephone  <tag key="phone"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Selling software electronically has been tried before without much success, primarily because the devices were so limited, says Chuck Kinch, ComputerLand's vice president, products.  Some units, for instance, distributed software by telephone  <tag key="phone"/>  from a central location, but the process wasn't reliable, Mr. Kinch says. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The IBM announcement said the PC Convertible will now come with a "supertwist" liquid crystal display screen, which uses a new technology to greatly enhance readability.  IBM also dealt with complaints about the modem, which lets computers communicate across telephone  <tag key="phone"/> , by offering an optional modem that adapts to the industry standard. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Occasionally, the language seems formulaic: After computers confirm a rocket's "incredibly precise" trajectories, an Air Force general enters his "highly secure" office.  Moments later the secretary of defense speaks on a telephone  <tag key="phone"/>  available only to "very senior administration officials." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The state panel confirmed an earlier ruling that determined the services to be in the public interest.  In addition, it ordered Pacific Telesis Group Inc.'s Pacific Bell unit and GTE Corp.'s General Telephone Co. of California unit to continue efforts to find an inexpensive way to block access to 976 programs from their telephone  <tag key="phone"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The union leaders, from 24 countries, claim to represent some 26.5 million organized workers around the world.  The proposed measures include setting up toll-free telephone  <tag key="phone"/>  in Britain and other countries for IBM employees to contact union organizers, forming an international clearing house for the unions to swap information about IBM, stepping up recruitment advertising and publicizing instances of what labor leaders call IBM's "union-busting" actions. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 US Sprint Communications Co., a long-distance telephone company owned jointly by GTE Corp., Stamford, Conn., and United Telecommunications Inc., Kansas City, Mo., is also expected to enter the competition.  The new service would replace the federally managed network of owned and leased equipment and leased long-distance telephone  <tag key="phone"/>  that link 1.3 million government workers nationwide and handle 300 million calls a year. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 American Telephone & Telegraph Co. said it signed a $92 million contract with the Navy to install a telecommunications network linking 14 naval facilities in the San Francisco Bay area.  The 10-year agreement includes 40,000 telephone  <tag key="phone"/> , in a system that will have capacity of 120,000 lines. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 One of them recalls that when Col. North found out that Defense Secretary Caspar Weinberger objected to the plan to force down an Egyptian airliner carrying the Achille Lauro terrorists, he persuaded his Security Council superiors to initially order the White House operators not to disturb President Reagan with telephone calls.  (Mr. Weinberger and the president eventually spoke over an unsecured  <tag key="phone"/>  while Mr. Reagan was aboard Air Force One and Mr. Weinberger was on another aircraft.) 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Mr. Rollwagen also said he told Seymour Cray, the company founder, about how Apple was using the machine.  "There was a pause on the other end of the  <tag key="phone"/> ," Mr. Rollwagen recalls, "and Seymour said, 'That's interesting, because I'm designing the next Cray with an Apple.'" 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 At the Federal Bureau of Investigation, agents probing the Iran-Contra affair are assigned "secure" telephone  <tag key="phone"/>  that can't be bugged. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Based on Rochester's closing price of $44.75 a share in composite trading yesterday on the New York Stock Exchange, the transaction has a total value of about $26.3 million.  Enterprise, which serves about 15,700 access  <tag key="phone"/>  in a territory between Harrisburg, Pa., and Philadelphia, will become Rochester Telephone's third telephone operating company in Pennsylvania. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 But officials close to Mr. Carlucci said the new national security adviser is determined to serve as an honest broker between the Pentagon, the State Department, the CIA and other agencies.  The officials said Mr. Carlucci also has been careful to secure a direct  <tag key="phone"/>  to President Reagan, bypassing White House chief of staff Donald Regan. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The commission voted 5-0 to seek public comment on a plan to "streamline" regulation of packet switching networks and telecommunications services offered under competitive contracts.  Commercial packet switching services divide data transmissions into tiny digital segments and route those segments economically over telephone  <tag key="phone"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Picture hundreds of traders sitting or standing at consoles, each with perhaps eight or more flashing computer screens.  Picture each trader with two telephone handsets, connected by direct  <tag key="phone"/>  to maybe 500 customers and fellow traders. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The transaction includes J.B.N.'s Independent Communications Inc. unit, a Fairview, Kan., provider of communications services to the Defense Department, the telecommunications concern said.  J.B.N. Telephone serves 2,500 access  <tag key="phone"/>  in 13 exchanges in north central Kansas, Contel said. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 BOSTON  The call came shortly after Michael Janeway resigned under pressure as editor of the Boston Globe.  Suddenly Gov. Michael Dukakis, almost a stranger, was on the  <tag key="phone"/>  inviting him over to the Statehouse, and there, alone, the two talked about how much it hurts when a man works hard at a job he loves  and is judged a failure. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The company also wants to expand in telecommunications to take advantage of the growth in that industry.  For example, it is producing and installing a product that enables utilities to read customer meters through telephone  <tag key="phone"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 IBM also boosted the 9370's prospects by announcing products that will let it attach to a token-ring network, which will help it communicate with other IBM computers.  In addition, IBM announced products that will make it easier to group 9370s, to have a 9370 dial into a central computer through telephone  <tag key="phone"/>  and to update a 9370's software from a remote location. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The result of this bureaucratic obstacle course: New foreign investment, excluding companies already established in the Philippines, reached a meager $712,000 in the first quarter of this year.  Many businessmen claim it is more difficult to transact business now than under Mr. Marcos, when a direct  <tag key="phone"/>  to the palace, however costly, usually assured an investor of official cooperation. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Irving Trust Co., a major player in the foreign exchange market, said it is taking a "sabbatical" from interbank dealing after its trading desk was "decimated" in a move by a group of dealers to E.F. Hutton & Co.  Irving has traded currencies since the 1920s and is one of about a dozen U.S. banks with direct trading  <tag key="phone"/>  to the Federal Reserve. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Similarly, AT&T blames the breakup of the Bell System for lack of certain services that use a separate signaling network within the nation's phone system.  This network is used within AT&T's long-distance  <tag key="phone"/>  to send the phone number separately from the call itself, enabling AT&T to keep from sending calls to places where lines are busy. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Instead of pushing hot new funds through performance rankings, companies are now emphasizing diversification.  And with many investors unable to get through clogged telephone  <tag key="phone"/>  during the crash, companies are stressing service. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 ABC also is testing new marketing approaches for its soaps.  It has created a soap-opera trivia contest on radio and a special 900 telephone  <tag key="phone"/>  called "Soap Talk." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Neither one is practical."  GM, he notes, has established toll-free complaint  <tag key="phone"/> , and has rewritten its service bulletins for fifth-grade-level readers. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The Federal Communications Commission, which recently eased up on raunchy radio and TV shows, yesterday started cracking down on raunchy telephone services.  The agency launched investigations into whether two California companies violated the Communications Act by providing lewd telephone messages without screening the calls to see if children were on the  <tag key="phone"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 But with the city's growth as the West Coast's financial hub and the gateway to the Pacific Rim, businessmen with expense accounts have clamored for first-class hotel rooms.  Guests, who typically shell out $175 to $300 a night for a single (the price can go up to $3,000 for the ne plus ultra in sybaritic surroundings), are being pampered with larger rooms or suites, real marble bathrooms with television, phones with more than one  <tag key="phone"/> , plush robes, exotic flowers and complimentary wine. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 At the hospital, nobody could call in except on the emergency number.   <tag key="phone"/>  out were jammed. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "They can't," he says flatly.  After decades of scrimping on new equipment, British Telecom is stuck with a tired, antique phone system that is expensive to maintain and prone to crossed  <tag key="phone"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Teradyne Inc. said it received a $25 million contract from British Telecommunications PLC for its automated test system for subscriber  <tag key="phone"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Recently joining the list of foreign players were Austria's Girozentrale Vienna and Belgium's Banque Bruxelles Lambert.  Richard W. Magee, managing director of Tullett & Tokyo Forex Inc., a currency broker, said that in the past year, the company has installed trading  <tag key="phone"/>  to about a dozen new branches of foreign banks, mostly from smaller countries. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Operators sometimes take half an hour to answer the phone.   <tag key="phone"/>  mysteriously go dead, and repairmen won't fix them unless paid tips. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Computer Sciences also has been "consistently late" in providing certain quality control products, he said, resulting in some incorrect payments to providers and incorrect reporting to the state.  And the company has failed to set up sufficient toll-free telephone  <tag key="phone"/>  to handle inquiries from providers, he added. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 In your May 21 story about the phone industry billing customers for unconnected calls, I was surprised that you did not discuss whether such billing is appropriate.  A caller who keeps a  <tag key="phone"/>  open waiting for a connection uses communications switching and transmission equipment just as if a conversation were taking place. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 There is no more reason not to pay for tying up network facilities when calls go unanswered than there is for a refund on gasoline when one drives to a store only to find that desired merchandise is out of stock.  Callers anxious to reach parties whose  <tag key="phone"/>  are busy or unanswered can freely redial until they get through. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 As the long-distance market becomes more competitive, however, prices of services will conform more to the costs of providing those services.  If holding a  <tag key="phone"/>  open while waiting for a call to be answered imposes costs, eventually a price will be charged. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The Federal Reserve Bank of New York said it granted "several" currency brokers direct access to its foreign exchange desk, a privilege previously limited to about a dozen commercial banks.  For the time being, the New York Fed said, it will use direct  <tag key="phone"/>  to brokers only to gather market information, and it will continue to deal only with banks in foreign exchange transactions. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "It's a step in the right direction," an investment banker said of the move.  A Fed spokesman said Friday that extending  <tag key="phone"/>  to investment banks is still under consideration.  Morgan Stanley & Co., Goldman, Sachs & Co. and Salomon Brothers Inc. are among the investment banks that have become major foreign exchange market participants in recent years and seek lines to the Fed.  The Fed wouldn't say which or how many brokers it established links with, but two New York brokers identified themselves as having opened lines to the Fed: Noonan, Astley & Pearce Inc. and Tullett & Tokyo Forex Inc.  For the Fed, lines to brokers provide instantaneous information on exchange-rate moves.  For brokers, as for commercial banks, getting a line to the Fed brings prestige and at least the appearance of having access to the internal workings of the often secretive central bank.  If the Fed eventually chooses to use brokers for its currency transactions, the lines also could deliver sizable chunks of profitable business. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The brokers' combined average daily trading volume was $25.9 billion, a rise of 84% since 1983.  Brokers had been seeking  <tag key="phone"/>  to the Fed since the 1970s, according to Joe Roderick, vice president at Noonan Astley.  The Fed hasn't discussed its deliberations about granting lines to investment banks. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 He also said he didn't learn of Morgan Stanley's decision to rescind the trade until his broker called him at about 11:30 EDT last night.  "He said they'd have an explanation in the morning, so I won't know until then what we're going to do," he said while his lawyers held on another telephone  <tag key="phone"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Rolm's operations in Europe are much smaller than those in the U.S.  In Britain last year, IBM and Rolm had less than 3% of the market for large office switchboards, private automated branch exchanges handling 100 or more telephone  <tag key="phone"/> , according to Dataquest Inc., a San Jose, Calif.-based market research firm. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 But a new breed of investor is going high tech.  Some carry beepers that alert them to sudden market changes; others rent or buy portable computers that retrieve financial-news wires by telephone  <tag key="phone"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 That's because not all of those switchboards keep track of whether calls are routed long distance, so it would be difficult to add access charges to such calls.  He said the agency would look at ways to monitor such calls and may propose a flat-rate fee for some private  <tag key="phone"/> .  The FCC currently makes companies pay $25 a month for certain local lines that connect to big companies' switchboards, but it feels that the revenue raised from those charges is inadequate. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Major firms contacted, including Morgan Stanley & Co., Kidder Peabody & Co., PaineWebber Inc., Goldman Sachs and Salomon Brothers, all either denied that they were responsible for the buying or declined comment.  As news of the rally in MMI futures reached the New York Stock Exchange (major firms maintain open  <tag key="phone"/>  both to their traders in Chicago and to specialists in New York), the market got another important psychological boost: the announcement of stock buybacks by major corporations. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 It has made organ-donor education its public cause, and bowing to "growing public concern," it begrudgingly pulled out of South Africa earlier this year.  It set up a special 800 inquiry  <tag key="phone"/>  for reporters, supported a science-journalism project and launched a "Dow Lets You Do Great Things" ad campaign. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 A caller in Chicago, for instance, could call a Chicago company and get switched to a branch office in New York without paying the full long-distance rates.  To pay for such activity, the FCC now makes companies pay $25 a month for certain local  <tag key="phone"/>  that connect to big companies' switchboards. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Rochester Telephone Corp. said it signed a letter of intent to acquire C,C&S Systems Inc. for about $25 million in stock.  Jackson, Mich.-based C,C&S Systems is a holding company that operates C,C&S Telco Inc., a telephone company that serves 17,000 access  <tag key="phone"/>  in South-Central Michigan, and T-COM Inc., a paging service that operates in Florida, Michigan and Texas. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Rochester Telephone operates three telephone companies in New York and four in Pennsylvania.  Its companies serve a total of more than 500,000 access  <tag key="phone"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 More than a week after the market tumbled through the glass into Wonderland, the telephone  <tag key="phone"/>  at Rothschild Securities Corp. still crackled with customers' anger and apprehension. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 It is the Federal Reserve Bank of New York, agent for the U.S. government.  And for a moment, Mr. Scala doesn't see the  <tag key="phone"/>  light up.  "When that line comes in, you've got to pick it up quick," Mr. Remigio chides his partner. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 A hotline service operated by the Institute of Securities Market Development handles complaints from investors.  In recent weeks, as many as one thousand callers a day have clogged the  <tag key="phone"/>  just to "let off steam," says Leon Hu, president of the government-sponsored agency. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 WALL STREET CHAOS spurs activity in a $99, simulated trading game from Wall Street Games Inc., Wellesley, Mass.  With nothing real at stake, players still swamped the game's toll-free telephone  <tag key="phone"/> , selling stocks short on Monday and buying on Tuesday and yesterday. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 But Southwestern Bell's economists note that the signs of a recovery are centered in the manufacturing segment and provide a weaker boost to demand for phone service than does an economic rebound fueled by service and construction industries.  Mr. Barnes said that in the past 12 months, the phone company's customer  <tag key="phone"/>  increased only 38,000. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "That is far below our traditional growth rate within our five-state territory," he said.  That also sharply contrasts with gains of 176,000 new  <tag key="phone"/>  by Pacific Telesis Group's telephone company unit during the third quarter. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The SIPC is an industry-backed organization that provides reimbursements to individual customers of failed member firms.  Meanwhile, some firms weren't answering their trading  <tag key="phone"/>  yesterday, possibly to avoid sales that would drive prices of their proprietary little issues down even furtheir, traders said. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Revenue rose 8% to $3.12 billion from $2.89 billion.  BellSouth had a record increase of 232,000 new customer  <tag key="phone"/>  in the quarter.  So far this year, it said, it has gained 504,000 new lines, compared with 510,000 for all of 1986. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Indeed, even enthusiasts concede that human operators have a role.  "If you have a consumer complaint  <tag key="phone"/>  and a computer answers it, that's the worst possible application," says Brad Wendkos, president of Phoneworks, a Hackensack, N.J., firm that designs telephone promotions. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Revenue rose about 1% to $2.33 billion from $2.31 billion.  Donald E. Guinn, chairman and chief executive officer, said the company's Pacific Bell Telephone Co. unit added more than 176,000 new customer  <tag key="phone"/>  during the quarter. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 D.C. Staley, chairman, said the results "are within our expectations," although the rate of growth in net income has been "slowed somewhat due to investments and expenditures intended to improve Nynex's long term financial outlook."  The company had 14.3 million access  <tag key="phone"/>  in service at the end of the quarter, up 3.2% from the year earlier period. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Mr. Nakasone, meanwhile, retains the power of considerable public popularity and control over a sizable faction within the LDP.  His goal is to continue to exert that power and to keep a  <tag key="phone"/>  open for a repeat session as prime minister in a few years. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Mary and Philip Robertson have sent a postcard from Italy to their three Shih Tzus.  "Dear Nanky-Poo, Yum-Yum and Tu Ling," the card says, "We are having a splendid time, but as always, miss you guys." (Some clients telephone to talk to their dogs, but Ms. Katz jokingly tells them that the pets are "on another  <tag key="phone"/> .") 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Many mutual funds offer telephone switching privileges where an investor can call to switch out of a stock mutual fund into a money-market fund at the end of that day's trading.  But sometimes a fund's telephone  <tag key="phone"/>  are jammed.  When stock prices made sharp corrections earlier this year, some investors complained they tried unsuccessfully for three and four days to get through to mutual funds on 800-number telephone lines. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 These views have been translated into action.  When Mr. Harkin was a member of the House, he was instrumental in persuading Congress to purchase up-to-date equipment that allows hearing-impaired people to communicate by typing messages over the telephone  <tag key="phone"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 AT&T's recent price decreases have not been shown to result from increased efficiency, deregulation or competition.  They are largely the result of the FCC's effort to shift telephone costs from long-distance carriers to local monopoly companies through increases in subscriber  <tag key="phone"/>  charges and separation changes. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Conservatives suspect it is actually spending much more.  People for the American Way volunteers, using a dozen telephone  <tag key="phone"/>  at the group's Washington headquarters, this week will be urging members in Alabama, Arizona and Pennsylvania to contact Sens. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Many of those downtown workers who arrived at their offices after the quake were turned away.  Stores and bank branches in the area didn't open or opened late, and telephone  <tag key="phone"/>  into the Los Angeles area were overloaded for several hours following the quake. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 So far, OS/2 hasn't sold well, mainly because there were no programs that tap the operating system's snazzy graphics and ability to juggle several computing tasks at once.  Sidekick provides a planner calendar, an automated phonebook, a calculator, a bare-bones word processor, and makes it easy for a personal computer to connect with other computers through telephone  <tag key="phone"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Merrill executives familiar with the telecommunications operations offer a different view.  They said the company currently uses a combination of dedicated private  <tag key="phone"/>  and public lines to transmit voice, data and video signals.  The use of the lines is coordinated by an internal technical staff and managers. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 But judging from their vastly different marketing methods, the cattle auctions might as well be on different planets.  Superior Livestock Auction, which has headquarters here and in Brush, Colo., uses a satellite dish, dozens of camera crews, nationally distributed catalogs and hundreds of telephone  <tag key="phone"/>  and video screens to market steers that never leave the ranch until they are sold. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 An important challenge facing Mr. Adams is the distressed economy of the company's regional-service territory, which has been hard hit by the drought and energy slump.  Last year, the company's telephone business had its poorest annual growth volume for new telephone  <tag key="phone"/>  since the Great Depression.  It installed only 8,100 new lines. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 But insiders say they believe Mr. Adams can step up to the challenge.  In Texas, he stimulated new telephone  <tag key="phone"/>  growth by pushing advanced products such as Integrated Services Digital Network, which combine voice, data and video transmissions over one telephone line.  For the third quarter, new telephone lines quadrupled, with Texas responsible for about 62% of the growth.  The company added 114,866 new lines in the quarter. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "Our computers have been down for 1 1/2 days."  The facsimile machine, which can send and reproduce copies of a document over telephone  <tag key="phone"/> , is suddenly ubiquitous. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The tape-recorded voice answering the phone tells callers how to enter a contest for a free trip to London, which includes a plug for Continental Airlines.  If you stay on the  <tag key="phone"/> , running up an even bigger phone bill, the same voice goes on to advertise the movie, and would have gone on but I'd heard enough. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Revenue from telephone operations increased 7% to $634.6 million, while long-distance connection services surged 10.5% to $327.9 million.  William L. Weiss, Ameritech's chairman and chief executive officer, said the company had its "largest telephone- <tag key="phone"/>  increase ever," a 2.5% jump for a total of 371,000 lines installed. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Zane E. Barns, Southwestern Bell's chairman and chief executive officer, said he expects the company's cellular properties to be profitable by the end of 1989.  In new telephone  <tag key="phone"/> , Southwestern Bell had its best quarterly performance since 1985.  New telephone lines quadrupled.  The company added 114,866 new lines in the third quarter, up 88,866 from 26,000 a year earlier. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The company said overall expenses in the quarter jumped 16% to $2.69 billion from $2.31 billion a year earlier.  Non-telephone operations and growth in new telephone  <tag key="phone"/>  helped revenue surge 11% to $3.46 billion from $3.11 billion a year earlier. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Those revenues increased 45% to $757.6 million from $524.1 million, while revenues from long distance calls made within the same area code rose 8% to $427.1 million from $394.6 million.  New telephone  <tag key="phone"/>  continue to grow at a clip of 4.5% annually.  The company added 216,000 new telephone lines in the third quarter for a total of 16.3 million.  So far this year, the company has added 537,000 lines. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Profits for five telecommunications concerns rose in the third quarter, generally reflecting increases in new customer  <tag key="phone"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Basic telephone business revenue increased 2% to $2.47 billion from $2.42 billion, while non-telephone operation revenue slumped 17% to $137.3 million, compared with $165.2 million.  In the business segment, new telephone  <tag key="phone"/>  increased by 7.1% and call volume, reflected in minutes of use, rose 11.5%.  Bell Atlantic installed 105,000 new telephone lines, both business and residential, for an increase of 3.2% and a total of $16.3 million. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Pacific Telesis's net benefited from gains in its cellular and paging business, increased local long-distance use, and new telephone  <tag key="phone"/> .  Minutes of use for local long-distance calls jumped 8.9%, profit in the cellular and paging business surged 73%, and new telephone lines grew 4.2%. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Revenue from basic telephone service increased 2.7% to $805 million, while revenue from long distance calls made in the same area code climbed 4.6% to $581 million.  Pacific Telesis installed 207,000 new customer  <tag key="phone"/> , a 4.2% increase, for a total of 12.95 million access lines. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Local service revenue was flat at about $1.41 billion, compared with $1.40 billion in the year-ago quarter.  New customer  <tag key="phone"/>  grew 3.5% in the third quarter.  Nynex, based in New York, installed 194,000 access lines for a total of $14.8 million. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Access charge revenue rose 6.7% to $676.3 million from $633.9 million.  U S West, based in Denver, also had increases in minutes-of-use and new telephone  <tag key="phone"/> .  Minutes-of-use rose 8.2% to 8.5 million from 7.87 million, while new customer telephone lines increased 2.3% to 11.8 million, signalling changes in the economy. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 But, he adds, support costs are high.  Customers who buy the upgrades average two calls apiece to the company's help  <tag key="phone"/> , the same number as for new customers. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 That, in turn, should continue to cut the costs of the machines and expand their market.  Sharp Electronics Corp. and Ricoh Corp. recently announced faxes that use normal paper, rather than the rolls of chemically treated, heat-sensitive paper most faxes use to reproduce documents from signals transmitted over telephone  <tag key="phone"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Missing perhaps 300 or more of their local pilot fish to follow them and magnify their trading power, the Wall Street houses will eventually be ground down by even moderate portfolio insurance selling, Serfling realizes."  He still has the German client on the  <tag key="phone"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 They are here," Mrs. Guba answered.  On the tape recording of Mrs. Guba's call to the 911 emergency  <tag key="phone"/> , played at the trial, the baby sitter is heard begging for an ambulance. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Local bills for residences and small businesses will show an FCC-ordered 60-cents-a-month increase in charges by local companies beginning in December.  The so-called subscriber  <tag key="phone"/>  charge, currently $2.60 a month, reflects part of the cost of connecting long-distance companies with local companies. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Residences average $15 a month in long-distance charges, according to Jack Grubman of PaineWebber Inc.  The subscriber  <tag key="phone"/>  charge is scheduled to increase 30 cents in April for residences and small businesses. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The Federal Communications Commission restricted the ability of local telephone companies to charge high prices for private telephone  <tag key="phone"/>  used in communications networks. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 In fact, one of the quickest post-crash reforms was to install special phone links between New York, Chicago and Washington market overseers.  This arrangement, which the Big Board calls the "hoot and holler"  <tag key="phone"/> , is meant to make sure that in a crisis, markets can be in instant contact without the risk of busy signals or switchboard snafus. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Records show, for example, that three top Soviet laser scientists had access to classified areas of Lawrence Livermore National Laboratory, even though they were authorized to visit only unclassified areas, the GAO said.  In another case, an Israeli scientist barred from classified areas gained access to the laboratory's supercomputer through the telephone  <tag key="phone"/>  of a worker at whose home he was staying, the GAO said. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Local phone companies will be restricted by the FCC in charging high prices for private telephone  <tag key="phone"/>  used in communications networks. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Callers seem baffled by the change.  When investors now get a live voice on the  <tag key="phone"/> , says Steven Norwitz, a vice president for T. Rowe Price Associates Inc., Baltimore, "They'll be saying, 'What happened to my yield?'" 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The Philadelphia-based telecommunications concern also said it hopes this will lead to more contract work as the Dutch government proceeds with long-range plans to modernize its telephone system.  The Dutch network has about six million telephone access  <tag key="phone"/> , making it slightly larger than New Jersey's network, which also serves a densely populated area. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 However, continuing cutbacks in personnel could further irritate some already-frustrated investors.  Mario Maltese, a Fidelity fund shareholder and the chairman of an audio-visual-systems company in Mineola, N.Y., says clogged  <tag key="phone"/>  recently caused him to quit seeking help from Fidelity's phone representatives during the day. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "The allegations are not true and we intend to defend ourselves vigorously."  The suits, filed in U.S. District Court for the Southern District of Ohio, stem from claims by two fired Cincinnati Bell employees, who told local newspapers that they had been ordered to illegally tap the telephone  <tag key="phone"/>  of more than 1,000 Cincinnati area residents. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The only reason the former employees reportedly gave for tapping the phones was for national security concerns.  Three of the residents, whose  <tag key="phone"/>  were allegedly tapped, filed the suits. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 In addition to the Knight-Ridder-Tribune and Scripps-Howard wires, the other major news wires operated by newspapers are the New York Times News Service, and Los Angeles Times/Washington Post News Service.  Over telephone  <tag key="phone"/> , each service transmits news stories and features to subscribing newspapers. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "If you can buy and sell with a personal computer, you can't be put on hold," says William Coppel, a Quick & Reilly marketing executive.  But Michael Gianturco, author of "The Stock Market Investor's Computer Guide," notes that computers use telephone  <tag key="phone"/>  to communicate with the brokers' electronic systems.  And when the telephone lines are jammed, he says, a computerized trader won't be able to get through any better than anyone else trying desperately to call a broker, he says. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 By conservative estimates, at least $20 billion is held in accounts outside the country.  Bankers with comfortable offices overlooking crumbling Buenos Aires streets are always on the  <tag key="phone"/>  to Switzerland. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Martin L. Quinn, the president of a small marketing firm in Seal Beach, Calif., says he is tired of brokers interrupting his dinner or leaving urgent messages on his answering machine.  "I know it's a salesman when they ask, 'How are you?'" says Mr. Quinn, who stays on the  <tag key="phone"/>  only long enough to hear a brokerage firm's name. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Inside a dark tent, Kayitan Kavas, a county commissioner, shouts into a telephone for more help.  On the other end of the  <tag key="phone"/> , a voice promises 8,400 more blankets. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 He wanted to discuss a cabinet appointment with Vice President George Bush, and, thinking Mr. Bush was nearby, asked the switchboard to get him.  Soon, the vice president was on the  <tag key="phone"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 By comparison, it is usually pretty easy to track down White House and administration aides.  Top staffers have direct telephone  <tag key="phone"/>  to the White House installed in their homes. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "That was my fault," says a chastened Mr. Griscom.  Generations of White House aides confess an attachment to the disembodied voices on the other end of the telephone  <tag key="phone"/>   voices that, among other small favors, give wake-up calls to staffers going on trips. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Mr. McPherson and arms negotiator Paul Warnke both remember what happened when President Johnson tried to reach Mr. Warnke to offer him a Pentagon promotion.  The president talked for five minutes before realizing that the man on the other end of the  <tag key="phone"/>  was John Carl Warnecke, the architect. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Mr. Duggan, the former LBJ aide, once asked the switchboard to find a long-lost girlfriend in New York.  "Forty-five minutes later, they had her on the  <tag key="phone"/> ," he recalls. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 But now, even the libertine French are cracking down.  French entrepreneurs dish out pretty much the same fare that their U.S. counterparts provide: "gab"  <tag key="phone"/>  that dozens of people can dial to converse in language as off-color as strikes their fancy; private lines for one-on-one dirty talking; and prerecorded sex chatter. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The French also offer something not available in the U.S.  the pink Minitel, which allows customers to send dirty messages to one another through video terminals, called Minitels, that are attached to millions of French phones.  As in the U.S., the gab  <tag key="phone"/>  have been a big money-maker. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 But, whereas in the U.S. they are extremely difficult to regulate, in France they are being banned.  France Telecom, the nation's telecommunications authority, announced last month it will abolish the gab  <tag key="phone"/>  as of October.  "We realized that every one of the chat lines was pink {pornographic}," says a France Telecom official. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 He brushes aside protests from pink-telephone services that the action restricts free speech.  "There isn't any law that says we have to provide chat  <tag key="phone"/> ," the official says.  He estimates that the gab lines were bringing their operators at least 100 million French francs ($15.6 million) a year.  Despite the ban, French officials say their crackdown on other forms of dial-a-porn is limited by the same legal void that exists in the U.S. Nothing in French law restricts what two individuals can say over a telephone line.  Unless somebody involved can be judged guilty of "inciting debauchery," the only way to prevent pornographic services is to close down an entire category of them  as France has done with the gab lines. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The new system has already irked powerful senators.  Earlier this year, they discovered that they couldn't get more than one person on the  <tag key="phone"/>  at the same time when Senate leaders called President Reagan to tell him that the historic Intermediate Nuclear Forces treaty had been approved. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Someone identifying himself as a security officer phoned the newsroom saying he intended to kill the editor.  Obscene shouting often bursts on the  <tag key="phone"/>  in the middle of phone calls. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 But news of the trade had fans flooding the phone circuits at the Kings box office here, hungry for season tickets.  Meanwhile in Edmonton, the  <tag key="phone"/>  were jammed with disgruntled fans steaming over the defection of their star player. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The bills are actually quite similar.  Both would require airlines to report far more performance data than they do now and to set up toll-free complaint  <tag key="phone"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Chances are, the hotel operator will just let the phone in the empty room ring and ring.  Eventually, the operator may pick up the  <tag key="phone"/> , but many don't, forcing people to call back. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "If there's a loophole in your tariff you can leave it to this company to find it  quickly," says Rose Llauget, an executive at GTE Florida Inc., which runs the Tampa-area phone service.  Megaquest, meanwhile, argues that phone companies are keepers of a public utility, and shouldn't be allowed to censor what goes out over the  <tag key="phone"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 They can also choose from a variety of tapes by pushing a number on the phone. ("Press 1 for the sexiest love kittens in New York. . . .  For the pain and humiliation you deserve, you gotta push 6. . . .") Or callers can choose a one-on-one  <tag key="phone"/>  like the C-Line, which recently ended its run in Houston amid growing public pressure. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Megaquest is also a big player in the clean side of the dial-it market, such as taped jokes.  But its biggest business is in the industry's hottest and most controversial new area: the "gab"  <tag key="phone"/> , a service that dozens of people can dial at once to talk to one another.  Gab lines bring in about 70% of Megaquest's revenue.  About three-fourths of all the 400-odd gab lines in the U.S. today are Megaquest's, Mr. Eisenberg says. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 They are easily the most slippery dial-it service to regulate.  Callers on a gab  <tag key="phone"/>  are just talking to one another on the telephone, something the phone companies and the government can't very well prohibit.  Megaquest loves to talk about the support gab lines offer the shy and the lonely, as it did in a recent case in Alabama.  "Many people in Birmingham are shut-ins, people who because of a handicap, illness or old age, cannot get out of their homes frequently," the company argued in a filing before the Alabama Public Service Commission, after South Central Bell tried to stop billing for its lines. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "Through group conferencing, these people can interact with other members of the community."  Ms. Superfon says a soothing Megaquest operator on a Fresno, Calif., gab  <tag key="phone"/>  once talked a deranged Vietnam veteran out of killing himself.  Actually, it's hard to imagine the aged or the suicidal getting much comfort from many of Megaquest's gab lines. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "Welcome to the only X-rated party  <tag key="phone"/>  in town!" blares a tape that callers hear on one line before the gabbing begins.  "For a steamy sexual encounter you'll never forget, call . . . !" Another gab line calls itself "the hot centerfold line" and refers callers to another number where they can "teach an inexperienced lady about the birds and the bees!" 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Like other gab- <tag key="phone"/>  proprietors, Megaquest hires operators to monitor callers.  That is ostensibly to keep disruptive people off the lines, and to enforce the ground rules of its special teen service: no callers over 17, no cursing and no talk about drugs or sex. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Not surprisingly, the rules are loosely enforced.  On one recent afternoon on the New York teen  <tag key="phone"/> , a caller could hear Tony and Robert screaming obscenely at each other in an argument about their virility. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 One important role monitors play is to juice up conversations whenever they lag.  The monitor on Megaquest's bisexual  <tag key="phone"/>  recently got the conversation rolling by discussing the relative merits of different gender combinations. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Another job for the monitors is steering customers to Megaquest's out-and-out porn services.  One wall poster in the New York office lists a special number and adds: "The most important  <tag key="phone"/> ! 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 That's a number Megaquest uses for various extra-pricey, hard-core porn services.  This side of the gab  <tag key="phone"/>  is one you won't learn about in Megaquest's filings with the public-service commission. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 To a lot of parents, what Megaquest does is turn their telephones into raunchy, high-priced jukeboxes.  Cincinnati Bell started running gab  <tag key="phone"/>  last year and was stunned to see customer complaints double. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 But lawmakers and the industry are finding that writing dial-it regulations that stand up to scrutiny is as hard as nailing Jell-O to the wall.  Phone companies, as regulated common carriers, can't always simply stop doing business with  <tag key="phone"/>  they deem offensive.  Southwestern Bell tried to quit billing for gab lines by arguing that the state rules authorizing its dial-it services covered taped messages, not live talk. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "Sex sells," he says.  The public firestorm has made him a little hesitant about launching expensive new X-rated  <tag key="phone"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Business at Southwestern Bell Corp. nearly hit rock bottom last year.  Operating in the depressed oil patch of Oklahoma and Texas and the hardscrabble farm states of Arkansas, Kansas and Missouri, the company posted its poorest telephone- <tag key="phone"/>  growth since the Great Depression: fewer than 8,200 new residential lines and an actual reduction of business lines. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 So far, the technique is working.  Since January, Southwestern Bell has sold about 16,000 new  <tag key="phone"/>  to current business customers by introducing them to various features of Integrated Services Digital Network, such as "inspect," which displays the name and telephone number of the party calling. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Since January, Southwestern Bell has sold about 16,000 new  <tag key="phone"/>  to current business customers by introducing them to various features of Integrated Services Digital Network, such as "inspect," which displays the name and telephone number of the party calling.  Impressed by what they learned in the lab, Tenneco Inc., Shell Oil Co. and Minnesota Mining & Manufacturing Co. each bought more than 3,000 new lines.  For instance, the laboratory experience helped Houston-based Tenneco to decide to buy 3,900 more lines for an advanced network that integrates voice and data traffic. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 THE DIRECTIONS must be designed as carefully as the product itself, more companies are finding.  For instance, Prodigy Services Co., a joint venture of International Business Machines Corp. and Sears, Roebuck & Co., worked for three years to develop its system for shopping and retrieving information from a home computer over telephone  <tag key="phone"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Twelve air-traffic "flow control" centers in Europe coordinate these crisis-control actions by telex or telephone.  Flowcontrol units in London, Paris, Madrid, Rome and Frankfurt, West Germany, soon will be linked with special teleconference circuits so they won't have to rely on telephone  <tag key="phone"/> , which often are busy. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 He says further that he hasn't been paid for some of his work.  The West Palm Beach and New York telephone  <tag key="phone"/>  of Millionaire's publisher, Douglas Lambert, have been disconnected. . . . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 San Francisco-based Pacific Telesis said a robust California economy, streamlined operations and curbs on expenses were the key factors for its profit gain.  Business and residential  <tag key="phone"/>  increased 4% to 12.7 million, up 488,000 from a year ago. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The company's Cincinnati Bell Information Systems unit contributed $38.2 million to revenue in the quarter and $73.8 million in the six months.  The Cincinnati-based telecommunications concern said it added about 8,234 new  <tag key="phone"/>  in the quarter, boosting the total to about 755,000. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Philadelphia-based Bell Atlantic said its second-quarter earnings increase was bolstered primarily by economic expansion in the mid-Atlantic region.  For instance, business telephone  <tag key="phone"/>  jumped 6.8% to five million from 4.7 million.  The total number of new lines grew 3.4% to 16.2 million, compared with 15.7 million a year ago. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Nynex said telephone operations remain strong.  The company said it added more than 479,000 telephone  <tag key="phone"/>  in the quarter, boosting the total to 14.6 million. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Regional long-distance revenue increased 13% to $345.3 million from $305.2 million.  New telephone  <tag key="phone"/>  grew 2.5% to 11.7 million from 11.4 million. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The New York State Public Employees Federation in Albany wins three pilot evening-shift day-care centers in a yet-to-be-ratified pact.  LATCHKEY KIDS placed so many calls to Whirlpool Corp.'s consumer information  <tag key="phone"/>  appealing for help with appliances that the company conducted a survey, which found big use of appliances among school-age kids home alone. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Two regional Bell telecommunications concerns posted higher second-quarter earnings, bolstered primarily by strong growth of telephone access  <tag key="phone"/> , while a third Bell company reported a decrease. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Earnings for Chicago-based Ameritech soared, aided primarily by strong growth in telephone and cellular  <tag key="phone"/>  and a one-time gain from the sale of Canadian cellular operations. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The company posted a $42.1 million gain from the sale of its 17% interest in Cantel, a Canadian cellular company.  Business and residential telephone  <tag key="phone"/>  increased 2.4% to 15.2 million, up 354,000 from a year ago.  Cellular-mobile lines grew 58% to more than 100,000. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Total operating expenses increased 15% in the quarter, primarily because of costs relating to the elimination of Silver Pages operations and increased telephone company expenditures.  The company said more than 83,000 telephone access  <tag key="phone"/>  were added in the 1988 second quarter, compared with only 5,000 for the like period last year. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 BellSouth, based in Atlanta, said earnings rose because of increases in new customer  <tag key="phone"/>  and toll usage. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Revenue climbed 6.3% to $3.21 billion from $3.02 billion.  The company said it added more than 133,500 access  <tag key="phone"/>  in its nine-state territory, boosting the total to about 16 million. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 So the company's Southern Bell unit in Atlanta and its South Central Bell unit in New Orleans have been installing hundreds of miles of fiber optic cable; preparing links from inside the convention centers to satellite relay trucks that will be parked outside; installing public phones with special jacks to accommodate data transmission on laptop computers; and putting in new cells to handle the hundreds of cellular phones that many news organizations plan to bring.  Southern Bell has been furiously installing about 3,600  <tag key="phone"/>  at the World Congress Center in Atlanta for the Democratic convention starting today. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Calling on one  <tag key="phone"/>  is a campaign aide deep into negotiations with the Jesse Jackson campaign over the rules for the 1992 presidential election.  On another line is Robert Strauss, the former Democratic chairman. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 After his success in advertising, Mr. Ezoe looked to diversify.  When Recruit began renting communications  <tag key="phone"/>  to tie its nationwide computers together, it discovered it could sell time on those lines. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 John E. Hulse, vice chairman and chief financial officer, predicted that network usage for the Pacific Bell and Nevada Bell units will increase about 7% to 10% this year.  He said the number of new customer  <tag key="phone"/>  is expected to grow about 3% to 5%.  In 1987, the two telephone operations combined had $2.14 billion in network-usage revenue and they added about 462,000 customer lines, a 3.8% gain. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Currently, New York-based AT&T leases more conventional consumer phones at $2.70 to $8.85 a month.  The telecommunications company added it will begin leasing three other specialized models, including one with two  <tag key="phone"/> , in August. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 In the past week, he also has fielded calls from reporters around the world.  Last Friday, an associate of New York television personality Geraldo Rivera was on the  <tag key="phone"/> , asking Mr. Finckle to appear as his talk-show guest. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 An even tougher problem is the distressed economy of the company's regional service territory, hit hard by the energy slump and the drought.  Last year, the company's core telephone business added only 8,100 new access  <tag key="phone"/> , the poorest annual growth volume since the Great Depression. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The U.S. will maintain diplomatic relations with Haiti's military government following a coup Monday that returned military leader Namphy to power after four months of civilian rule, the State Department said.  Schools, markets and businesses in Port-au-Prince were reopened, and international telephone  <tag key="phone"/>  were restored. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The Information Age has been put on hold.  By now, consumers nationwide could have been taking advantage of all kinds of special services through their telephone  <tag key="phone"/>   checking airline schedules or baseball scores, tracking prices of their favorite stocks, arranging to watch pay-for-view movies on their TV sets. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The decline in first-quarter profit reflected a shift in Northern's Canadian production to less profitable wire and cable products during a four-week strike in March at its main Canadian plant in Bramalea, Ontario, where telephone switches are produced.  Central-office switches, which accounted for 53% of Northern's revenue last year, are used by telephone companies to route voice and data communications over telephone  <tag key="phone"/> .  Mr. Fitzgerald said he expects that sales of switches, as measured by new telephone lines, "are going to flatten out" during the next few years, and that increased competition in North America will continue to drive down prices. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The five-year, profit-sharing venture will provide U.S. news organizations, businesses and other users with direct telephone communications and digital transmission of data, photos and other information to and from the Soviet Union.  Only 11 dedicated telephone communications  <tag key="phone"/>  currently exist between the two countries, company officials said. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Her question: How can she raise a child on a $1.75 refund check?  Then there is the girl who ran up a $600 telephone bill dialing toll-call party  <tag key="phone"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Advanced Micro Devices Inc., Sunnyvale, Calif., and Siemens AG of West Germany said they agreed to jointly develop, manufacture and market microchips for data communications and telecommunications with an emphasis on the integrated services digital network.  The integrated services digital network, or ISDN, is an international standard used to transmit voice, data, graphics and video images over telephone  <tag key="phone"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Atlanta-based BellSouth recently gave the party  <tag key="phone"/>  a new function and renamed it Ring Master.  Atlanta-based BellSouth recently gave the party line a new function and renamed it Ring Master.  The service allows a residential customer to have as many as three telephone numbers fed into the home through the existing single telephone line. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 And, as in the good old days, people will be able to listen in on conversations from other extensions  but only within the same household.  While any one of the  <tag key="phone"/>  is in use, neither incoming nor outgoing calls can be made on the other extensions that are part of the service.  Ring Master costs about $4 a month for one additional number, and BellSouth will promote it as an inexpensive alternative to separate lines, for which the monthly fee totals $12 to $20, depending on geographical location. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Dial-a-porn has been a point of contention for several years.  Anti-pornography groups and parents have fought vigorously to keep sexually explicit messages off the telephone  <tag key="phone"/>  because children could easily call the services. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 EXECUTIVES INSTALL high-tech equipment in houses to ease take-home chores.  Bert Roberts Jr., president of MCI Communications Corp., has two computers, three telephone  <tag key="phone"/>  and a copying machine to handle the work he brings home at night and on weekends. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Japan wants to block competitive foreign technology from a lucrative telecommunications market, U.S. trade negotiators said.  The negotiators said they learned in trade talks with the Japanese this week that Japan's Ministry of Posts and Telecommunications wants to limit technologies used in value-added networks, or VANs  services that allow computers to communicate with one another over telephone  <tag key="phone"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 That business is far and away the company's fastest-growing and most profitable segment.  The information  <tag key="phone"/> , which includes everything from reference books such as Who's Who to trade guides for lawyers and health-care professionals, has grown to $229 million in sales in 1987 from $146 million in 1985. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 One of Nasdaq's technological innovations  its trans-Pacific link with Singapore  went on the blink, and some traders half-jokingly groused that volume might have been slightly stronger otherwise.  Nasdaq said the link with Sesdaq (Stock Exchange of Singapore Dealing and Automated Quotations System) was suspended yesterday morning because of  <tag key="phone"/>  problems in the U.S. Introduced in March, the link allows Nasdaq and Sesdaq to exchange quotes on about 35 Nasdaq securities traded in both markets. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 For Kodak, the trade-in already has been a costly public relations headache.  It has spent an estimated $17 million, much of it for a toll-free  <tag key="phone"/>  it has kept open for two years and for a variety of early notices it sent to camera holders. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Precise terms weren't disclosed.  Lakewood, which serves 1,275 access  <tag key="phone"/>  in a 25-square-mile territory in eastern Pennsylvania, had revenue last year of about $750,000.  Lakewood will become the fifth Pennsylvania telephone company purchased by Rochester, N.Y.-based Rochester Telephone, giving it a total of 26,000 access lines served throughout the state. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Since then, they have amended their misguided messages and bombarded the market with new advertisements.  Now, at the end of each commercial, Pacific Telesis tells viewers, "We're in the business to move information and keep it moving over telephone  <tag key="phone"/> , over cellular systems, over computer networks we design." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The technology exists so that the dial-a-something services  dial-a-porn, dial-a-preacher, dial-an-oddsmaker  can be regulated by the phone company or by the phone owner.  With some technology, a phone company could simply block a resident's  <tag key="phone"/>  at his request so that no one could make those dial-it numbers from his house. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Almost all would agree that kids shouldn't be running up phone bills by dialing dirty talkers; it's bad for the parent's wallet and probably bad for the child's mind.  But the argument can't be made that adults shouldn't be able to call these smut  <tag key="phone"/>  if they want to. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Pacific Telesis Group said its first-quarter earnings surged, bolstered primarily by the strong California economy, streamlined operations and its early retirement program.  San Francisco-based Pacific Telesis said access  <tag key="phone"/>  increased 3.7% to 12.6 million and local-long distance volume jumped 9.3% to 684 million. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The communications company also built a small call-switching room in Home Shopping's building and beefed up parts of its own network to handle the additional traffic.  From MCI's  <tag key="phone"/> , traffic is switched to a Rockwell International Corp. automatic call distributor; the system also uses Unisys Corp. ordering equipment. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 COLLECT CALLS: Two-thirds of the major companies surveyed by recruiter Korn/Ferry International say they pay outside directors an average of $712 for each telephone conference in which they participate.  And the vast majority get the full fee no matter how long they're on the  <tag key="phone"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The plaintiff, United Missouri Bank of Kansas City, alleges that Kemper mismanaged $8 million in pension funds right before the market debacle in October.  In general, some holders of stock funds complained after the crash that they couldn't get through clogged telephone  <tag key="phone"/>  or that fund companies failed to honor their redemption requests in a timely fashion. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Southwestern Bell provides telephone service to the hard-hit oil states of Oklahoma and Texas, as well as to Arkansas, Kansas and Missouri, which have felt some of the economic pressures of the farm belt.  Last year the company gained only 8,100 new telephone  <tag key="phone"/> , the worst year for growth since the Great Depression. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Annual revenue of general interest dial-up services total about $186 million, estimates Information Industry Bulletin, a Stamford, Conn., industry newsletter.  That compares with dial-a-porn revenue of $54 million and revenue of about $90 million from so-called gab  <tag key="phone"/> , where customers call up and chat with others who are on the line.  Gab lines have a reputation only slightly better than dial-a-porn among some parents because teen-agers run up steep phone bills talking for hours. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Independent of Congress, several local phone companies already are introducing plans to block calls to porn and gab  <tag key="phone"/>  because of complaints by subscribers.  Bell Atlantic Corp. plans to block all porn and gab lines in Pennsylvania and Maryland.  Customers there that want to dial these services would have to write the phone companies to unblock the lines. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Some Democratic lawmakers want to make these plans mandatory  and free.  According to several plans under consideration, phone companies would be required to assign different phone number exchanges to dial-a-porn services, gab  <tag key="phone"/>  and general dial-up services. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Behind a glass window sits the moderator.  He is about to get a report from Washington when the telephone  <tag key="phone"/>  dies. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 There was no response.  Later, when we phoned again, the  <tag key="phone"/>  was disconnected." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Telephone  <tag key="phone"/>  are about to get busier. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "Am I the toughest guy you know?"  The friend on the other end of the  <tag key="phone"/>  can be heard saying, "You're tough all right. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Some of Mr. Abboud's advisers had already left for Houston to begin poring over First City's books, but the banking concern's chairman and president, Daniel C. Arnold, was on the phone and was balking.  On another  <tag key="phone"/>  was First City's investment banker, Goldman Sachs & Co.  On the third line, advisers to Mr. Abboud.  And on the fourth line, officials from the FDIC. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Merrill Lynch declined to comment.  Most of those affected by Fidelity's latest layoffs worked on the investment group's toll-free telephone  <tag key="phone"/> , in back-office processing jobs and in Fidelity's discount brokerage. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The party- <tag key="phone"/>  effect could defeat that.  Officials of Telaction say if lines get jammed there is a built-in queuing function to call a customer to the phone when it's his or her turn to shop. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 There, he works at a Formica desk stacked high with newspapers and mail in an open New York newsroom with a dozen other people.  He has two phones that seldom stop ringing, plus a  <tag key="phone"/>  for his best sources  a network of traders, raiders and sundry other tipsters. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 But he doesn't apologize for the idea, because ZapMail was an effort to address a real and continuing problem.  Facsimile machines, which transmit documents over telephone  <tag key="phone"/> , are eating into Federal's overnight business. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 AT&T later developed a form of picture phone for business meetings, but it was too cumbersome and costly for consumers.  Now Mitsubishi Electric Corp. of Japan has begun selling VisiTel, a telephone accessory that uses a built-in camera to send still pictures over ordinary  <tag key="phone"/> .  The user sits in front of the camera, frames a picture on a small video screen, and presses a button to send it, about five or six seconds later, to the VisiTel on the other end of the line. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Meanwhile, expenses climbed 12.2% to $2.49 billion from $2.22 billion.  The company said more than 185,000 new access  <tag key="phone"/>  were added in its nine-state territory, boosting the total to more than 15.9 million. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Philadelphia-based Bell Atlantic's earnings increased as intrastate toll use grew 11.2% and interstate access volume climbed almost 13%.  The company said total access  <tag key="phone"/>  grew 3.5% to 16.1 million. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 If a product triggers a flood of calls, she can soften her presentation or spread it out a few more minutes.  "We've even had situations where we've told the audience, 'Don't call now because the  <tag key="phone"/>  will be busy for a while,' " says Jerry Troupe, executive assistant to Home Shopping Network Inc.'s chairman, Roy Speer. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Toward that end, Mr. Gibbs has increased by 21% to 253 the number of so-called problem-resolution officers and their assistants, who intervene in taxpayers' disputes with the agency.  He has hired more clerks to handle telephone inquiries, increased the number of incoming telephone  <tag key="phone"/> , and expanded the hours the public can call for assistance. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Ameritech's outlook is based on expectations for steady economic growth in the Midwest-Great Lakes region, a densely populated and generally stable area.  Mr. Springer predicted that combined network usage for Ameritech's five Bell operating companies will increase this year "in the upper end of the 4% to 8% range" and the number of customer  <tag key="phone"/>  will grow by "better than 1-plus per cent."  In 1987, total network access usage grew about 10.5% and Ameritech added about 340,000 customer lines, a 2.3% gain. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Most dial-up services charge about 50 cents a minute, but dial-a-porn messages can run a few dollars for the first minute.  Independent of Congress, several local phone companies already are introducing plans to block calls to porn and gab  <tag key="phone"/>  because of complaints by subscribers.  Bell Atlantic Corp. plans to block all porn and gab lines in Pennsylvania and Maryland.  Customers there that want to dial these services would have to write the phone companies to unblock the lines.  Pacific Bell, a unit of Pacific Telesis Group, lets consumers block calls for free to all 976 dial-up services, and soon plans to give consumers the option of just blocking calls to adult messages or gab lines. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 So far 450,000 subscribers have signed up for the 976 blocking service.  New York Telephone, a part of Nynex Corp., plans to offer  for a one-time charge of $5  call blocking to dial-a-porn and chat  <tag key="phone"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Previously, the Fed lacked the effectiveness of the West German Bundesbank or Bank of Japan, they add.  A currency dealer at a New York bank with a direct  <tag key="phone"/>  to the Fed says that previously, "when the Fed would come in, the dollar would almost always go against them. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 By contrast, BellSouth Corp., which operates in the robust Sun Belt, added more than 650,000 new  <tag key="phone"/>  last year.  In 1988, with the health of its service territory showing slight signs of improvement, Southwestern Bell expects telephone lines to increase about 1%, which would represent about 100,000 new lines. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Met with outrage, the plan was hastily abandoned.  Other innovations, such as banking at home via personal computer and telephone  <tag key="phone"/> , have been painfully slow to catch on. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Analysts said the two-year contract probably makes the Swedish telecommunications group the leading supplier of telecommunications equipment to China.  Ericsson already has installed or taken orders for about 442,000  <tag key="phone"/>  in China, and has a few smaller orders to supply switching equipment. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Terms weren't disclosed.  Telefonica Nacional had operating revenue equivalent to $5.3 billion last year; it has 10 million  <tag key="phone"/>  in service, with 15 million telephones in use, making Spain's system the ninth-largest in the world. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The program was proving so popular that H&R Block apparently couldn't keep up with preparing all the returns.  Consequently, the spokesman at the Kansas City, Mo.-based company said, computer capacity has been increased 50%, more telephone  <tag key="phone"/>  have been added and additional workers hired to handle the backlog of customers seeking to file electronically. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Instead of hiring tellers and account officers to take deposits in the office, they advertise deposit rates in regional newspapers.  Customers call on toll-free telephone  <tag key="phone"/>  and conduct transactions by mail, by wire or through an automated-teller network shared with other banks. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Mr. Allbach says he is beginning to suspect that Kodak instigated the suit, hoping everyone will pitch their cameras.  Kodak denies that and says the delay is costing it a bundle in legal expenses, not to mention the cost of maintaining an 800 telephone  <tag key="phone"/>  for instant camera owners. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Separately, a federal appeals court in New York dealt the dial-a-porn business another setback, affirming long-contested regulations that make it harder to dial raunchy phone tapes.  The two developments are the latest shots in a bitter battle over dial-a-porn, which is becoming widespread both on AT&T and local phone-company  <tag key="phone"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Telephones were busier than usual at Fidelity Investments over the weekend  but far less busy than the weekend that preceded October's Black Monday.  Fidelity, the nation's largest mutual-fund group, estimated that it received about 45,000 calls  28% more than usual  on its 24-hour customer service  <tag key="phone"/>  during the weekend in the wake of Friday's 140.58-point drop in the Dow Jones Industrial Average. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Finding him became an obsession for Mr. Stoll.  He made a midnight requisition of all the printers he could lay hands on so that he could monitor all the telephone  <tag key="phone"/>  coming into the lab's computers.  After discovering that the hacker had taken over the dormant account of a legitimate user named Joe Sventek, he rigged up an alarm system, including a portable beeper, to alert him when Sventek came on the line. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Currently a $300 million-a-year business, 900 telephone service is expected to hit $500 million next year and near $2 billion by 1992 as uses for the service continue to expand, says Joel Gross of Donaldson, Lufkin & Jenrette Inc.  The service  which costs the caller from 30 cents to $25 a minute  currently is dominated by celebrity chatter, horoscopes and romance  <tag key="phone"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Richard Breeden hadn't noticed that his new desk had just four telephone  <tag key="phone"/>  and one phone. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 It was, after all, only his second full day as chairman of the Securities and Exchange Commission.  But the lack of  <tag key="phone"/>  became painfully apparent.  As the stock market lurched into a 190-point free fall on Oct. 13, Mr. Breeden found himself scurrying around the sixth floor of the SEC  from his desk, where the New York Stock Exchange was on an open line, to his assistant's office, where the Commodity Futures Trading Commission was connected, to a third room, where a computer monitored market moves. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 It won't happen again.  Now there are more  <tag key="phone"/>  connected to the chairman's office, and the market-monitoring computer has been moved next to his desk. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Rochester will exchange shares of its common stock for all shares outstanding of Viroqua Telephone, a family-owned company.  Viroqua serves about 3,000 access  <tag key="phone"/>  in western Wisconsin. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Place a phone order through most any catalog and chances are the clerk who answers won't be the only one on the  <tag key="phone"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Meanwhile, supporters of the Dellums two-party consent bill say it is needed because of a giant loophole in the one-party consent law.  Currently, if the person taping is a party to the conversation, it's all right to record without the knowledge of the other person on the  <tag key="phone"/> . (Intercepting other people's private conversations is illegal and punishable by five years in prison and fines of $10,000.) 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Overall they increased 2.8% to 12.1 million, putting U S West over the 12 million mark for the first time.  Business  <tag key="phone"/>  increased 3.7% to 3.3 million. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The three-month-old strike at Nynex seriously hurt the installation of new telephone  <tag key="phone"/>  in the quarter.  Nynex said access lines in service at the end of the quarter were off 18,000 from the previous quarter, which reported an increase of 160,000 new access lines. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Meanwhile, the FEMA announced a toll-free telephone number (800-462-9029) to expedite service to victims of the earthquake.   <tag key="phone"/>  will be available 24 hours a day to take applications for such disaster relief as temporary housing and emergency home repairs by phone. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Contel Corp. said third-quarter net income increased 16% to $72 million, or 45 cents a share, from $62 million, or 39 cents a share, as a result of strong growth in telephone-access  <tag key="phone"/>  and long-distance minutes of use. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Information systems posted a loss of $8 million, compared with a loss of $9 million a year earlier.  Customer-access  <tag key="phone"/>  increased at an annualized rate of about 4% and minutes of long-distance use rose about 12%. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Revenues rose 8.8% to $4.35 billion from $4.0 billion.  The company said the quarter included a 10% increase in local-exchange usage for long-distance calling and a 5% increase in the number of access  <tag key="phone"/>  in service. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Chairman Zane E. Barnes said Southwestern Bell's "businesses are healthy and are continuing to grow."  The company reported a 3.1% increase in the number of access  <tag key="phone"/>  in service, and also said its Southwestern Bell Mobile Systems unit added 30,000 new customers, with a current total of about 333,000. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 In composite trading on the New York Stock Exchange, Cincinnati Bell fell 25 cents to $29.  The company said that the number of access  <tag key="phone"/>  dropped slightly in the quarter, a decline attributed to seasonal fluctuations.  For the year, however, access lines in service have increased 5.5%. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Although two Baby Bells showed strong growth in access  <tag key="phone"/> , usage and unregulated business revenue, one reported a modest gain in third-quarter net while the other posted a small drop. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 BellSouth  At BellSouth, based in Atlanta, customer access  <tag key="phone"/>  grew by 162,000, or 3.5%, during the 12-month period ended Sept. 30. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 In addition, earnings were reduced by rate reductions in Florida, Kentucky, Alabama, Tennessee and Louisiana.  Ameritech At Ameritech, based in Chicago, customer access  <tag key="phone"/>  increased by 402,000, or 2.6%, and cellular mobile lines increased by 80,000, or 62.3%, for the 12-month period ended Sept. 30. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The use of 900 toll numbers has been expanding rapidly in recent years.  For a while, high-cost pornography  <tag key="phone"/>  and services that tempt children to dial (and redial) movie or music information earned the service a somewhat sleazy image, but new legal restrictions are aimed at trimming excesses. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Kurt Sanger, ABC Sports's marketing director, says that now "tens of thousands" of fans call its 900 number each week to vote for the best punt return, quarterback sack, etc.  Profit from the calls goes to charity, but ABC Sports also uses the calls as a sales tool: After thanking callers for voting, Frank Gifford offers a football videotape for $19.95, and 5% of callers stay on the  <tag key="phone"/>  to order it. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Jackets may be sold next.  Meanwhile, NBC Sports recently began "Scores Plus," a year-round, 24-hour 900  <tag key="phone"/>  providing a complex array of scores, analysis and fan news. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Viewers can call a 900 number for additional advice, which will be tailored to their needs based on the numbers they punch ("Press one if you're pregnant," etc.).  If the caller stays on the  <tag key="phone"/>  and leaves a name and address for the sponsor, coupons and a newsletter will be mailed, and the sponsor will be able to gather a list of desirable potential customers. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The biggest flurry of investor activity came early in the day.  Vanguard Group Inc. saw heavy exchanges from stock funds into money market funds after the telephone  <tag key="phone"/>  opened at 8:30 a.m. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 But analysts say that on short flights, if many passengers pick up their phones at once, the wait for a dial tone could be longer than the flight.  An America West Airlines spokeswoman concedes, "You might have to wait three to five minutes to get a  <tag key="phone"/> ." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The New York plan froze basic rates, offered no protection to Nynex against an economic downturn that sharply cut demand and didn't offer flexible pricing.  In contrast, the California economy is booming, with 4.5% access  <tag key="phone"/>  growth in the past year. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Communications would be even worse in the old downtown section of the city, where Gen. Noriega maintained his military headquarters complex.  CIA officials hadn't provided Maj. Giroldi or his allies with any means to communicate with the Southern Command, nor did they arrange to keep a telephone  <tag key="phone"/>  open to Gen. Noriega's headquarters. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 So, after rebels apparently had seized the building, several U.S. officials attempted in vain to contact them by phone to determine what had become of Gen. Noriega.  Some of their outgoing calls were interrupted by their own switchboard operators, who chastised the officials for using  <tag key="phone"/>  they had been ordered to keep free. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 St. Croix Telephone would be the fourth telephone concern in Wisconsin  and the tenth in the Midwest  acquired by Rochester Telephone in the past year.  St. Croix Telephone serves 5,300 access  <tag key="phone"/>  near Minneapolis.  Rochester Telephone serves 575,000 access lines, primarily in Western-Central New York. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "Consolidated expenses will be higher than anticipated as a result of certain nonrecurring expenses, including legal fees," the company said, adding also that revenue has been below its projections.  In the past year, Rochester Telephone, which serves more than 570,000  <tag key="phone"/> , mainly in Western-Central New York, has acquired or announced agreements to acquire nine Midwestern telephone companies  five in Illinois, three in Wisconsin and one in Indiana. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Ebaugh, the show's creator.  "Earthbeat's" activism will be reflected in its use of telephone  <tag key="phone"/>  to record viewers' opinions on issues and perhaps invite them to add their names to "electronic petitions" to be sent to politicians or corporations. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 For instance, the technology isn't sophisticated enough to recognize unusual accents.  Moreover, some people still don't like talking to a machine, forcing them to stay on the  <tag key="phone"/>  until a human operator eventually picks up the call. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Its 10 million people are burdened with an $18 billion debt, stuck with a defunct infrastructure and a technologically untrained work force.  In Budapest offices, secretaries often work in groups to make a single call on one of the country's huge, pea-green telephone "machines," which have plenty of levers and flashing lights but a poor record of finding a free  <tag key="phone"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Now, field representatives drop by each store every few days, clipboards in hand, to evaluate customer-oriented operations.  Also, to make sure that customers have a direct  <tag key="phone"/>  to the company, Burger King is installing a toll-free phone number for consumer feedback. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Barry K. Davis, the founder of Traders & Investors Alert, a telephone stock-tip  <tag key="phone"/> , is expected to disassociate himself from the service within a few weeks. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 It declined to disclose the number of shares involved.  Mt. Pulaski Telephone, which would be Rochester Telephone's fifth Illinois telephone concern, serves about 1,800  <tag key="phone"/>  in central Illinois. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Despite the name, Mt. Pulaski no longer has electric customers, Rochester said.  Rochester Telephone, which serves more than 570,000  <tag key="phone"/> , mainly in Western-Central New York state, has acquired or announced agreements to acquire eight Midwestern telephone companies this year  five in Illinois, two in Wisconsin and one in Indiana. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 A previous increase occurred last May, when the San Francisco AIDS Foundation issued a strong plea for people to consider early testing and treatment.  In New York City last week, "Eight to 14 telephone  <tag key="phone"/>  were ringing at once, in contrast to the usual four to five," said Susan Rosenthal, director of AIDS counseling and testing for seven city test sites. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Pacific Telecom, Vancouver, Wash., also has agreed to retain for five years all current employees of the city's telephone company and to refrain from requesting new rate increases in that period.  In April, Anchorage requested bids on its telephone system, setting a minimum price of $400 million for its 115,000  <tag key="phone"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Securities regulators are investigating a New Jersey-based telephone tip  <tag key="phone"/>  that has been getting attention for its blend of "inside" Wall Street research, gossip and investment advice.  The tip line, Traders & Investors Alert, based in Fort Lee, N.J., is run by a 46-year-old former insurance broker and publicist, Barry K. Davis, who has run afoul of regulators in the past. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Critics say it could be a vehicle for stock manipulators.  Oddly, many of the people that seem to be calling the tip  <tag key="phone"/>  are Wall Street brokers, hungry for stock tips they say aren't available from their own research departments. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "We have put Traders & Investors on notice that they appear to be operating as an unregistered investment adviser," says Richard Barry, supervisor of enforcement with the New Jersey agency.  Meanwhile, the SEC, which is aware of the Traders & Investors  <tag key="phone"/>  and the growing attention being given to it, declines to comment on whether it's investigating. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 In contrast, Pacific Telesis has won back many private- <tag key="phone"/>  and Centrex customers since it gained the right to reduce rates.  California's booming economy helped give Pacific Telesis the highest second-quarter growth in access lines among the Baby Bells. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Prospects for modernizing Jiangsu's antiquated telephone system also have dimmed.  The province's population of 61 million surpasses that of France, but Jiangsu's phone system can handle only 50,000  <tag key="phone"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 American Express Co. and American Telephone & Telegraph Co. have formed a partnership to expand in interactive telephone marketing.  The new company, Call Interactive, will use the telephone  <tag key="phone"/>  for an array of sales and market-research services. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The acquisitions of six other companies are pending, with completion scheduled before year end.  Rochester Telephone expects to serve more than 600,000 access  <tag key="phone"/>  in six states when the acquisitions are completed. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Callers are invited to play interactive games with the movie's characters, to enter sweepstakes and, of course, to run, don't walk, to the nearest theater.  Toll telephone services have mostly been the stuff of pornography  <tag key="phone"/>  and of children's horror-story and Santa Claus lines.  But movie marketers hope they can use the lines to entice potential moviegoers, especially teen-agers and young adults. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Even better from the marketer's point of view: The calls cost money, so marketers can break even or even turn a profit, in effect charging people to be subjected to advertising.  Typical of the new services is the Indiana Jones  <tag key="phone"/> , which costs $2.50 for a two-minute story. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Sen. Howard Metzenbaum (D., Ohio) has threatened to propose legislation curtailing phone  <tag key="phone"/>  advertised to children.  While the movie lines say they are geared towards older teens, they are advertised on MTV and cable stations watched by younger children, too. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 To combat the critics, Interactive TeleMedia, a Los Angeles-based firm specializing in 900 numbers for the entertainment business, has come up with a system to block multiple calls.  Its system would allow a movie  <tag key="phone"/> , for example, to accept only a certain number of calls from a single phone number. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Interactive has worked with Paramount, Lucasfilm and others, but so far hasn't used the blocking system.  "The abuse has been in sex  <tag key="phone"/>  and gab lines, and we don't have either. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 We've had absolutely no complaints," says Barclay Lottimer, vice president of sales and marketing.  Still, the  <tag key="phone"/>  are far from a sure thing, and it's too soon to say if they even work. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Since then, Paramount's "Star Trek V" and "Indiana Jones" have followed, while Orion's "Great Balls of Fire" has experimented with a 900 number in a very limited way.  So far, though, most of the phone  <tag key="phone"/>  have been disappointing.  Interactive's Mr. Lottimer, for example, says he expected to get more than one million phone calls on the "Star Trek" and "Indiana Jones" lines, which his company worked on, but response was in the "high six figures" instead. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "The key is to be able to handle those calls," says Ronald A. Katz, president and chief executive officer.  He says his company will be looking into movie  <tag key="phone"/> , as well as record promotions in which, say, callers could hear a preview of a new Madonna song. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The drawbacks haven't prevented film marketers from continuing to dabble, if cautiously, in untested waters.  D.L. Blair is working on a 900  <tag key="phone"/>  to coincide with the Aug. 31 video release of "Bill and Ted's Excellent Adventure," a teen movie starring George Carlin as a time traveler.  A TV commercial plugging the line will run on MTV, and a long promotional spiel for the toll line will appear on the video.  Blair's Mr. Ellman says the company is also working on a 900 line to coincide with an animated Christmas video release and a major feature film for next summer.  Still, plenty of moviemakers are steering clear of the 900 number lines, wary of the sometimes sleazy reputation of the business. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Some of your old henchmen at the Yard doing their stuff , splendidly .   Been on the  <tag key="phone"/>  to them on and off all day . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 In the back row sit Mission Control's brass .   Alongside Kraft sits Mission Director George Hage , who has direct  <tag key="phone"/>  from his console to the White House , the State Department and NASA'S Washington headquarters . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Contributed by Mary-Jo Jansson Van B. Fox , who directed NBC'S live program series , " Wide , Wide World , " tells about a show on America's mountains : There were five location directors working in the field , and I was directing from the control center in New York .   We had just come to the last three minutes on the air , when suddenly the producer barked a warning : " Van , they've lost the  <tag key="phone"/>  from the next location . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 " Now that's panic time , for TV'S cardinal rule is : The programs must end on time !   I punched a button opening my  <tag key="phone"/>  to Joe Behar , the director in Colorado : " Joe , we've got to stretch . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 " Hello . "   But by now the  <tag key="phone"/>  was dead . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Alvin jerked up the phone and shouted " Hello ! "   The  <tag key="phone"/>  was dead . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 He crossed to the desk and lifted the telephone .   The  <tag key="phone"/>  was dead . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 She would send Philippe a telegram .   Help could not be had by talking into a dead  <tag key="phone"/>  , but no one in his family would leave a telegram unread . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 There was nothing new about the boy .   One of Tibbs's fellow investigators came on the  <tag key="phone"/>  briefly ; he had made a quick check of the area where the shooting had taken place . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 " Mommy , " came a very small voice , " did you say I killed him ? " " Johnny ... " she began when another voice cut into the  <tag key="phone"/>  . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Then he held his breath . "   Mr. Tibbs , " the voice of Maggie McGuire came tearfully over the  <tag key="phone"/>  , " I've heard from Johnny ! " 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 " Did he say where he was , Mrs. McGuire ? "   A suppressed sob came over the  <tag key="phone"/>  . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 " Why , yes .   The operator came on the  <tag key="phone"/>  , like they do , and said that three minutes were up and to signal when we were through . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 At last there was a response , he listened for a moment and then passed the phone to Tibbs . "   Tom Satriano is on the  <tag key="phone"/>  , " he advised . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 What's your trouble ? "   On the other end of the  <tag key="phone"/>  , in the forward torpedo room of the Squalus , Lt. ( j. g. ) John Nichols struggled to maintain his composure . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 " There was a short pause before Oliver Naquin said with quiet elation , " Hello , Wilkie . "   But just as Wilkin started to respond , the Sculpin rose high on an ocean swell and the  <tag key="phone"/>  went dead . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 In his position , I'd have had to do the same thing . "   A wild laugh reached Ainslie from the other end of the  <tag key="phone"/>  . " 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 That was all she was permitted to say .   The  <tag key="phone"/>  went dead . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 " You hear me ?   Get off this  <tag key="phone"/>  ! 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Don't call back .   Keep this  <tag key="phone"/>  open ! 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Please , please don't " Suddenly that was all .   The  <tag key="phone"/>  died . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 " Hullo , hullo .   Don't go away ... .   Hullo ... . "   The  <tag key="phone"/>  was dead . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 She dialled the Fire Station .   The  <tag key="phone"/>  was still open there , but no one answered , not even the base radio officer . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 But by noon the voice which claimed to be Obolensky was back on the phone again , this time being referred to another Dominick executive , since his original contact there had gone out to lunch .   By the time the call was switched , the  <tag key="phone"/>  was dead . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The details came through around two in the afternoon .   The voice which claimed to be Mr. Szemzo seemed to be consulting at the other end of the  <tag key="phone"/>  with someone at the bank . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 " The quote was slightly over 550 per share .   There was more mumbling at the other end of the  <tag key="phone"/>  . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Several minutes went by as Miss Bailey held the phone .   Then the voice which claimed to be Szemzo came back on the  <tag key="phone"/>  . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 At this point Jaquith was carrying on a detailed operation for the Slayton interests .   He had a direct  <tag key="phone"/>  to the Model order room , set up for daily confirmations of purchases and sales . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Many types of business use rented circuits to connect home office with branches .   Certain offices at the United Nations complex in New York have direct  <tag key="phone"/>  going back to government offices in their home country . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 She told me how much she loved me , that she was counting on me to keep the hui going no matter what , and that she planned to leave a little something for you , my son , in her will .   Then suddenly , in the middle of a sentence , the  <tag key="phone"/>  went dead . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 One day I got a long-distance call from an affiliated station in Washington .   The man on the other end of the  <tag key="phone"/>  let's call him Barry Stump was the moderator of a popular panel show . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 " Right up against the door on his face , just like the first ... " Brian's hard young finger dialled rapidly and without error .   Somewhere distant at the other end of the  <tag key="phone"/>  a furious but controlled voice addressed him . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 " He misdialled in his haste , and swore , and started over again .   The sergeant's voice , only slightly furred with sleep , came over the  <tag key="phone"/>  . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 His face gave nothing away as he went to the telephone ; but certainly he went with alacrity . "   I know you told me to get in touch with the police , " said the creamy voice of Alix over the  <tag key="phone"/>  , without preamble , " but I needed to confirm something with you first . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 " Very odd , " agreed Alix .   There was one instant of curious and speculative silence on the  <tag key="phone"/>  . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Sergeant Moon had been dispatched home for a well-earned rest and a brief look at his more regular responsibilities , and it was Detective Sergeant Brice who answered the telephone and handed the receiver across the table . "   Here's ballistics on the  <tag key="phone"/>  , sir . " 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 That is one aspect of the Zeigarnik effect a proclivity to REMEMBER unfinished business , and to forget finished business .   You have experienced this when you have looked up a telephone number but found the  <tag key="phone"/>  busy when you first called it . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The whole goddamned system was breaking down .   He redialed the Hospital Maternity Floor on a direct  <tag key="phone"/>  busy too ! 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Here he was with two phone booths and a phone to each ear the guy probably thought he was a horse player or a bookie .   The answering service came through while the Hospital  <tag key="phone"/>  was still ringing busy . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 I was just going to try to reach you .   I have the husband of one of your patients on another  <tag key="phone"/>  . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 With his partner on vacation he would have to grab whoever was on the Maternity Floor and ask them to hang on until he got there .   A voice came on the Hospital  <tag key="phone"/>  , crisp and businesslike . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 " Hello , Weaver , " he said and then to put her on the defensive , " what's all the gabbing on the house phones ?   I couldn't get an open  <tag key="phone"/>  to you . " 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 " Fine , " Henderson said , aimiably . "   Can you get him on the  <tag key="phone"/>  ? 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 He heaved himself to his feet and sat down at the desk , making the long distance call to the Wisconsin hospital's emergency room .   The resident who was taking care of Mrs. Cochran was quickly on the  <tag key="phone"/>  . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Cheerful .   Here , I've got her on the  <tag key="phone"/>  for you now . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Keeping low by crawling across the kitchen floor , he reached up for the wall phone , placed it to his ear and heard nothing .   The  <tag key="phone"/>  was dead . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 I was sound asleep .   I certainly haven't been getting any calls and just now when I grabbed the phone to call you , the  <tag key="phone"/>  was dead . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 He hurried into the bedroom , putting the gun back in its secret hiding place and snatching up shoes , socks , shirt , and slacks .   Back in the kitchen he took the wall phone and dialed the emergency room at the Hospital on a direct  <tag key="phone"/>  . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 " I've got a call for you from Dr. Laden .   He's on the  <tag key="phone"/>  . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 There goes her goddamned placenta ! "   Have you still got her husband on the other  <tag key="phone"/>  ? " he asked . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 I may need you . "   Bill Sinclair came on the  <tag key="phone"/>  . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Ruth Sinclair's sister was calling .   When he tried to return the telephone call , the  <tag key="phone"/>  was busy and rather than waste any time he had driven right over to the house . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 He got up and headed out through the swinging doors .   His answering service was on the  <tag key="phone"/>  , holding a call from Bill Sinclair . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 " Oh , my , " I said in an apologetic voice , " I didn't get you out of bed , did I ? "   There was a moment of silence on the other end of the  <tag key="phone"/>  , and then with a wistful little sigh she replied , " No. But I wish you had . " 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Mrs. Barbara Agte , Allison's closest friend on the faculty , says , " No one felt responsibility for informing the parents of the dead students .   The Krauses tried to telephone Kent , but all  <tag key="phone"/>  were out . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Telex Computer Products , Tulsa , Okla .   For information : Circle 375 on Reader Card The model 185 terminal allows a user to process unjustified paper tape from a remote site using either dial-up or dedicated  <tag key="phone"/>  . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 A seemingly minor semantic dispute has given on- <tag key="phone"/>  dp users and suppliers a good chance of winning a major victory against Ma Bell .   If they win , the FCC will take jurisdiction over " information system access lines " that cross state borders . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The hope is that if FCC takes over , ISAL rates will be reduced or abolished .   The semantic dispute began last spring , when the commission asked Ma Bell why it had filed interstate tariffs to cover only a portion of Type 2006 foreign exchange service the portion represented by the foreign exchange  <tag key="phone"/>  . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Last September , AT&T was told to file tariffs with the commission covering " the complete interstate foreign exchange service . "   It will be some time before these rates are filed , says an FCC official , because the ruling affects literally thousands of foreign exchange  <tag key="phone"/>  . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The latest frontal assault concerns the IBM 2701/2/3 data adapter / telecommunications controller , which this vendor feels can be very nicely removed and replaced by the IDS-64/360 .   A MAC-16 mini is used to control from 1 to 256 synchronous or asynchronous  <tag key="phone"/>  . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Paul had brought the fig tree from north Florida and Honor always thought of the one Jesus cursed when she looked at it , because it remained barren in spite of Paul's careful tending .   When she had finished the dishes Honor called Ann Luise and knew at once from the glum tone at the other end of the  <tag key="phone"/>  that Ann Luise's parents had gone out and left her to baby-sit . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The noise damper on my air-conditioner has blown through the roof . " " Oh , hell , " a tired voice said at the other end of the  <tag key="phone"/>  . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 I telephoned the office and had them connect me with Bertha Cool . "   Donald , Bertha , " I said , when I heard her voice on the  <tag key="phone"/>  . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 " Just a second . "   Sellers came on the  <tag key="phone"/>  . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Now what are you going to do ? "   I picked up the phone , asked for an outside  <tag key="phone"/>  , dialed Homicide , and got Frank Sellers . " 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 I walked past him out of the office , on into my own office and called Sacramento .   I got Lucille Patton on the  <tag key="phone"/>  . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 As might happen in a real shoot , the countdown was interrupted several times because of problems , and it was soon determined that a key radar station on Wake Island in the Pacific Ocean was not operating properly .   A  <tag key="phone"/>  check was made and the malfunction traced to a switching center in Hawaii . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 We've put an automatic tracer on the phone which feeds our equipment .   If he calls , the number he called from is automatically locked in and fed to us and we don't have to go through all that two-phone jazz , keeping him on the  <tag key="phone"/>  . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 " Okay , do that , " I said .   Elsie picked up the telephone , punched the button for Bertha's  <tag key="phone"/>  , waited a moment , then said , " Mr. Lam just came in , Mrs. Cool . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 " The woman would simply ask to be connected with my office .   You'd talk with her and she would tell you what she wanted to see me about so then I'd get on the  <tag key="phone"/>  . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Leave them to me .   I'll talk long enough to keep the  <tag key="phone"/>  busy for the proper interval . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The switchboard operator said , " I'll connect you with his secretary . "   A moment later Elsie was on the  <tag key="phone"/>  . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Publicity was siren music to the ears of the stripper , and she quit pulling the zipper to listen .   When I had Colley on the  <tag key="phone"/>  , I said , " Okay , Colley , your idea worked . " 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Sex , seduction and sure-fire story stuff .   Get the hell off the  <tag key="phone"/>  so I can start calling the newspapers ! 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 I grinned and said , " Back to your crime clippings , Sister .   Bertha Cool will be in directly , and I've got to get an attorney on the  <tag key="phone"/>  and get Irene Addis to file a petition for the probate of the last will and testament of Herbert Jason Dowling . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Basically , this is because the noise is eliminated in the process of converting the signal into light pulses .   The result is that noise generated at the sending end isn't transmitted , and there is no "  <tag key="phone"/>  noise " as such . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Mark Computer Systems , Inc. , Plainview , N.Y. For information : Circle 309 on Reader Card CIP ( Communications Interface Processor ) is a turnkey system that enables multiplexing of low speed terminals directly into 360 computers without software modification .   Consisting of processor , ROM for multiplexing / demultiplexing and OS compatibility , 360 interface hardware , and  <tag key="phone"/>  adapters , CIP takes care of code conversion , network maintenance and monitoring .   The system supports up to 12 multiplexors over full duplex , voice grade lines ( 1200 , 2400 or 4800 baud ) and up to 176 low speed ( 600 baud ) lines .   The ceiling on the low speed lines is determined by the number of channels addressable by the 360 systems . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 He closed his eyes and tried to make his mind a blank , and he had almost dropped off to sleep when the telephone rang , sending a jolt through him like an electric charge .   He picked it up and said , " Hello , " and immediately wished he hadn't , because it was Selden Fulton at the other end of the  <tag key="phone"/>  . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Standish took the emended proof sheet and left , and Goodman picked up the phone and dialed his home number .   The  <tag key="phone"/>  was busy , so he hung up , and almost immediately his phone rang . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 And don't phone me .   If he finds the  <tag key="phone"/>  busy , he might decide Just promise me you won't talk to that agent , or the police , or anyone . " 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Thanks , anyway . "   The transatlantic  <tag key="phone"/>  died . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Takada seemed pleased .   Once , the voice at the other end of the  <tag key="phone"/>  was that of Pete Russo , who wanted to know if he could borrow a left-handed toggle switch . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 " Ross , you bastard , is this your idea of a joke ? "   On the other end of the  <tag key="phone"/>  , safe by half an island , Stuie Ross beamed . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 " Wrong telephone , " she said . "   That's the outside  <tag key="phone"/>  . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 " Household scandal .   That awful sanctimonious Gamboni , our butler , was on the  <tag key="phone"/>  , making a call from Paul's room , which he has no right to do anyway . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 There was a tiny hesitation , and then Emmy said , with curious emphasis , " I'm all right .   It's you that ... " There was a click , and the  <tag key="phone"/>  went dead . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 " When John came out of Natasha's room and ran into Paul and myself , " he went on , " he was embarrassed not to see Paul , who understood the situation perfectly , but to see me .   For my benefit , he made up a ridiculously lame excuse ; that he had been trying to telephone from Natasha's room , but that the  <tag key="phone"/>  was engaged . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 She asked him , " Was I very bad , darling ? "   Without answering her , he picked up the telephone and told the operator to try him on that  <tag key="phone"/>  if he could not be found elsewhere . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 I walked straight into the telephone booth and asked for Merlin's office number .   Would his  <tag key="phone"/>  be tapped ? 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 I gave my name as Caneton .   Merlin came on the  <tag key="phone"/>  , first as a distant voice saying apologetically : " ... m'excuse , Inspecteur . " 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 I thought " I took a couple of quick steps and picked up the phone . "   Qui est " But the  <tag key="phone"/>  was dead by now . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 " One of them's pretty . "   There was a crackle on the  <tag key="phone"/>  that might have been his aged chuckle . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The dialer sets off a series of impulses that race electronically toward any given number .   Once the phone is answered , the apparatus locks and an experienced technician , knowing where to look , can figure out where the call originates , but only so long as the caller remains on the  <tag key="phone"/>  . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 In the Mackle game room 669 miles south of Atlanta , Agent Lee Kusch impatiently picked up the telephone . "   Get off the  <tag key="phone"/>  , please , " he began , then stopped in mid-sentence . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 " And now something that is a part of all of our lives ... a message from the sponsor , " Kupcinet said to the camera .   He smiled until the red light went out , then immediately turned and picked up a telephone with " Kup " printed on the dial , his  <tag key="phone"/>  to the control booth . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 I was beginning to get the distinct impression that Brother Allen did not like me .   Then he bustled out of the box , jerked his head over his shoulder at the phone and said : " My business manager is on the  <tag key="phone"/>  . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 " That was the last time Bell ever talked on the phone .   He couldn't get his wife off the  <tag key="phone"/>  . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 I found out it was me .   Both Jeanette and I assumed he was there to test the  <tag key="phone"/>  or change the dial . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 I forgot about transcontinental phone calls .   My wife spent so much time calling her mother and sister that the State Department used to break in and ask her to get off the  <tag key="phone"/>  . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 " I'll tell you what , " she volunteered . "   We'll put a test on your  <tag key="phone"/>  , and I'll let you know what happens . " 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Put him on . "   At this point I hear all sorts of garbled commotion at the other end of the  <tag key="phone"/>  . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 " Yeah . "   There was another very long pause with dead air on the  <tag key="phone"/>  between them . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 I crumpled the note and tossed it on the bed , then snatched up the phone again . "   Get off the  <tag key="phone"/>  , Jim . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 I've got to call the airport . " " Get off the  <tag key="phone"/>  ? " he said . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 " I'll be by your place in a few minutes to pick it up .   Now get off the  <tag key="phone"/>  so I can see if I'm too late to hold the plane . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Don't even put that phone down .   Keep this  <tag key="phone"/>  open and stick that phone in General Cooper's face the instant he comes through that door . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Just a moment .   Bob Vincent of the FBI'S coming on the other  <tag key="phone"/>  . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 I want to talk directly with my crews . " " Can we keep an open  <tag key="phone"/>  with you ? " 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Only three chutes .   Someone forgot he was on open radio  <tag key="phone"/>  and swore viciously . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 He's got the word .   We're keeping an open  <tag key="phone"/>  to his office . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 " Yes . " " If you still have that open  <tag key="phone"/>  to the White House you'd better notify the President of the situation . " 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 " Sheridan tossed the telephone to Vincent and turned to his aide . "   Is that  <tag key="phone"/>  open to the Pentagon ? 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 He says that some of his best tips have come from the least likely sources ( " people with their offices in their hats , " he calls them ) and he never refuses to talk to strangers who visit his office or telephone him . "   You never know when Santa Claus might be on the other end of the  <tag key="phone"/>  , " Fuqua remarks . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The telephone rings .   Ah , it is one of our happy customers about to come on the  <tag key="phone"/>  , no doubt wanting to express his satisfaction with some handsome Masonite product that he has installed . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 He would still have liked to use Charles Russell but he didn't think Russell would change his mind .   So he picked up a phone whose  <tag key="phone"/>  was secure and he rang to what Russell had once commanded . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Most of the public telephones were already tied up by correspondents .   Somebody was fighting with the house phone , under the impression that it was an outside  <tag key="phone"/>  , and so Brad took the elevator up to his room and put in a call to Rhona's suite . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 He picked up the telephone . "   This is Eddie , " he said , when Foley came on the  <tag key="phone"/>  . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Earlier that same morning Mahler had been awakened by the inexorable telephone .   Landowski was on the  <tag key="phone"/>  . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 He turned away and asked for a telephone number .   Jane Gates was instantly on the  <tag key="phone"/>  . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 " Yes , Doctor ? "   The  <tag key="phone"/>  went silent . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Staff people passed the open door , waved good night , and went on .   Finally a cautious syrupy voice got on the  <tag key="phone"/>  . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 " Wait a minute , " O'Dwyer said .   Sarah got on the  <tag key="phone"/>  at once . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 I screamed , " My God , she's been burned , " and ran half-dressed and half-crazy to the phone downstairs .   Picking up the receiver , I heard two Farsi voices chatting and I screamed for them to get off the  <tag key="phone"/>  immediately . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 But now , when I needed them , the words were coming .   It seemed like hours before I could reach Bob on the crackling , scratchy  <tag key="phone"/>  . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 " For now , we'll concentrate on the system .   Some of the major data banks , like the ones held by Defense , may have five hundred or a thousand access  <tag key="phone"/>  . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Some of the major data banks , like the ones held by Defense , may have five hundred or a thousand access  <tag key="phone"/>  .   A year ago , Wilkens's congressional committee started to worry about unauthorized tapping into those access lines . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 " Pete , just tell me what it means . " " Jesus , this is an open  <tag key="phone"/>  . " " I know it's an open line . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 " I haven't got time . " " You're asking me on an open  <tag key="phone"/>  to define a hot new weapons system and break its code and you haven't got " 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 " Yes we did , and now somebody's got themselves a half-ton of ZV gas in binary aerosol cylinders , and we want to know who . " " You certainly ought to be concerned , " Graves said , " but this is an open  <tag key="phone"/>  . " 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 When he reached the station the one-and-only taxi was off on a long trip .   He tried to phone Fenella but the  <tag key="phone"/>  was out of order , so naturally he put a call through to us and Olive took it . 
</sentence>
</body>
