<body>
<sentence>
 These proteins bind tightly to specific molecules, offering the prospect of such applications as the diagnosis and treatment of cancer and the separation and purification of materials.  In addition, Mr. Frashier will push for development of a  <tag key="product"/>  of protein-based adhesive and coating products. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 William Gates, founder and chairman of Microsoft Corp., became the personal computer industry's first billion-dollar man yesterday.  The 31-year-old Harvard University dropout holds 11,018,955 shares, or about a 42% stake in Microsoft, which supplies, among other things, the internal program that controls the basic functions of International Business Machines Inc.'s PC  <tag key="product"/>  of personal computers and compatible machines. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Terms weren't disclosed, but industry sources said the price was about $2.5 million.  The sale includes the rights to Germaine Monteil in North and South America and in the Far East, as well as the worldwide rights to the Diane Von Furstenberg cosmetics and fragrance  <tag key="product"/>  and U.S. distribution rights to Lancaster beauty products. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 AMC executives have said they are frustrated about the timing of the bid, contending AMC was just about to turn the corner after a string of troubled years.  The company's Jeep sales are strong and AMC is just now introducing  <tag key="product"/>  of larger Renault cars that could finally give it a position in a broader segment of the auto market  but only if currently skeptical buyers start returning to AMC's showrooms. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Separately, James E. Edwards, an AT&T senior vice president who preceded Mr. Cassoni as head of the computer division, said he is leaving the company, effective Monday.  According to managers in the computer, or Data Systems, division, AT&T will announce new products that include an addition to its 3B minicomputer  <tag key="product"/> , software products to connect its machines to those of International Business Machines Corp., a laser printer, the latest version of the Unix V operating system software and some local area network products. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Several Data Systems executives have quit recently.  John Walsh, a vice president in charge of the 3B minicomputer  <tag key="product"/> , surprised colleagues in January when he left to join a small West Coast videoconferencing concern. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Faced with the innovative competition and an overall flat market since 1984, Nelson, the biggest U.S. religious publisher, lost market share and now is trying to recover ground.  Its "Precious Moments Bible," illustrated with a popular  <tag key="product"/>  of cherubic children's characters, has sold more than a million copies in about a year. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 RJR Nabisco Inc. said it expects to retain at least 95% ownership of its tobacco business if it decides to spin off the  <tag key="product"/>  in a master limited partnership. 
</sentence>
</body>
