<body>
<sentence>
 The company argued that its foreman needn't have told the worker not to move the plank to which his lifeline was tied because "that comes with common sense."  The commission noted, however, that Dellovade hadn't instructed its employees on how to secure their lifelines and didn't heed a federal inspector's earlier suggestion that the company install special safety  <tag key="cord"/>  inside the A-frame structure it was building. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The set, designed by Mr. Hall's longtime associate Eugene Lee, has the audience divided in half, facing a central playing area.  Off to one side  representing the "have-nots" of Louisiana  is a broken-down shack with a woodpile and a wash  <tag key="cord"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The new technology represents a considerable savings over conventional offshore production technology.  The foundation of the project, a "tension-leg well platform," will be a floating structure that is anchored to the seabed by steel mooring  <tag key="cord"/> , a design that requires far less steel than conventional platforms do. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 There is nothing easy about running a cruise boat in winter.  It takes boiling water to thaw the frozen  <tag key="cord"/>  at the Clinton's overnight berth so that the boat can be brought around to the passenger pier. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 But she could use a pair of spikes to help her navigate the icy deck.  Three times she tries to throw a dock  <tag key="cord"/>  to the pier. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "Give it a prolonged blow."  Proudly, I give the green  <tag key="cord"/>  a tug. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 To my horror, I realize I have pulled too hard.  Down comes the green  <tag key="cord"/>  as the great whistle blares forth, a shrill torrent of sound that won't stop. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "There are grown macho men who can skin game but who won't touch an eelpout," says Jeffrey Gunderson, a representative of the University of Minnesota's Sea Grant Extension program, which tries to promote underused fish.  "They'll cut their  <tag key="cord"/>  rather than bring it into the boat and unhook it." 
</sentence>
</body>
