<body>
<sentence>
 "She has a lot of information in her head about the acquiring company and there may be information there that may be useful to Supermarkets General in their defense.  I think she's walking a very thin  <tag key="division"/> ." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 One reason Optima could reshape the credit-card business is that American Express is the first high-profile card issuer with national marketing muscle to introduce a low-rate card.  Beyond that, its foray into revolving credit  in which the card holder must make only a minimal payment each month  further blurs the once-well-defined  <tag key="division"/>  between banks and other financial-service companies. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The Pentagon has strenuously resisted moves to upgrade the status of the units that deal with "low intensity conflict."  Members of the Joint Chiefs argued that Congress was trying to create a "fifth service" that would cut across traditional  <tag key="division"/>  of military authority. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 A Japanese Embassy spokesman in Washington said: "The supercomputer issue is a matter between two governments.  This (the Fujitsu proposal) is a matter between two companies, and a  <tag key="division"/>  should be drawn between the two." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Adds Ray Ablondi, a marketing research director at Ford Motor Co.: "We don't recognize something called a middle class.  We work across demographic, psycho-graphic and life-style  <tag key="division"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 In the past, people's shopping decisions were restricted partly by their limited familiarity with what was available.  But mass communication has since spread tastes and wants across social and economic  <tag key="division"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 But she refuses to buy imported New Zealand strawberries at $5 or $6 a box.  "That's where I draw the  <tag key="division"/> ," she says. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Today, it is more vital than ever.  In 1983, the act was entrenched in the new constitution, which established a tricameral parliament along racial  <tag key="division"/> , with separate chambers for whites, coloreds and Asians but none for blacks. 
</sentence>
</body>
