<body>
<sentence>
 For their part, some indigenous valley residents complain that their native soil has already become a veritable colony of the Midwest.  A Latino businessman saw something symbolic about recently spending 20 minutes in a cafeteria  <tag key="formation"/>  behind a group of Winter Texans, only to find that the Mexican entree was sold out by the time he was served. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Mr. Hodel, a former energy secretary, has been the most outspoken cabinet member on the threat to the U.S. from dependence on oil imports.  He has been warning that unless the U.S. changes its ways, it will face gasoline  <tag key="formation"/>  within two to five years. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Am I right or am I wrong?"  He is every bit as high on his scheme to unify this bifurcated city with a  <tag key="formation"/>  of gondolas suspended 320 feet above the Mississippi River. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 For most of nine hours we prowl the shoreline and places in the lake where weeds or fallen trees puncture the water's surface.  We cruise a  <tag key="formation"/>  of rundown boat sheds, and Cook slips a neat cast into each. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The Japanese, sociologists note, tend to follow the crowd.  They measure the quality of ice cream, for example, by the length of the  <tag key="formation"/>  in front of the shop. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 C-LD-R L-V-S V-NNA reads a sign in Caldor's book department.  The 1,000 or so people fighting for a place in  <tag key="formation"/>  have no trouble filling in the blanks. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "Nope," says Ms. White firmly.  She has only 90 minutes to sign books for the privileged 250 who queued up before Caldor's closed off the  <tag key="formation"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Ms. White kisses a little girl who brings her a rose.  "Give ME a kiss," yell some high school boys in the middle of the long and winding  <tag key="formation"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "I get her first," says his friend and classmate Kevin Marski.  Meanwhile, a woman offers Dan Kelly a $1 bribe to cut into the bulging  <tag key="formation"/>  and get Ms. White to autograph a book. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Mr. Kent believes the incident, which lasted two or three minutes, may have been connected to some sort of high-energy weapons experiment.  Two years ago, Mr. Nonella's buckaroo found four dead cattle lying in a straight  <tag key="formation"/>  one mile long, their chests and bellies pocked by some sort of lesions. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Some food shortages were reported.  Tourism slumped and  <tag key="formation"/>  for visas and passports formed as people sought to leave the South Pacific nation. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 So there's a new emphasis on trying to make such transactions just a bit more pleasant.  In New York and some other cities, for example, the service is experimenting with computers that can tell customers how long they'll wait in  <tag key="formation"/>  before being helped. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 But a consumer-price index wouldn't capture the full measure of inflation.  Experts note that rampant repressed inflation shows up in long  <tag key="formation"/>  at stores, poor quality of goods, new products that contain no improvements over cheaper earlier models and shrinking selections on store shelves. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Back in December, Harrison J. Goldin was at the front of a long  <tag key="formation"/>  of institutional investors itching to take a verbal swipe at General Motors Corp. and its chairman, Roger Smith. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Then amid profound silence he assured his audience, sedate and terrified, that while their personal safety was most dear to him he felt bound to confide that the plane's computer system was down, he had no idea how much fuel was left in the plane, and he was planning an unscheduled landing in Atlanta forthwith.  Such episodes are now the conversational loose change of airport bars and taxi  <tag key="formation"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 He's the leader-elect of West Germany's biggest party, the Social Democrats, and he's standing before a downtown hall full of workers in a city that's long been a SPD stronghold.  Down the street, monuments to the German welfare state  the health office, the employment office and the union  stand in a  <tag key="formation"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 It's actually a waste of time to debate the merits of each case, because under our current tort system, it really doesn't matter who was wrong or responsible for the injury.  In this society, if someone gets hurt, somebody, anybody must pay  and a  <tag key="formation"/>  of hungry trial lawyers will be waiting outside the hospital room to get a share of the action. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 But while Alysheba's win made him big stuff with the turf cognoscenti, it was, as usual, only a rumor to a large part of the throng of 130,000 that annually turns the old twin-spired track into the nation's biggest picnic grounds.  Behind me in the serpentine taxi  <tag key="formation"/>  outside the track after the races was a sunburned young couple lugging a huge cooler. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 But not nearly as many immigrants showed up the first day as had been expected.  The wait-and-see attitude among wary illegal immigrants was typified by Rudolfo Aspara Contreras, a native of Michoacan, Mexico, who spent the morning observing a  <tag key="formation"/>  of applicants outside a Houston processing center. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The distribution of applications, and the processing of the few turned in yesterday, appeared to go smoothly in most locations.  The INS had braced for a crush of applicants; in Houston, for instance, when long  <tag key="formation"/>  began forming a day early, officials passed out applications to about 1,000 before the law actually took effect. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 He frequents the flea markets.  He  <tag key="formation"/>  up daily outside state parts shops, fingering a list of scarce bits and pieces. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Should the FDA's new rules on experimental drugs go into effect without being compromised, they will be a watershed event in American medical science.  The U.S., which possesses the intellectual and financial resources to produce some of the world's most useful medical interventions, has for years labored under a system that made Americans stand at the end of the  <tag key="formation"/>  for these treatments. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 During his controller's tenure, which ended in 1983, he did several refresher stints behind restaurant counters.  "Some people on the cooking  <tag key="formation"/>  would tell me that my name sounds familiar; then they would realize it's on their paychecks," he says. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The 76-year-old physician's latest study, published in the October 1986 issue of the American Heart Journal, found that heart-attack victims cut their risk for a second attack in half by completing training he has devised.  The two-year program at the Meyer Friedman Institute in San Francisco includes patience-building drills such as driving in the slow lane of traffic or standing in long  <tag key="formation"/>  at banks. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 But why are Mr. Hodel and Secretary of Energy John Herrington trying to resurrect another "energy crisis"?  Mr. Hodel has warned of  <tag key="formation"/>  at the gas pumps in "two to five years." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The hospital director is taken away by the secret police.  The novel ends with a vivid taxi ride to the American Embassy in Tehran, surrounded by angry crowds who will overrun it and take hostages in just a few months, and with a final burst of imperialist frenzy on  <tag key="formation"/>  at the caviar shop in the Tehran airport minutes before the jets take off for Geneva, Los Angeles and New York. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The platform is crowded with soldiers buying tickets to Chimoio, the next stop on the corridor.  A boy with a basketball, which could use some air, also waits in  <tag key="formation"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 He aroused an angry backlash in Canada when he suggested that Canada is demanding strong U.S. acid-rain controls to improve its own energy exports to the U.S.  His wide-ranging comments on energy policies have irritated Energy Secretary John Herrington, who has publicly disagreed with Mr. Hodel's predictions of gasoline shortages and gas-station  <tag key="formation"/>  in two to five years. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "Things may never turn back like they were," says James T. Trado, the senior vice president and general manager of Mazda Motors of America's Eastern U.S. operations.  "We went several years without enough vehicles  customers were waiting in  <tag key="formation"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 It's just declasse," said Joel Silverman, a money manager attending the conference.  "I'd rather go out and pay retail for the stuff than wait in  <tag key="formation"/>  for a free album." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 He continues at this often thankless job, he says, because of the "injustices out there."  He recalls handing out food last Christmas to a long  <tag key="formation"/>  of laid-off workers: "It made me want to hold on to the jobs I have." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The jokes Russians tell among themselves are more pointed.  Marshall Goldman, co-director of Harvard's Russian Research Center, heard this one: Two Russians are standing in a long  <tag key="formation"/>  to buy vodka, grumbling about Gorbachev's restriction on liquor-store hours. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Laments over deteriorating standards of public courtesy are nearly as old as civilization, so perhaps those who feel besieged by rampant rudeness are simply responding to new forms of rudeness made possible by social and technological changes.  The advent of large, self-service supermarkets and department stores has made it possible for the inconsiderate to wheel full shopping carts into express checkout  <tag key="formation"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 IBM has said it has received tens of thousands of orders for 9370s, and analysts generally put the number at 40,000 to 45,000.  The analysts said, though, that many customers placed those orders just to get in  <tag key="formation"/>  for an early delivery and could still withdraw the orders without penalty if the 9370 doesn't seem to meet expectations. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 At Delta Kogyo Co.'s plant in Hiroshima, for example, two women operate three machines that turn out seat-reclining devices for Mazda.  Until October, the work took three people  one for each machine  but the seat maker found that by arranging the machines in a circle instead of a straight  <tag key="formation"/> , two workers were enough. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Bowler Earl Anthony was supposed to begin a practice session for the True Value Open at 10:30 a.m. at Landmark Lanes here on Tuesday, but the cluster of autograph seekers was so deep around him that he couldn't shake free until about 10:45.  As he bowled, new  <tag key="formation"/>  formed, and for the next hour he halted his exertions every 10 minutes or so to accommodate them. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Advocates of systematic investing say it's impossible to time the market and that most individual investors get killed trying.  "It's like trying to pick the fastest  <tag key="formation"/>  at the bank," says Bryan Mattes, assistant vice president of the Vanguard group of mutual funds in Valley Forge, Pa. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 And many expressed the hope for continued clear, mild weather.  Sunshine eased the pain of standing in long  <tag key="formation"/>  to enter some crowded stores along New York's Fifth Avenue. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 On Saturday, from morning until dusk, there were more than 100 people  <tag key="formation"/>  up to enter F.A.O. Schwarz's new toy store at 58th Street and Fifth.  Said one man who had been in line 20 minutes, "Put it this way: I wouldn't be here in a blizzard." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 But the company recognizes that improving service requires changes that can't be measured in numbers.  "Goal for '87 is turning glares into gleams," Eastern's employee newsletter says, showing photos of glowering customers in long  <tag key="formation"/>  at ticket counters. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The ruling involves the area that, although technical, is important in determining where lawsuits may be brought, and where companies and other defendants may be forced to defend themselves.  In a long  <tag key="formation"/>  of decisions, the Supreme Court has said there must be "minimum contacts" between a company and a state before the company can be sued in that state. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 That trend intensified when, starting in 1981, Nissan Motor Co. built its Smyrna, Tenn., plant, largely without union workers.  The Toyota plant was seen by the unions as "the second domino in what we feared would be a long  <tag key="formation"/>  of losses on major construction projects," Mr. Hammond says. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 She is from a political family: Her mother, a member of the school board in Manchester for 13 years, worked in the presidential campaigns of Wilbur Mills and Lyndon Johnson here, and Miss Reardon remembers licking envelopes for a Democratic gubernatorial candidate at age four.  "From the grubby, 'what-do-I-get-out-of-it?' view of politics, there's a long  <tag key="formation"/>  of people who are ahead of me in the Hart campaign," says Miss Reardon, who is interested in arms-control issues, troubled by the deficit and opposed to operation of the nuclear power plant at Seabrook. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The men stretch their feet and pay attention to correct arm positions.  The women hold their shoulders at a graceful angle, maintain a clean, unbroken  <tag key="formation"/>  and use their eyes as an adjunct to expressiveness of movement. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The company blamed expansion-related costs and a more competitive U.K. government bond market.  Just before that, a Canadian financial and health concern, Crownx Inc., bought a 14.9% stake in Mercantile House, joining a  <tag key="formation"/>  of foreigners swooping in on British financial houses. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 As the afternoon wore on, an air of crisis hung about the firm.  Television cameramen, chased out of the lobby of the firm's headquarters by security guards, hovered around the long  <tag key="formation"/>  of limousines parked outside Goldman's headquarters. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 But even the improved American prospects didn't turn this event into a gate attraction.  On Saturday, when the sun shone brightly and temperatures were in the 50s, the  <tag key="formation"/>  of cars trying to get into a car wash across the highway from the 400-meter oval at the Wisconsin State Fairgrounds was longer than that seeking admission to the races. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The most fundamental element of a program to deal with the present disequilibrium in the world economy is to remember that the pricing system works, and attempting to fix prices always produces mischief.  In the 1970s, the U.S. saw gasoline prices as the problem and thereby imposed on itself long  <tag key="formation"/>  at filling stations. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 While Catholic and Jewish agencies have had enough beds to accommodate children of those religions, Protestant agencies have not.  That has meant that non-Catholic and non-Jewish children have had to get at the end of the  <tag key="formation"/>  for acceptance into agencies, solely because of their religion. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Mr. Smyth and the three hunters continued their ridge-top hunt and within minutes were in the midst of more flushing prairie chickens.  The hunter at the left of the  <tag key="formation"/> , the one who had yet to bag a bird, was quick to score. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Organizers, who expected maybe 2,000 or 3,000 visitors, were stunned by what happened.  Nearly 30,000 people showed up, some waiting in  <tag key="formation"/>  for three hours. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "You'll have to look in your miracle section for an answer."  Miracle or not, St. Nicholas's icon is attracting such throngs that parishioners must put in long hours organizing the  <tag key="formation"/>  of tourists. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Some believers say the Madonna is spilling tears of joy.  But after waiting in  <tag key="formation"/>  for an hour to see the icon the other day, Alice Stavrides takes a dimmer view: "It means society had better shape up." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The committee's civilian anti-crime squads have stopped their nightly patrols.  Residents say they miss the committee's weekend soup  <tag key="formation"/> , which enriched their diets of rice, beans and bananas. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 To Salomon Brothers, which in October claimed another in a long  <tag key="formation"/>  of firsts staked out by Wall Street firms last year. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 From George Washington's time on up to 1932, you were able on New Year's Day to shake hands with the president of the United States.  You just got in  <tag key="formation"/> , no questions asked, and waited your turn. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 John W. Hunefeld," read a Jan. 2, 1936, news item, ". . . walked through the snow to the White House today to retain a hollow title.  Since 1926 Hunefeld had claimed the distinction of being first in  <tag key="formation"/>  for the traditional New Year's Day reception there. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Curmudgeons are horrified by Warren Burger's plans for celebrating the bicentennial of the Constitution.  He wants 50 million copies of the holy document printed on cereal boxes and sold in supermarket checkout  <tag key="formation"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 That's not to say that Mr. Wilson has abandoned his characteristic bag of stage tricks: He sends vultures, geese and herons flapping lazily through the air; he perches a giant singing owl on a tree limb; Robert E. Lee floats weightless in space; and Abraham Lincoln, tall as a house, wafts across the stage like some benign monster, then goes belly up.  The intricate lighting, by Beverly Emmons and Mr. Wilson, makes magic of a  <tag key="formation"/>  of singers in Christophe de Menil's billowing black robes, or of a narrow ladder silhouetted against a bare drop. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 To cut vodka consumption in the battle against alcoholism, a liter bottle  a treasured solace for many Russians  was more than doubled in price to 15 rubles, or about one-tenth of the average worker's monthly pay.  Production was curbed, and half the liquor stores were closed, increasing the average wait in  <tag key="formation"/>  to three hours. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 By midnight, the moon is an intense white spotlight beaming on no less than 50-odd ensembles and hundreds of onlookers.  Some partiers practically wait in  <tag key="formation"/>  for the prime spot: a gaping hole in the barn below the illuminated "Live Bluegrass Music" sign from which lucky ones sit and swing their legs. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 His deputy, William Ruckelshaus also refused, and Mr. Nixon fired him.  Then Mr. Nixon turned to the person who was third in  <tag key="formation"/> , Solicitor General Bork. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Two other stations just pump gas.  But standing in the midst of them, with its service bays full and cars waiting in  <tag key="formation"/> , is a Minit-Lube center. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 On weekdays, there's often no wait.  But on Stella Link Road during a typical Saturday rush recently, the  <tag key="formation"/>  to get into the Minit-Lube service bay was at least an hour long. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Its cost of $22 billion is more than four times Libya's estimated petroleum earnings in 1986.  The average Libyan must pay for this by standing longer in  <tag key="formation"/>  for scarce consumer goods. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "I'd hit balls nights, mornings, when it rained, when it snowed  I could never get enough golf," remembered Zembriski.  "On Friday nights after work, I used to sleep in the car at public courses so I could be the first in  <tag key="formation"/> , as soon as they opened the doors. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 His friends look at him in disbelief.  "If you really think that," Elias says, "why aren't you in  <tag key="formation"/>  applying for amnesty?" 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 They have high regard for some studies, while other research, even if it has enjoyed brief, intense popularity, gets debunked as unsupported or misleading (including Konrad Lorenz's "critical period").  For parents overwhelmed by the advice of so many researchers, their own pediatricians, and even the cashiers in checkout  <tag key="formation"/> , this sifting of the evidence is useful. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The authors find little empirical evidence to support a positive answer to these questions.  Parents, then, can nod and smile to the Ann Landerses of the checkout  <tag key="formation"/>  and escape with their confidence intact. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 He asserted that few other companies have the resources or the desire to take on JWT.  "If there are any other bidders, I think the  <tag key="formation"/>  at the door is very short," he said. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The industry's technological track record in other areas is spottier: The know-how is there, but the willingness or ability to use it lags far behind.  Travelers today still wait in long  <tag key="formation"/>  at baggage check-in or at the departure gate  procedures that can be automated. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 He says he slipped away from his protesting doctor, staggered into a government press conference and announced that he knew the man's identity and wanted to confirm that there was a reward.  Mr. Batuigas made his reputation in the 1970s by several times passing through police siege  <tag key="formation"/>  to negotiate the surrender of gunmen who were holding hostages. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 President Reagan is warning that if the U.S. Navy doesn't defend oil shipping in the Persian Gulf, Americans may soon be waiting in gasoline  <tag key="formation"/>  again. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The kids could then take their squid prints home to tack on their bedroom wall or stick on the refrigerator with a squid magnet purchased at the souvenir booth.  There was a long  <tag key="formation"/>  at the squid face-painting booth, from which small children emerged with large squid bodies painted on their foreheads and 10 squid legs extending down their cheeks. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 It is also an easy political target, and its image of inefficiency and corruption is a drain on the Sandinistas' lagging popular support.  Micoin is widely blamed for more problems than any 11,000-member ministry could ever possibly hope to fix  from the extra hours consumers must wait in  <tag key="formation"/>  for rationed food, to falling agricultural production caused by Micoin's stifling price controls, to the proliferation of a politically hostile class of small merchants operating outside the socialist-planned economy. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 At a Micoin neighborhood food store in Managua's Santa Ana Sur barrio, residents blame the ministry for distributing spoiled cooking oil that gives their children indigestion.  Once every 15 days barrio housewives leave bricks, empty paint cans and bottle caps outside the store at 9 a.m. to secure a place in  <tag key="formation"/>  for the 1:30 p.m. opening. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The Nikolai Quarter, for example, sports a set of new dining accommodations, but a recent hunt for a restaurant lunch there was as depressing as ever.   <tag key="formation"/>  spilled out into the street and around corners. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Mr. Trinkl said he recommended that the workers accept the offer after the company threatened to replace the strikers.  "We didn't have any other jobs for our people and I didn't want to put them on the welfare  <tag key="formation"/> ," he said. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The Bloomingdale's store at the mall, manager John Guerra said, posted a "double-digit increase" in December sales this year.  And stores throughout the mall were especially crowded the day after Christmas, with shoppers waiting in  <tag key="formation"/>  for the doors to open at 9 a.m. and then flocking to the bargains in the trim-a-tree section at Bloomingdale's to buy decorations for next Christmas. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 A cook at a local Italian restaurant, the 38-year-old Ms. Figueroa sat in the back seat of her nephew's car so that she would have her own window to roll down.  While Mr. Parra hopes his drive-up window will shorten the  <tag key="formation"/>  inside the center, he hasn't yet figured out what he'll do if it causes traffic jams. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "It wasn't obvious how the assembly process went," he recalls.  "I said to myself I don't know where the  <tag key="formation"/>  starts and ends. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "Canada is still trying to get some leverage from the U.S." said Mr. Waitzer, who warned foreign firms are losing interest in the Canadian market.  "You can only keep them waiting in  <tag key="formation"/>  for so long," he said. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "If I've ever attended an electric evening," the General Motors chairman said on a Detroit radio talk show last week, "that was it."  He went on: "They have a very nice custom there of a receiving  <tag key="formation"/> .  And as I went through the receiving line with my wife Barbara, why, we've gotten to know the President well enough that his aide doesn't have to introduce us to him, he recognized us. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "We told him he could bid with other developers," says Meyer Frucher, the president of the Battery Park City Authority.  "Sam said he didn't want to stand in a delicatessen  <tag key="formation"/> ." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Although Mr. Aganbegyan is believed to have Mr. Gorbachev's ear on issues of economic reform, he is only one of many officials working out details of what could be a very controversial and disruptive change in the Soviet economy.  An economic reformer, Mr. Aganbegyan believes that lower subsidies would make the economy more efficient and reduce the  <tag key="formation"/>  and shortages that Soviet consumers currently endure. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 In fact, she mocks herself for occasionally exploiting it.  "Like I'll walk into a deli and go right up to the head of a  <tag key="formation"/>  as though I don't know there's a line there and say, 'I'd like . . . ' Or I'll buy a ticket for a movie and go up to the security guard and say my dog really can't stand in that line, and he'll say, 'Well, come right in.'" 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The real bargains go to those tourists with the strong currency.  For example, just stand outside a Louis Vuitton shop in Hong Kong and watch middle-class Japanese alight from tourist buses and form  <tag key="formation"/>  on the sidewalk, says Mr. White. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Last year, Hutton took a $130 million charge against fourth-quarter earnings for liabilitiies related to municipal bonds it had improperly sold to customers a few years ago, and Merrill feared there could be more of such problems, these sources said.  Hutton, founded in 1904, thus becomes the latest in a long  <tag key="formation"/>  of major securities firms to seek a larger parent. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 But most major expansion efforts won't be completed for at least another year.  In the meantime, travelers must risk missing flights because they can't find spaces, or must wait in long  <tag key="formation"/>  to get through exit toll booths. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 In the meantime, travelers must risk missing flights because they can't find spaces, or must wait in long  <tag key="formation"/>  to get through exit toll booths.  At Newark, though, long lines can pay off; drivers are occasionally let through the booths without paying. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 In 1978, the year air travel was deregulated, the airlines carried 275 million passengers; this year, the total is expected to be more than 450 million.  This means crowded parking lots, long  <tag key="formation"/>  in restrooms, flight delays and tedious waits for baggage  which the FAA says are bound to worsen unless airport capacity is added. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 A chaos of cars and tents and trailers covers a field of trampled tall grass.  In late afternoon, bathing suits flap on clotheslines, and a  <tag key="formation"/>  has formed outside the showers. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 A hundred cowboys and cowgirls race their horses into the arena, the riders forward in their saddles urging the horses faster, circling the arena on the run before forming two parallel  <tag key="formation"/>  that stretch from one end of the space to the other. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 In recent months, conga-record breaking has become serious business, tainted with fierce rivalry and maybe even espionage, all for one sweet goal: a spot in the 1988 "Guinness Book of World Records."  The race heated up about three weeks ago, when 10,442 people shuffled into a  <tag key="formation"/>  at the Edmonton Heritage Festival in Alberta, Canada, aiming to break the previous record of 8,659, set in 1982 in Great Britain.  It took two hours to put the Canadian line together, for a conga that lasted nine minutes. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 They will use their new-found conga skills to guide a horde of challengers tomorrow on the Royal Gorge Bridge in southern Colorado.  Lorraine Payne, who helped arrange the  <tag key="formation"/>  in Edmonton, claims she saw the men looking for potential snags and taking photographs at her event. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Ben Hart, one of the two men in question, maintains that he started planning the Royal Gorge event in early March, well before the Canadian attempt: "It was strictly coincidental.  We had no idea about the Edmonton  <tag key="formation"/>  until it happened." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 To break the record, the dancers will have to follow certain rules, says David Hoy, managing director of the record book's editorial offices in Middlesex, England.  At least 10,443 people will have to actually dance  hands on hips to a syncopated Latin rhythm  and the  <tag key="formation"/>  will have to remain unbroken. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "I'm making $5.50 an hour (in Houston); in Mexico I was making 7,000 pesos (about $5) a week."  Yesterday he took his place in  <tag key="formation"/>  at midnight. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Like most Buenos Aires ministries, it is suffused with stale cigarette smoke.  The occupants appear to be mainly bored but loquacious hangers-on, who must wait in  <tag key="formation"/>  20 minutes for the elevator to the top floor. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 But good intentions sometimes aren't good enough.  One recent day, as a jostling crowd of Cubans waited in  <tag key="formation"/>  for more than an hour to get their monthly allowances of beans, rice and other foodstuffs, one of Mr. Leiva's freezers was out of order. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Those numbers should improve in 1987 because banks have pledged to lend more than $9 billion to Mexico, Argentina and Nigeria this year.  But there is a long  <tag key="formation"/>  of debtor countries looking for more loans. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Why not talk your way out of your woes?  If that sounds appealing, get in  <tag key="formation"/> , because sports psychoanalysis is booming among psychologists, psychiatrists and others aiming to tap the lucrative health-and-fitness craze. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 If the models now under scrutiny are found to be defective, GM will recall and repair them, he said.  The consumer group said one of the worst accidents involving the cars occurred in Cincinnati on March 3 when, it said, a 1986 Oldsmobile Delta 88 suddenly accelerated and ran into a  <tag key="formation"/>  of customers standing outside a restaurant. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Commercial bank traders with firsthand knowledge of the intervention estimated that the Fed sold $100 million through several banks in early New York trading, shortly after the Bundesbank sold a like amount in the open market in Frankfurt.  The central banks formed a skirmish  <tag key="formation"/>  for the dollar at 1.8840 marks, where they sold the currency, knowledgeable traders said. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 In addition, Wolfgang R. Schmitt, president of Rubbermaid's Home Products division, was named executive vice president of the company, placing him in  <tag key="formation"/>  to succeed Mr. Williams in the No. 2 spot.  In making the announcement, Mr. Gault said, "We have now provided a clear line of succession" when he retires in 1991 as chairman and chief executive. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "How does the '60s song go about the age of Aquarius?  We had all the planets in  <tag key="formation"/> ," Mr. Channell said. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The new law could, of course, provide work for the homeless, who are the ones most skilled at this task.  But how long will the  <tag key="formation"/>  be at the Conservation Center? 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 I can do a lot of things.  You won't see me at the food stamp  <tag key="formation"/>  . . . and we're not going to run a telethon and ask for contributions." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 These powers include the withholding of material formally requested by the Congress.  George Washington was the first of a long  <tag key="formation"/>  of presidents to insist on this prerogative of the office. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "The problem with Continental service is it's so unpredictable," says Hal Salfen, an industry consultant.  "I had absolutely splendid, perfect service flying Continental to Guam, but when I got to Los Angeles, it was back to long  <tag key="formation"/>  and rude counter help." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 I wonder if those supporting the bill ever took a sick child and two well ones to the doctor for a routine illness such as an ear infection or strep throat.  Did they then face another 20-plus minutes at the drugstore with the same three whiny children, one in pain and the other two frustrated while an overworked pharmacist attempted to serve a long  <tag key="formation"/>  of customers? 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 What customers do is get in the queue.  Each day,  <tag key="formation"/>  of them snake across the lobbies of Telmex's branch offices in the capital to report broken telephones. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 But the  <tag key="formation"/>  move slowly; the dispatcher typically takes 40 minutes to answer.  "This has happened to me four or five times since February," says television repairman Jorge Recio Garcia, waiting in line to report his broken telephone. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Still another says a car crashed in his neighborhood two weeks ago and knocked out phone service; no one has come to restore it.  "This is horrible  very ugly," says the branch manager, whose office looks out over the  <tag key="formation"/>  of angry customers. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Company headquarters stands tall over central Mexico City in a vaguely M-shaped tower.  There are no  <tag key="formation"/>  of angry customers, no cowed managers, no bossy subordinates. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "The (baseball) commissioner's job is taken," sniffs Peter V. Ueberroth, who holds the post.  "Besides, he'd have to get in  <tag key="formation"/>  behind Bryant Gumbel," the television newscaster, who said in a recent interview that he wants the job. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The sign in the airport cafeteria reads: "It is not rude to move ahead of someone if there is a space in the  <tag key="formation"/> ." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 I love this sign.  I love it because it so blithely challenges one of the basic tenets I was raised by  that it is rude to jump ahead of someone in  <tag key="formation"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 But darn it, I just don't want to appear rude."  Every time I stand in that  <tag key="formation"/>  I expect to see some burly construction worker push in front of an elderly woman. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 He seems to believe that South Vietnam fell, in part, because U.S. commanders unwisely restrained South Vietnamese military commanders.  And, as much as some of his other criticisms of the West ring true (people get more excited about solo adventurers sailing the seas in small boats than tens of thousands of Vietnamese boat people cruelly adrift), they aren't original in thought or expression, but echo the long  <tag key="formation"/>  of commentators who see the West imperiled by its love of comfort and lack of intellect. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Some foreign countries and industries have hired Washington lobbyists and law firms to help and have pressed U.S. companies doing business with them to pitch in as well.  Senate Finance Committee Chairman Lloyd Bentsen (D., Texas), who co-sponsored the trade bill with Sen. John Danforth (R., Mo.), says: "There's a long  <tag key="formation"/>  of foreign representatives waiting to see me. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 But Southland could win over customers like Mrs. Dallas, the Denver legal secretary, who rents movies for her sons and buys sandwiches at the 7-Eleven when they're on special.  "If they could prove their milk was cheap enough, then I would go to the convenience store to avoid the  <tag key="formation"/>  at the grocery store," she says. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "The real financial and social problems of the country are deeply rooted," Thornton Management Ltd., a British fund-management group, says.  In addition, with the economy and stock market recovering, the government is speeding approval of the long  <tag key="formation"/>  of companies wanting to issue shares. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 In Southern California, however, where developers have been especially active, legislators and community groups complain that the mini-malls have led to a host of problems that can't be ignored any longer.  Opponents complain that the mini-malls' design  typically a collection of a dozen or so stores grouped in a  <tag key="formation"/>  or a U-shape or L-shape behind a parking lot that fronts the street  makes them uninviting to pedestrians. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 But it also said JAL and government transport authorities failed to detect the flaws during several routine inspections.  The report said the Boeing work crew inserted a single  <tag key="formation"/>  of rivets to the bulkhead when repairing a broken tail section, instead of a double line as required. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "It started to aggravate our agents and inconvenience our passengers," says Marc Wallace, a United vice president.  United's employees began suggesting to the Continental passengers that they defect to United's shorter  <tag key="formation"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Dinner-table conversation was recorded by the KGB, which made Soviet citizens fearful of ideological misstatements, which made their dinner-table conversation boring.  But not as boring as shopping in Soviet grocery stores, waiting in long  <tag key="formation"/> , being abused by surly state employees, and finding almost nothing for sale. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Battling the crowds on New York's Fifth Avenue was no less challenging.  There were long  <tag key="formation"/>  of shoppers waiting to enter F.A.O. Schwarz, a children's toy store, and the fashionable Trump Tower. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 No heat: From bureaucrats and hotel clerks to students, everyone sits around all day long in overcoats from October through April.  No food: Everything from milk to rice is rationed, but long  <tag key="formation"/>  and limited supplies mean people often wind up with only a ration ticket on the dinner table  some people could show you whole crocks filled with expired coupons. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Several nations don't count oil as produced until it is sold.  Thus, Kuwait can insist that it is within its production quota even though  <tag key="formation"/>  of loaded tankers sailing through the Persian Gulf would suggest otherwise. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 But Mr. Walser does not leave it at that.  "Breakers" does not end up as another in a long  <tag key="formation"/>  of stories about rigid Germans who cut loose and lose their dignity in a relaxed, sunny climate. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "If we do see consumers start to make that connection  connecting the problems on Wall Street to unemployment that affects them  then we'll see much more impact on sales," Mr. Curtin said.  "With the oil embargo, from day one it was immediately clear to consumers what it meant to them personally: longer  <tag key="formation"/> , higher prices. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Fred muttered something aloud about how, after all, his student didn't really know how to drive, and you never knew when she might step on the gas pedal.  The  <tag key="formation"/>  parted, and Fred, wielding his lollipop stick, motioned for me to move on. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Magnet extended banking hours at the branches on Friday and Saturday.  After Mr. Wall's statement was released and distributed by Magnet officials, some of the  <tag key="formation"/>  thinned at the branches. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "Home shopping is quick, clean (and) painless," says the Roper study.  "No long  <tag key="formation"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 And many of the responses came right out of the music.  For instance, the galloping marimba  <tag key="formation"/>  did suggest the horse running alongside a train described by Noah from New York. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The Ghost Town at Knott's Berry Farm theme park is usually a pretty cheery place, bustling with cowboys staging shootouts on the storefront boardwalks, folks buying souvenirs and snacks from calico-clad shopkeepers, and  <tag key="formation"/>  streaming onto the park's Log Ride. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "The New York Stock Exchange did not blow up.  There were no  <tag key="formation"/>  at banks." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Right now you may be asking yourself: "Why not me?  My boss is a jerk, I'm sick of long  <tag key="formation"/>  at the bank during lunch and only now, decades after kindergarten, have I come to fully understand the importance of a nice nap right after lunch." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 After the swim meet my wife and I watched as my daughter danced at a team get-together.  It made me remember parish-house dances when we boys would wait in  <tag key="formation"/>  to dance slow numbers with a prematurely endowed girl named Anne.  I checked the dance floor for my daughter  no lines were forming, yet. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 They put up with appalling and often dangerous conditions because other jobs are hard to come by and because the pay, while low by U.S. standards, goes a long way back home.  Danilo Pineda, a Filipino ship's cook, says that in Manila the  <tag key="formation"/>  of seafarers at manning agencies are growing longer. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 It is obvious to anyone that the general quality of consumer products of all kinds is poor, not only by comparison with those available in the West but even with the Eastern European imports that are for sale in the Soviet Union.  And the long  <tag key="formation"/>  to buy quality food or clothing when they happen to be available demonstrate the malfunctioning of the Soviet price system and of the state's inability to produce what consumers want. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 A tall, blond woman pushing a baby girl in a Kanga-Roll stroller conceded that her timing was unusual.  "But we really know what commitment is about and we're ready to make it," she said, waiting her turn in  <tag key="formation"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Great America, a Santa Clara, Calif., amusement park, brags about its thrilling roller coaster.  But if you want to do something really wild, try cutting in  <tag key="formation"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Santa Clara won't comment on the lawsuit  but it will defend its law, adopted in 1986 after the city bought the amusement park.  The law makes  <tag key="formation"/>  cutting, shoving and other forms of rowdiness a crime punishable by a $1,000 fine or six months in jail. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "Well, we're not talking about the Hell's Angels here," fumes Mr. Ince, who notes that his clients include an engineer and a banker.  In the lawsuit, Mr. Ince says his clients hadn't actually cut into  <tag key="formation"/>  but had stepped out of line for a moment  with the permission of those around them. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 In another, two clients had soaked their clothes on a previous Great America water ride.  "The  <tag key="formation"/>  they were in was in shade, so they stood off to the side in the sun to dry their clothes," says Mr. Ince.  When they tried to reclaim their place in line, however, security guards nabbed them and, with little explanation, turned them over to city police who drove them in a paddy wagon for booking at the city jail, the suit alleges. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 She will say, however, that with two million people visiting the park annually, the number of  <tag key="formation"/> -cutting arrests is negligible.  "Besides," she says, "you shouldn't leave the line to get a hot dog." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 With fewer than 70 shopping days till Christmas, millions of Americans are avoiding long  <tag key="formation"/> , bad weather and crowded parking lots by doing some or all of their Christmas shopping by mail. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 He fired those he didn't like, with only the briefest of explanations, if any.  Being called to his office "was like being summoned to see God," said Lee A. Iacocca, now Chrysler Corp. chairman and perhaps the most famous of a  <tag key="formation"/>  of former Ford presidents first beknighted and later beheaded by Mr. Ford. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Should players and owners resolve their gripes in the next day or two, everybody will be having a good laugh about all this at next week's tailgate parties in stadium parking lots across the country. (The two sides met for 90 minutes yesterday and are scheduled to meet again today.)  But if the strike drags on anywhere near the 57 days of the 1982 strike, a lot of people along New York's Madison Avenue and "Broadcast Row," homes to the major advertisers and television networks, will be standing on  <tag key="formation"/>  to renegotiate contracts worth hundreds of millions of dollars. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Rep. Frank Annunzio, a rough-hewn Chicago machine pol who is the third-ranking committee member, is in frail health and isn't likely to seek the chairmanship.  Others down the seniority  <tag key="formation"/>  eyeing the post include Del. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 But then, he went home to Massachusetts, devoting much of his time to routine state house duties instead of focusing on the campaign.  Mr. Bush wasted no time in opening an attack on the governor for being just another in a long  <tag key="formation"/>  of liberal Democratic politicians out of touch with the American mainstream. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Taiwan will export three million personal computers this year, up 50% from 1987.  Long  <tag key="formation"/>  form outside discos that charge $20 a head, and $5 a beer, to dance to the beat of imported bands. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "The thing that hit hardest was the energy crisis," Mr. Atkins said.  If someone "had to wait in  <tag key="formation"/>  for gas for his car, he couldn't justify" waiting for gas for a snowmobile. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Monday, Nov. 7, 7-7:30 p.m. EST, on HBO (repeated Nov. 11, 16, 20, 26 and 28): "Madeline."  Don't miss this musical version of the famous children's book that begins: "In an old house in Paris that was covered in vines/lived twelve little girls in two straight  <tag key="formation"/> ." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 But it had reduced alcoholism hardly at all while spawning extensive moonshining and black-marketeering.  It resulted in sugar hoarding for private production and long  <tag key="formation"/>  for limited quantities of vodka. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 At Tampa Bay in the NFL, where he signed a six-year, $5.25 million contract, life was financially more secure, but professionally precarious.  Flung into action against the big-time pros behind a weak  <tag key="formation"/> , Young threw almost twice as many interceptions as touchdowns, and fled with the ball more often than he ran it. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 And they reflect the growing turmoil in the U.S. bond trading industry, weakened by anemic profits and intense foreign competition.  The departure of the three executives marks yet another outbreak in a long  <tag key="formation"/>  of defections and dismissals that have roiled the giant securities firm over the past year. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "Can you imagine thousands of kids walking into these offices, getting urine samples, and presenting them to state officials to be tested?  The  <tag key="formation"/>  would be miles long." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 There are more characters in the novel than in the film, and consequently more seductions and betrayals.  I could criticize the film for cutting a couple of these characters, as well as for hammering the novel's whirling, vertiginous shape into a straight chronological  <tag key="formation"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 At the sprawling 207th Street repair shop in upper Manhattan, this shift promised new discipline for employees used to meeting minimum work quotas and then having a little time to themselves.  Workers suddenly faced dismissal for insubordination or inebriation, or suspension for lesser infractions like spending long periods in the coffee  <tag key="formation"/>  or the bathroom. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 After the fervor of a campaign in which the regime portrayed the poll as a choice between itself and Marxist chaos, there was a hushed solemnity and respect during the Oct. 5 voting.  Not a voice was raised, not a badge worn nor banner carried, as people waited in long  <tag key="formation"/>  to put a pencil mark on a piece of paper. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "I'd say the $1 million to $15 million market has been the most competitive arena of commercial lending in Florida for the last few years," says William H. Allen Jr., chairman of Miami-based Atico Financial Corp. and a former NCNB executive in Florida.  First Union Corp., the other Charlotte banking giant, dates its own "sales culture" back to 1984, when it began making a science of shortening teller  <tag key="formation"/> , cross-selling products and spot-checking employee courtesy. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 They caused traffic jams in the parking lot.  They formed checkout  <tag key="formation"/>  that wound all the way back to the meat department. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 So even though Burger King can boast that its Whopper hamburger beats McDonald's Big Mac in taste tests, it has been losing sales because it can't promise its customers an identical experience from one Burger King to the next.  While one restaurant may sparkle, another may have long  <tag key="formation"/> , pot holes in the parking lot and filthy tables. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 These days, Lishen Toy Factory can hardly keep up with demand.  Sales soared this summer, when long  <tag key="formation"/>  of buyers formed outside Shanghai's No. 1 Department Store. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Military patrols combed the streets of the capital, but there was no sign of disorder after a night of uncertainty Tuesday that was punctuated by power cuts and occasional explosions.  People waited patiently in long  <tag key="formation"/>  to cast their ballots. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Gen. Pinochet has expressed "particular faith in the women of Chile."  Final results had been expected around midnight, but the long  <tag key="formation"/>  delayed the vote count. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "We feel comfortable that the next time they (United) go to kick tires and look for airplanes to buy, we have a good, fair shot with them," an Airbus spokesman said.  The A-320 transaction by United would have given Pan Am badly needed cash in return for giving up its spot in  <tag key="formation"/>  for the new planes. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 But by February, when Geraghty & Miller Inc. was brought public by Alex.  Brown along with Robertson, it had 125 institutions waiting in  <tag key="formation"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Critics say that in winning preferential treatment, the DeBartolo organization played all the right political notes  including hiring a former governor's chief of staff to be track director of operations and granting a $165,000 food service contract to a company owned by the state speaker of the House.  Remington is off to a rousing start despite some opening-day snafus, which included slow  <tag key="formation"/>  at betting windows that prevented a number of people from wagering. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 That the trip was a success is due to the Georgians themselves, a smiling dark-haired people who even in the darkest Brezhnev days impressed the Beatles rock group enough to make them write in their song "Back in the U.S.S.R." the words "Georgia's always on my mind."  Long before perestroika the healthy Georgian black market provided its citizens with a standard of living here far different from Leningrad and Moscow, the cities of food  <tag key="formation"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 As for new home sales, the outlook continues weak, as evidenced by the 3.3% drop in August housing starts out last week.  Mr. Resler added in jest that another "indicator" he likes to watch is "the hostility level in grocery checkout  <tag key="formation"/> ." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 They must be Ku Klux Klanners or something.  But as Mr. Newman suggests, about all that distinguishes Yonkers from other cities is its bad luck to be first in  <tag key="formation"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Wind-whipped fires raced through the Sierra Nevada foothills, charring nearly 30,000 acres, destroying about a dozen homes and prompting about 4,500 people to evacuate.  In Wyoming, firefighters took advantage of damp weather to strengthen  <tag key="formation"/>  around blazes that have burned nearly one million acres in Yellowstone National Park. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "The whole town has come to aid, but even that is insufficient," he says.  A long  <tag key="formation"/> , mostly of women carrying small children, stretches outside the medical tent. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The sellers of radishes and cucumbers are bored.  So are the frozen fish merchants, but the poultry dealers are busy, watched vacantly by customers in  <tag key="formation"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The closing of the Cameron plant dashed farmers' hopes of expanding markets for their promising new crop.  With the plant vanished the jobs of 58 residents and the  <tag key="formation"/>  of trucks that snaked into town during the annual harvest. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Here at the Festspielhaus, the world's Wagner shrine, they have found the antidote for the master's long operas  long intermissions and long buffets.  In a ritual I never grow tired of seeing, the blond young man lifts the cover off the tureen and the mere glimpse of those fat, white, green-flecked weisswurst ready to bust their skins revives everybody on  <tag key="formation"/>  like the unveiling of the Holy Grail in the master's "Parsifal." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Judge Pollack, who is known as a tough, brilliant jurist, agreed Wednesday to do so.  The altercation, witnessed by a long  <tag key="formation"/>  of attorneys waiting to file court pleadings, lasted a minute or so, says a rather baffled Mr. Pomarico. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 African bees generally dominate in mating, but the scientists hope to give a numerical edge to the calmer European honeybees, the type widely used throughout North America for honey production and crop pollination.  Farther north, researchers are setting hundreds of traps along three  <tag key="formation"/> : a 100-mile stretch from the coastal town of La Pesca to Ciudad Victoria in Mexico; a 125-mile line from Tampico to Ocampo, also in Mexico; and a 100-mile section of the Rio Grande, roughly from Brownsville, Texas, to Rio Grande City. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "Out on Long Island, there are people who are hooked on drive-throughs.  They'd rather be in a  <tag key="formation"/>  of 10 to 15 cars than park and get out," said a spokesman for Chemical Bank, a unit of Chemical Banking Corp. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 If you want to wait in  <tag key="formation"/>  to climb the Statue of Liberty or the Washington Monument, go ahead. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 In Shanghai, China's biggest metropolis, consumers are withdrawing huge sums from savings deposits to purchase goods in anticipation of price increases.  Long  <tag key="formation"/>  are forming at many savings banks, according to China Daily, which estimates that $27 million has been withdrawn in the past two weeks. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Solutions from France weren't much help.  Canadians use the North American "qwerty" keyboard, named for the sequence of keys on the top  <tag key="formation"/>  of letters. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Elsewhere, earthiness is catching on.  A Brazilian beer commercial shows men standing at a  <tag key="formation"/>  of urinals singing the beer's theme song. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Then the women are banished to the sidelines, and the men begin to display their strength.  At one point, six of them form a tower of bodies, while a  <tag key="formation"/>  of smiling women, seemingly unaware of anything but the music impelling them, undulates slowly around the group. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 A substantial contribution to the increased production over the next two years is supposed to be made by the Baltic states of Latvia and Estonia, which have long turned out better-quality goods than factories elsewhere in the Soviet Union.  As they wait in  <tag key="formation"/>  at stores, many Soviets grumble that the variety and quality of products on sale actually have worsened since the days of the now-discredited leader Leonid Brezhnev. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Mr. Levenson has boosted his to about 2.5%, producing TV commercials based on the 1960s Lovin' Spoonful song, "Did You Ever Have to Make Up Your Mind."  He is remodeling stores to speed up the serving  <tag key="formation"/>  by splitting off the slow-moving dessert and beverage sections from the entree and vegetable line. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Mr. Questrom's resignation followed that announcement in May.  Founded in 1907 by Henry C. Marcus and family members, Neiman Marcus became known for its pricey merchandise, extravagant customers and  <tag key="formation"/>  of waiting limousines that had ferried some patrons from the airport. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 One reason is that Disneyland encourages photo-taking by lending cameras without charge, and setting up designated photo sites.  People tend to take pictures of  and thus remember  only pleasant scenes like the cute shot with Mickey Mouse, and not the long  <tag key="formation"/>  at the ladies' room. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 But their opinion is clearly not shared by large numbers of the Soviet public.  Since Mr. Glazunov's latest exhibition opened in Moscow this summer, thousands have been flocking to the Palace of Youth, waiting in  <tag key="formation"/>  for hours to get in. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 People stood in long  <tag key="formation"/>  outside the few operating bakeries and food stores in the Sudanese capital yesterday, after flooding left about 1.5 million homeless and at least 11 dead. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "Over here is the gay party  <tag key="formation"/> ," Steve Craig, Megaquest's office manager in New York, says, pointing to one bank of monitors.  "This is the actress and model line in here." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Living conditions are cramped and spartan, and temperatures usually top 100 degrees.  Two chow  <tag key="formation"/> , "one spicy and one regular," meet the needs of both the military and about 50 Indian and Filipino civilian workers living aboard, he said. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Several speakers at the recent Communist Party conference warned that ordinary citizens would be reluctant to back the rest of Mr. Gorbachev's reform program unless they could see a clear improvement in their living standards and the quantity of goods available in stores.  Many basic foodstuffs such as meat, flour and sugar are rationed in parts of the Soviet Union, and everywhere people have to stand in long  <tag key="formation"/>  for them. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Yet another casualty may be overall spending in restaurants, already slowing from the 8% annual gains posted in the mid-1980s.  Consultants say many people who have traded up from fast-food chains to sit-down eateries will be getting back in the hamburger  <tag key="formation"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The Polish Germans usually can say no more than "ja" or "nein," but may have advanced degrees as teachers or engineers.  Both groups now face several days of waiting in  <tag key="formation"/> , with stops at the Red Cross, at social workers  and at a cashier who hands out $108 in pocket money to each arrival. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The lobby is elaborately decorated, but noisy.  Large groups of guests wait in  <tag key="formation"/>  for elevators and check-out service. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "Or a medium?"  Arkansas Gov. Bill Clinton, the latest in a  <tag key="formation"/>  of white Southerners given prime spots at the convention, delivered the sole nominating speech for Mr. Dukakis, and the governor's first campaign swing with Sen. Bentsen tomorrow is designed to re-emphasize his commitment to challenge the GOP in every region of the nation. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 By last April, when Mr. Clausen took his first week off, his fast pace had scared off his first administrative assistant and run others ragged.  "The man has an iron will," says an official once stranded with him in a three-hour reception  <tag key="formation"/>  at a convention  without a bathroom break. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Students of economics learn that this is simply not true.  Russian consumers now wait in  <tag key="formation"/>  to buy lemons at a low price. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Carriers were allowed to keep flying the first 291 aircraft off the production  <tag key="formation"/> , although they received Federal Aviation Administration orders to inspect regularly for corrosion in the cold-bonded joints.  One scenario investigators are considering in the Aloha case is that corrosion-related fatigue may have led to "multisite damage" cracks running along the horizontal line of rivets in a metal splice. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 In Moscow, Party banners aside, the prevalent ads are the ones stuck to lampposts; each has a fringe of phone numbers to tear off and call for puppies or guitar lessons.  The queue is still the most effective Soviet ad; a Russian will join a long  <tag key="formation"/>  without a clue as to what is for sale at the other end. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 And several hundred delegates actually voting against conference resolutions.  That was heady stuff, and here in Moscow, Soviet citizens were talking about it in parks, while waiting in  <tag key="formation"/>  at stores and to Western correspondents. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 He filled his car and six big canisters, enduring hostile comments from fellow customers.  At noon, a truck delivered more gas, reassuring those at the end of the 120-car  <tag key="formation"/>  monitored by police to prevent double parking. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 I see the crowd and I don't want to stand in  <tag key="formation"/> ," said Krzystof Tom.  He ultimately took a place in line. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Twin Valu stores, for example, will cover 180,000 square feet  three times the size of the typical cavernous Cub store.  Each store will have 51 checkout  <tag key="formation"/> , require 600 employees and, company sources say, is expected to gross well over $1 million a week. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Depending on wind direction, that can eliminate the use of one of three arrival runways.  Still, some industry executives and observers wonder whether any improvement in delays would even be noticed, what with the litany of complaints about lost luggage, long  <tag key="formation"/>  and crowded planes. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Saatchi & Saatchi also hit a high note with an ad created for Britain's Conservative Party in 1978.  The ad featured a picture of a long  <tag key="formation"/>  of unemployed. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Meantime, hungry passengers have to order from mobile carts scattered around the terminal.  Continental insists that's sufficient, but the  <tag key="formation"/>  to get to the carts are often long  and there are few places to sit and eat. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 It is the parent company of Audi of America Inc., which imports Audi cars to the U.S.  Last week, a Westchester County, N.Y., jury said Audi was solely responsible for a 1985 accident in which an Audi 5000 car hit a car in a bank teller  <tag key="formation"/> , which hit Ms. Ruston's car. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Russians inching toward the checkout counter marvel at the genius of one-stop shopping.  "You just pick things out yourself," says a woman in the express  <tag key="formation"/>  with a block of goat cheese. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 SKATES: Alpha Sports Inc., St. Paul, Minn., agreed to grant Mitsubishi Corp. of Japan exclusive right to distribute Rollerblade skates in Japan.  The wheels of the skates are mounted in a single  <tag key="formation"/>  to create the sensation of ice skating. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Five million part-time workers, many getting the minimum wage, want full-time jobs, the U.S. Labor Department says; the figure is unusually high for this late in a business boom.  Geologists doing low-wage work in retail stores will be first in  <tag key="formation"/>  for jobs when a big firm comes to town, an Oklahoma employment service says. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Towering over the sand and scrub pine at this city's outskirts is South Florida's tallest landform  Broward County's last legal dump.   <tag key="formation"/>  of trucks snake up its sides, adding more than a thousand tons of trash daily. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Stations, of course, are sweltering.)  After a minute's walk to the Wall Street station and a long wait in a slow  <tag key="formation"/>  at the token booth, I saw the Lexington Avenue No. 4 express shut its doors and pull away just as I reached the turnstile. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The weather in Russia stinks.  There is a perfectly valid reason why we have a "negative image" of the Russians as a grim-faced, bulky race huddled in long  <tag key="formation"/>  to buy shriveled rutabagas. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 But Robert Fersh bristles at the notion that soup kitchens are thriving because of spongers.  "If it was all freeloaders, then why didn't we see these  <tag key="formation"/>  at soup kitchens seven years ago?" asks Mr. Fersh, Food Research's executive director. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "But every Kareem Abdul Jabbar in Japan flocked to the boat hoping finally to find large-sized clothes," remembers one U.S. official.  For months after, the U.S. Embassy here got letters from Japanese complaining of long  <tag key="formation"/> , no meat and the poor quality of U.S. products. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Bluffs work only if they're not called.  Within a few hours after the crash on the Enterprise, a Marine Corps honor guard in dress blues appeared on the carrier deck, followed by two aluminum coffins that slowly made their way between two long  <tag key="formation"/>  of crew members, heads bared and bowed. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The option is especially appealing, they said, because demand for organs is up but donations are down.  "There are a lot of people that can be helped that you would otherwise have waiting in  <tag key="formation"/> ," said Dr. Dixon Kaufman, a transplant fellow at the University of Minneosta. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Last night, the Beijing University students crushed forward to listen to speakers who ignored a handful of plain-clothes police present.  Nearby, dozens of students crowded under the dim lighting of bare bulbs to read a long  <tag key="formation"/>  of wall posters, some of which were splattered with red ink to symbolize the murder of Mr. Chai. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The result is congestion, harried air-traffic controllers and frequently irate travelers.  Passengers endure long  <tag key="formation"/>  for tickets, toilets, taxis and their baggage. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 M. Ali Issari, a retired university professor, parked his car in front of a new-home sales office near Los Angeles one recent Saturday and stuck this sign behind the windshield: "The  <tag key="formation"/>  for purchasing Deeridge homes starts from here."  One week later, when selling started, the line had grown to 150 cars, and Mr. Issari bought the first Deeridge home to a round of applause from a mob of other house hunters. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 To see the effect of the anti-alcohol campaign, take a walk along Stoleshnikov Alley in downtown Moscow.  At one end of the narrow street, the  <tag key="formation"/>  to get into a basement beer bar stretches around the block. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Her decision swiftly prompted moans from Hungarians, including a sour reader who wrote to the Magyar Hirlap newspaper asking, "Does every wonder only last three days?"  When the McDonald's restaurant opened in Belgrade, police were called in to keep watch on the  <tag key="formation"/>  of customers snaking around the block and to limit the number of people entering the premises to avoid overcrowding. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The best way to reduce erosion is to lower price supports and target-prices that make it profitable for farmers to plant on marginal, highly erosive low-yielding ground.  The Conservation Reserve Program is simply one more of a long  <tag key="formation"/>  of evasions to avoid dealing with the fundamental irrationality of our agricultural programs. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 These are the same House Democrats who demand that Attorney General Meese resign if the merest puff of ethical smoke blows out of the independent counsel's office.  But they are disinclined to look into the affairs of the man who is second in the  <tag key="formation"/>  of presidential succession. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 In some of the nuttiest policies ever implemented in any country, the dictator decided to retire his country's foreign debt by exporting everything that wasn't nailed down.  Food  <tag key="formation"/>  are now so long, Moscow looks like a diner's paradise, and tree bark is an officially recommended dietary supplement. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The boom is straining facilities.  "If you want to tee off on Bethpage {in New York} on a Saturday morning, you have to get on  <tag key="formation"/>  at 3:30 a.m. or 4 a.m.," says Charles Robson, of the Metropolitan Professional Golfers Association. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 A recent seminar in Mexico City began with discussions of Martin Luther King Jr., and ended with practical exercises.  In one, the students formed a human chain, while their teacher played the role of a counterdemonstrator crashing into the  <tag key="formation"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Some people actually think a long supermarket checkout  <tag key="formation"/>  is a godsend. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 This clearly isn't the thinking of those seen at fashionable spots like Spago, the Los Angeles restaurant, where guests are definitely paler.  At the Stock Exchange, a popular nightclub, doorman Ken Martin says watching the  <tag key="formation"/>  of people waiting to get in used to be "like looking into the sun." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The Immigration and Naturalization Service had estimated two million persons would apply and that as many as 3.9 million were eligible.  In Houston,  <tag key="formation"/>  of families wrapped around the shopping mall that houses the legalization center. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Damage was extensive and it wasn't known how long the plant would be closed.  Peter Beutel, analyst for Elders Futures, Inc., New York, commented that the plant's shutdown "Won't create  <tag key="formation"/>  at the gasoline pumps, but it will tighten supplies." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Mr. Mitterrand, Mr. Chirac, and a former premier, Raymond Barre, want to crack down on illegal immigrants, but not to discriminate against legal immigrants.  Mr. Le Pen wants to reserve jobs and government subsidies to the French, put the immigrants at the end of the  <tag key="formation"/>   and send the illegals home. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 It justified the requirement on its need for information to fulfill its legislative power to appropriate money.  There is a  <tag key="formation"/>  of Supreme Court cases, dating back to 1821, upholding Congress's implied power to demand information. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Able-bodied mules are herded in groups into a chute, where veterinarians give them a once-over and check off their numbers, which are stuck to their foreheads like Chiquita stickers.  Some of the mules jostle in  <tag key="formation"/> , some try to bolt for freedom, but most quickly catch the old "hurry up and wait" draftee spirit, gazing about with big brown eyes and then readily boarding a stock trailer. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Daewoo should know.  To demonstrate solidarity and irritate Daewoo Motor, the union there got all workers to use only one of the plant's 15 cafeterias, creating long  <tag key="formation"/>  and stopping work. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The group, headed by managing directors Arthur Nagle and Daniel O'Connell, is said by industry sources to have  <tag key="formation"/>  up several institutions and individuals as financial backers, including the highly successful leveraged buy-out investor Raymond Chambers of Wesray Corp.  The seven join an increasingly long line of investment bankers specializing in high-profit deal making who have decided to go out on their own in pursuit of more money and influence, leaving behind large organizations with high overhead and low profit margins in many other aspects of the business, particularly securities trading and sales. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 FORD MAY have a better idea, but General Motors is no dummy.  Take the situation at Detroit Metropolitan Airport, where long ticket-counter  <tag key="formation"/>  have been the norm since Northwest Airline's takeover of Republic. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Nor does it benefit Northwest employees when they're members of the traveling public.  Like everyone but the GM crowd, the Northwest spokesman says, Northwest employees have to stand in the usual  <tag key="formation"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Mr. Wilson's wife was laid off from GM's Hamtramck plant a year ago because the cars built there weren't selling well.  He says, "The drug-selling  <tag key="formation"/>  in my neighborhood are getting longer. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Mr. Gore's remark about Mr. Castro and Mr. Arafat refers to Mr. Jackson's celebrated meetings with the two men.  Mr. Gore's showing in Connecticut was another in a  <tag key="formation"/>  of dismal performances since his impressive showing in the South three weeks ago. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Our walk through the dense vegetation of the reserve was accompanied by the loud cries of multicolored macaws flying overhead.  Other brightly colored birds perched in the trees around us, and industrious "leaf-cutter" ants formed moving green  <tag key="formation"/>  that wandered on and off of the trail before us. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Taxi driver Hector Pina, for example, now keeps a magnifying glass in his glove compartment to scrutinize notes.  Checkout  <tag key="formation"/>  slow to a crawl as cashiers not only count their change, but read it, too. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Each store will have one employee whose main chore will be to tidy up.  And an increase in the number of checkout clerks should reduce the waits in  <tag key="formation"/> , which were longer than the competition. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 One fan arrived at 4 a.m.and found 20 people ahead of him.  "Sometimes the  <tag key="formation"/>  stretches 60 yards, three or four people wide," says white-haired Joe Keesler, the owner. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Discontent is strongest among the young.  "Many young people here are critical of the government," says a jean-clad teen-ager waiting in a block-long  <tag key="formation"/>  outside Cafe Nord, an East Berlin disco. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 He got there before anyone else to wait for the doors to open on the first day the agency was to begin screening applications for travel to China.  "By being the first in  <tag key="formation"/> , I hoped my family would be convinced that I did what I could to come home sooner," he says. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 At age 43, waiting in a long ladies' room  <tag key="formation"/>  during a break in a business meeting was a new experience; I usually had the room to myself. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 In 1986, 40% of all accountants and auditors in the U.S. were women, up from virtually none 20 years ago.  The wait in the FASB ladies' room  <tag key="formation"/>  capped some recent experiences that convinced me that the "glass ceiling" that supposedly keeps women from rising above a certain level in corporations because they are women is a lot of baloney. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Her asking price is 15 rubles a kilo, which comes to about $12.50 a pound at the official rate of exchange.  Unlike the drab state food outlets, this market, a ruble away from Red Square by cab, has no  <tag key="formation"/>  and the salespeople really want to sell what they've got. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Its all part of a system of controlled access to desirable commodities and desirable freedom of movement and action that pervades almost all areas of life here in which people are acting on their own, not as part of a collective.   <tag key="formation"/>  turn individuals into an ad hoc collective. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 If you should want to try one, I recommend the stolovia upstairs next to the Central Market.  On a Sunday at midday, it had no  <tag key="formation"/>  and the staff seemed quite proud to be serving a sound meal to the city's foremost food purveyors. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 From Aiglemont, the Aga Khan's estate near Chantilly, he directs the 150 people who administer $130 million a year in grants, who design schools to be built by villagers and who give awards for the best in Islamic architecture.  To world leaders, the Aga Khan is a figure worthy of receiving  <tag key="formation"/>  and state dinners. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Agents often revive passengers who are wedged behind fake paneling, stacked like cordwood into vans or piled into semitrailers that drip urine and sweat from the overcrowding.  "It makes you sick to see little kids stuck in the trunk or the women who you know get raped or beaten," says agent Arthur Lamberson, a lanky 15-year veteran, as he monitors an endless  <tag key="formation"/>  of vehicles. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Shoppers must bag their groceries in most supermarkets, a requirement that doesn't dent the high food prices.  In return, you have to wait as long as 40 minutes in long checkout  <tag key="formation"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Fannie Fourie is a white South African, which makes him one of this country's more privileged citizens.  So why is he waiting in  <tag key="formation"/>  at a relief center for a handout of corn meal and canned sardines? 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "So what are you going to get with Jesse Jackson?  You'll have longer welfare  <tag key="formation"/> , and the lady in front of you in the supermarket line is going to have veal and shrimp and steaks, and I got chopped meat, and she's got food stamps, and I got to count my dollars." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 He isn't likely to get it.  In fact, the counsel, Gerald Ducharme, worries that the European Community's big overhaul of merger matters, part of the EC campaign to remove internal trade barriers by 1992, will do little more than lengthen the long  <tag key="formation"/>  of bureaucrats Ford already must negotiate with. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 We meet host Roy Scheider in the familiar environs of Red Square, but immediately we are carried away between the wintry banks of the Volga, over the crystalline waters of Lake Baikal, through the sunlit markets of Iblisi, above the misty peaks of the Caucasus, and across the golden grasslands of the Ukraine.  If our mental picture of the U.S.S.R. previously has consisted of gray, grim folk waiting in  <tag key="formation"/>  to buy a few shriveled vegetables, we'll be surprised by the stunning cinematography of Michael Reagan. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 But what is a travelogue, if not an effort to display only that which is attractive?  "Portrait" shows one  <tag key="formation"/>  of consumers, but quickly identifies them as New Year's celebrants in a "shopping frenzy" of gift-buying, because, as Mr. Scheider intones, "the Russians love their children." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 In response to a 0.6% cut in its budget, the Post Office has cut back window hours by 10% and ended Sunday mail collections.  And next month the 40 million or 50 million Americans who mail their tax returns around April 15 will face long  <tag key="formation"/>  at their local post offices as the price of a first-class stamp goes up to 25 cents. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 At the same time, distribution mistakes often left the shelves empty of goods that shoppers did want.  And even when shoppers found what they wanted, some gave up and went elsewhere because cost-cutting staff reductions meant interminable waits in checkout  <tag key="formation"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 With the heavy competition for systems, even some of the more aggressive bidders are being priced out of some markets.  "We just bid $2,000 per subscriber for some rather ordinary systems and we were sixth in  <tag key="formation"/> ," says Jeffrey A. Marcus, chairman of Denver-based Western Tele-Communications Inc. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 During the early 1980s, investors were obsessed with the weekly money statistics.  Long  <tag key="formation"/>  formed in the lobby of the Federal Reserve Bank of New York each week, and dozens of Fed-watchers churned out lengthy treatises on what each squiggle in M1 might mean. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Miami Beach millionaire Victor Posner began work Friday at Camillus House, an emergency shelter for the homeless here, admitting approximately 800 hungry people to its cafeteria-style food  <tag key="formation"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Mr. Mulheren spent Thursday night in jail.  Early Friday afternoon, the arbitrager was led into a county courtroom, his left wrist shackled to a  <tag key="formation"/>  of a dozen other prisoners. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 University National Bank in Palo Alto, Calif., has tellers, but it serves coffee in real china and offers after-hours service by appointment.  Robert Tennyson, a travel-agency operator, took his business to University National about a year ago, after Crocker National Bank was acquired by Wells Fargo & Co. Following the merger of the big banks, service at the local branch was "a nightmare," according to Mr. Tennyson: Teller  <tag key="formation"/>  of 15 to 30 minutes "were not uncommon"; the bank "lost one of our checks for six weeks," and it "treated us like we were nonexistent." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "Some fund groups were begging people to come in early last year," says John Foppiano, a tax partner at Price Waterhouse & Co.  "But we won't be seeing any  <tag key="formation"/>  at mutual-fund sales offices this April 15." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 At Addenbrooke's, the hospital where the paying Soviet journalist got treatment, about two-thirds of cases classified "urgent" have waited more than a month, and some 40% of those hoping for "non-urgent" procedures have been waiting for more than a year.  Citizens with private insurance or foreigners who pay like Mr. Louis can jump the  <tag key="formation"/>  at public hospitals. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 In big-time corporate bankruptcy storms, lowly shareholders are starting to steal some thunder.  Traditionally, shareholders have been the last in  <tag key="formation"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 It was steep by American standards, maybe $20 per person, but unimaginably extravagant for a family earning a normal wage in rubles.  As the American wife of a resident U.S. correspondent said in the passport  <tag key="formation"/>  at Moscow's Sheremetyevo Airport: "This is a great place for losing weight." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 What does that candidate do?  Pat Robertson, says Republican Charles West, 62, himself a minister, "is going to say, 'Let us pray,' and when they kneel, he's going to the front of the  <tag key="formation"/> ." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Slightly better financed and more ambitious entrepreneurs have launched cottage industries to turn out canned fruits, ketchup, shoes and handicrafts.  Even more intrepid are government workers who spend hours away from their desks enduring long, snailing  <tag key="formation"/>  in order to buy such carefully rationed items as soap, shampoo, diapers and clothing. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The Federal Communications Commission reinstated its programs to help minority entrepreneurs, but the first group in  <tag key="formation"/>  for the aid is the family of stock manipulator Ivan Boesky. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Snowflakes swirl and the wind creeps in through cracks in a wall of the shack where Santiago Medrano lives.  Mr. Medrano folds his arms and shivers as he waits in  <tag key="formation"/>  for the evening's meal of corn tortillas and shredded beef. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 An ambulance trails the candidate's limousine.  Police cars form the vanguard and rear guard; other police cars block off all the crossroads to make sure an errant John Deere doesn't break the  <tag key="formation"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The other day, the press van became separated from its five companion vehicles as the motorcade pulled away from the Blackhawk Hotel here in Davenport to start a long campaign day.  A Coca-Cola truck crashed the  <tag key="formation"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "But I'm the only Republican candidate who's going to vote for that treaty in the Senate."  Mr. Bush campaigns as a man in logical  <tag key="formation"/>  to the White House. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Teachers say they can't recall a single week in the past four years when they didn't go on strike.  In the courtyard, under a corrugated metal roof, a score of mothers wait in  <tag key="formation"/>  for their children's report cards. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 While the campaign was Mr. Gibbons's idea, however, he won't be paying for it: The donations will come out of the chain's national advertising fund, which is financed by the franchisees.  And by basing donations on BK Doubles, a new double-hamburger  <tag key="formation"/>  the fast-food chain is trying to push, Burger King works a sales pitch into its public-service message. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The day was saturated with the weight of its own impending history.  Long  <tag key="formation"/>  of people waited to buy special souvenir World Series postcards with official postmarks. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "Shortage" and "crisis" became buzz words, although neither really applied.  The spot dislocations that showed up were largely the result of confusion (much of it in Washington), though that was cold comfort for drivers waiting in mile-long  <tag key="formation"/>  at the gas pumps. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Board of Education, was such an issue.  In our time abortion has become another, best left to a  <tag key="formation"/>  of Supreme Court decisions rather than to the chaos of 50 state legislatures. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Yet in Mr. Laband's rehash of free-market logic, human greed and self-interest are the only permissible psychological reactions.  Allowing uncontrolled prices for necessities would indeed shorten the  <tag key="formation"/>  at stores, as he contends. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 But not because resources are going to their most efficient use, leaving scarce goods "allocated to those buyers who place the highest value on them."  Rather,  <tag key="formation"/>  would diminish because at higher prices many victims could not afford necessities such as food and medical supplies. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Under the contract Hydro-Quebec was to supply 400 megawatts of power to Central Maine Power starting in 1992, 600 megawatts starting in 1995 and 900 megawatts starting in 2000.  Hydro-Quebec said Maine regulators' refusal to approve the contract means Central Maine Power has lost its place in  <tag key="formation"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 More important, however, is the recent exodus of Germans from the "better half" to the West.  There is a long  <tag key="formation"/>  of East Germans waiting to get out. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Over the years many have even risked their lives to leave.  I have never been able to find a  <tag key="formation"/>  of people waiting to enter. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Although Agriculture Department officials thought they couldn't prove Richco was such an alter ego, according to Mr. Glickman, they still concluded that they had legal grounds for suspending Richco because the company is under Mr. Rich's control.  In investigating Richco's capitalization, added Gregory Frazier, a Glickman aide, "they traced the  <tag key="formation"/>  of ownership back through Marc Rich & Co. to Rich himself." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 In any case, the IBM announcement, coming on top of Hewlett-Packard's recent introduction, should accelerate the move to laser printers, which are faster and quieter and print neater than dot-matrix printers, but which have been too expensive for some tastes.  That certainly means more convenience for many users, who now may have to walk across the office to wait in  <tag key="formation"/>  to print a letter on a laser printer. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 This means that the current domestic deficit must be financed with bonds, which of course become readily marketable in Moscow, Leningrad, New York and London if the bonds carry the promise to pay principal and interest in gold.  Indeed, I would expect the Soviet Union could step to the front of the  <tag key="formation"/>  in seeking credit at the lowest possible interest rate. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The government in East Berlin agreed to allow about 10,000 of its citizens at the West German Embassy in Prague to emigrate but banned unrestricted travel to Czechoslovakia, which has emerged as the main gateway to the West.  The clampdown on travel came after hundreds of East Germans stormed through police  <tag key="formation"/>  to get inside West Germany's embassy compound in an attempt to follow nearly 40,000 others who have fled. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 But the agreement gave Znaniye the right to omit the final chapter, which deals with religious upbringing of children in the family, according to the Russian translator, Renata Ravich.  Judging by the  <tag key="formation"/>  at the book fair, Soviet publishers could make a fortune if they only had the nerve to push religious glasnost a little further. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 BankAmerica has been leading the pack, handing out free checking accounts and pushing credit  <tag key="formation"/>  with no up-front charges.  Its Seattle-based Seafirst Corp. unit is offering five bucks to any customer who has to wait in line more than five minutes (it's paid out about $2,000 so far). 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 For one thing, the place is such a hit that Ms. Briggs's husband, who used to hold the title of most frequent guest (probably just checking to see what leftovers he'd be eating that night), rarely gets to eat at his favorite restaurant anymore.  "He has to get in  <tag key="formation"/>  like everyone else," said his wife, with a helpless shrug. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Mr. Virnich said it was his understanding that his predecessor intended to make an offer to purchase EAC, which for more than a month has been seeking a buyer.  While he reiterated today that EAC is proceeding with that effort, Mr. Virnich said, "We've got a lot of interested parties, adding that Mr. Fritzsche is "going to be in the same  <tag key="formation"/>  with everyone else." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Mr. Giblen is the first to concede that Smith's, which operates 94 stores in eight Western states, is well run and a nice place to shop.  Its large, modern stores combining groceries and drugs are full of wide aisles and beaming employees, who seemingly make it their goal for customers to breeze through checkout  <tag key="formation"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 There were immediate ego and technical problems to deal with.  "It was like trying to shepherd a group of wild animals into a straight  <tag key="formation"/> ," said one of the participants, who asked not to be named. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Just think of it.  Airlines hold you captive for hours  in maddening ticket counter  <tag key="formation"/> , in smoke-filled airports, and in planes that seem permanently parked on runways. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "Microwaves have changed our perceptions of time in the '80s much as telephones changed them at the turn of the century," says Mona Doyle, president of Consumer Network Inc., a consumer research firm in Philadelphia.  "It has made even fast-food restaurants not seem fast because at home you don't have to wait on  <tag key="formation"/> ." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 On the way to work one morning, he stops at the building to tell Mr. Arkhipov: "Don't forget the drains today."  Back in his office, the  <tag key="formation"/>  of people waiting to see him has dwindled, so Mr. Goncharov stops in to see the mayor, Yuri Khivrich. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 How about lowering the stress levels of America's very stressed-out shoppers.  It emerges that one of their top pet peeves is waiting in long  <tag key="formation"/>  while other registers or windows stay closed. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 He hastily kissed the tarmac at Windhoek airport and then gave his mother a quick hug.  He proceeded briskly through a reception  <tag key="formation"/>  of party officials and old friends, and he barely had time to tell the news media "I am happy to be back home" before one of his bodyguards tugged his elbow and said "Comrade, let's move." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 He proceeded briskly through a reception  <tag key="formation"/>  of party officials and old friends, and he barely had time to tell the news media "I am happy to be back home" before one of his bodyguards tugged his elbow and said "Comrade, let's move."  Then he was gone, disappearing in an official motorcade that rolled past a mile-long line of supporters outside the airport. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Naturally, when the Cubs won the pennant in 1932, we wanted to see a World Series game," he goes on.  "The first one in Chicago was on a Saturday, and Chester and I got to the ballpark Friday night to get in  <tag key="formation"/>  for tickets. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 In this case, the government said, the aim was to claim unlawful tax losses.  Defense lawyers argued in their 43-page memorandum that there was a long  <tag key="formation"/>  of cases allowing tax losses in cases that were almost the same as the one against the Princeton/Newport defendants. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Suddenly, a blue truck drives up and delivers some boxes.  As they are unloaded at a desk near the cashier, a  <tag key="formation"/>  quickly forms around the desk, even though people don't know what the boxes contain. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Consider Mr. Adorno, the young New Yorker who paid $3.30 to cash his paycheck.  Mr. Adorno shrugs his shoulders when asked why he doesn't use a bank instead and says, "The  <tag key="formation"/>  at the bank are longer." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Four years ago, Antonio Mamani, a truck driver for a state mining company, carried his pocket money in a burlap bag because the devalued pesos were too bulky to fit in his trousers.  The price of a movie ticket often rose while he waited in  <tag key="formation"/>  to buy it. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 With less competition and less of a chance for newcomers to get into the game, these U.S. carriers will have a more stable and profitable financial environment than they've had in the past, says George James, president of Airline Economics Inc., a Washington consulting firm.  Moreover, he says, major U.S. air carriers also have such assets as undervalued real estate, valuable landing slots, airport gates, salable aircraft and even positions in  <tag key="formation"/>  to take delivery of new planes. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Warsaw, Saturday, Aug. 19: The first sign of the intense Western interest in this country shows up outside my plane window as we touch down here: a white Boeing jet marked "United States of America" parked among the Aeroflot planes on the tarmac.  Inside the terminal, the first of many long  <tag key="formation"/>  is at the currency exchange. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Some 60 tired Poles queue in the lobby of Super Sam, a big food market.  They haven't reached food  <tag key="formation"/>  yet; this is a line for shopping carts. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 There is no sugar.  To pay for their purchases, shoppers stand in yet another  <tag key="formation"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 He seeks the House investigation "to ensure that the public record is clear."  Mr. Frank's troubles are simply the latest in a long  <tag key="formation"/>  of ethical peccadilloes  financial and sexual, heterosexual and homosexual  that have left politicians and their advisers searching for guidelines. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Fortunately, 80% of Polish agriculture is already privately owned, though farms are usually only three to six acres.  If the state choked off its ruinous 15%-a-week hyper-inflation, sold or gave away larger tracts of land to private farmers and abolished price-fixing marketing boards, Poland's food  <tag key="formation"/>  could start to melt away. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Congressmen sitting in Rayburn House Office Building 2358  the appropriations subcommittee on transportation  could provide the answer.  This particular day, a long  <tag key="formation"/>  of lobbyists and observers waits in the hall outside the committee room to no avail: The panel has voted to close its meeting to the public, and now is in the process of negotiating which projects get funded and which ones don't. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 On a given summer's day, some 150,000 people pass through the turnstiles of Disney's parks, estimates Tom Powell, the editor of Amusement Business magazine.  They spend at least $10 each on food and souvenirs, he says, and they are happy, or at least willing, to stand in hour-long  <tag key="formation"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "As junk-bond issuers can't make their interest payments, there will be a reckoning," he said.  Elsewhere downtown, big  <tag key="formation"/>  formed for tickets to the Illinois Lottery's Saturday Lotto drawing. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 As they stood in the Charles Schwab office late yesterday, the investors, many of them elderly, stayed near the machines.  They took turns punching in their stocks, then headed to the back of the  <tag key="formation"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Just two weeks ago the government freed food prices as part of its reform program, doing away with the meat-rationing system that's been around since the time of martial law.  The result has been a run on meat that means the  <tag key="formation"/>  and discontent are even greater than before. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 In June, the Naderite consumer group Buyers Up made a media splash by predicting tight supplies would send gasoline prices soaring by 10 cents a gallon this summer, and could lead to 1970s-style gas  <tag key="formation"/> .  Pump prices instead have dropped seven cents a gallon since June, and even remote resort areas haven't seen any lines. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 At the same time, Saratoga is up to date enough to make wandering New Yorkers feel at home.  Signs in front of several of the manses proclaim them to have been condo-ized, the track offers Pick Six and trifecta wagering along with other new-fangled betting gimmicks, and  <tag key="formation"/>  everywhere are Manhattan-long. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Companies such as gypsum marketer USG, hotel operator Holiday and publisher Harcourt Brace Jovanovich have fended off raiders by borrowing to pay big dividends.  Either way, the stubs stand behind a long  <tag key="formation"/>  of bondholders if a company is dissolved; only after debt is satisfied can stubholders stake a claim to assets or earnings. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 That produced a return of $2.40 on a $2 win bet and made such tickets as valuable as souvenirs as in bills and coins.  Payout-window  <tag key="formation"/> , however, indicated that most winners were cashing theirs. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 May Speed Up Customs  THE U.S. CUSTOMS Service thinks it can shorten the  <tag key="formation"/>  for clearing customs  at least for businesses. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 As tea is served, a young girl tells of being ordered out of her family home in Bulgaria and being brought to the police station.  There she waited in  <tag key="formation"/>  for more than eight hours for a passport  only to be sent home without one. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 At London's Gatwick airport, delays are so bad the airport has put up two marquees with 1,000 extra seats, and brought in clowns to entertain children.  In Honolulu, travelers coming from Asia have been stuck in two-hour  <tag key="formation"/>  at customs and immigration. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 By contrast, travelers to Asia encounter most of their problems on the ground.  At Tokyo's Narita airport, industry officials say, it can take an hour and a half to park and get through the airport's customs and immigration  <tag key="formation"/> ; they cite an expected 16% increase in the traffic this summer. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Early next year, work is to begin on a three-year project to add 33 more gates.  But the next major expansion, which is to overhaul the departure hall and replace the two oldest  <tag key="formation"/>  of gates, isn't scheduled to occur until 1998. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 But lawmakers argue that dropping direct loans wouldn't save much money and that disadvantaged entrepreneurs would have a hard time competing for the guaranteed loans.  "People are waiting in  <tag key="formation"/>  for those loans. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 It's at the Orpheum, where, whatever else you may say about the proceedings, there's at least no wait for the ladies' room during intermission.  The only  <tag key="formation"/>  is outside the men's  Mr. Busch's tried and true fans, who've been supporting this master of camp farce since the beginning. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The Burbank, Calif.-based entertainment concern also said it tentatively has plans for a new "sea-oriented theme park" around the Queen Mary ship and Spruce Goose airplane attractions in Long Beach, Calif., which the company obtained through its acquisition of Wrather Corp. last year.  The expansion of the $500 million Disney-MGM Studios attraction was disclosed by Disney's chairman and chief executive officer, Michael D. Eisner, when he responded to an article in the Orlando Sentinel about crowded conditions and long  <tag key="formation"/>  at the park. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Q: What are you most proud of having done as enforcement chief?  A: It would have to be the  <tag key="formation"/>  of cases  Levine, Boesky, Drexel, et al. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 As I look back and I think of major cases that have been brought in the past, there's the Whitney case, against the president of the stock exchange for manipulation, a very important case. {In that case, former New York Stock Exchange President Richard Whitney pleaded guilty to two counts of grand larceny in 1938, leading to highly publicized hearings on what William O. Douglas, then the SEC chief, called "the whole anatomy of Wall Street chicanery and corruption."}  I think this  <tag key="formation"/>  of cases will be remembered as equally important for their time. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 In meetings with FAA and Transportation Department officials, they said that inspecting each electronic item would turn airport security checkpoints into giant bottlenecks.  Some passengers caught in long  <tag key="formation"/>  would miss their flights. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Meanwhile, merchants in Woodstock, N.Y., say business is slow.  "Either they're all waiting for August or they envision mud and long  <tag key="formation"/>  of traffic," says Jean Gaede of the local Chamber of Commerce, adding that no special event is planned. 
</sentence>
</body>
