<body>
<sentence>
 At that point, Mr. Keenan said he would again have to check on exactly where the shares reposed.  He made another call and came back on the  <tag key="phone"/>  with the news that the stock was at Eppler, Guerin & Turner, a Texas brokerage firm with no offices whatever in Utah. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 A spokesman for the NSA declined to comment on the agency's role in the Iran-Contra affair.  Intelligence sources said the encryption devices, described as computer-type keyboards that are connected to ordinary telephone  <tag key="phone"/> , aren't the most sophisticated such machines developed by the NSA. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 PLESSEY CO. and GENERAL ELECTRIC CO. of Britain received the first big export order, valued at the equivalent of about $24 million, for their System X digital telephone exchange.  Plessey said Telecom Colombia, the national telecommunications authority of Colombia, is buying 13 of the exchanges, involving a total of 68,000 telephone  <tag key="phone"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "Additional increases won't be necessary to bring long-distance rates down," he said.  The subscriber- <tag key="phone"/>  charge, also called the access charge, makes subscribers pay part of the fixed costs of the lines to homes and small businesses rather than adding these costs to long-distance service. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Mr. Fowler's action appears aimed at quelling growing congressional opposition to any increase.  The subscriber- <tag key="phone"/>  charge, also called the access charge, makes subscribers pay part of the fixed costs of the lines to their homes and small businesses rather than adding these costs to the cost of long-distance service. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The plan, called Linkup America, would pay for half the cost of telephone installation, or a maximum of $30; the remainder of the installation charges would be financed over time.  In addition, low-income residents wouldn't be required to pay subscriber  <tag key="phone"/>  charges. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "I don't look for any real dramatic change," said Paul G. Sherer, an analyst with Robertson, Colman & Stephens, a San Francisco investment concern.  Mr. Sherer said that while Equatorial's marketing niche is potentially lucrative  it is the sole supplier of low-speed satellite data communications systems for companies which now must depend upon dedicated telephone  <tag key="phone"/>   its satellite systems still are considered experimental technology by many corporate telecommunications managers. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Instead, they use such companies as US Sprint Communications Co.'s Telenet subsidiary and McDonnell Douglas Corp.'s Tymnet subsidiary, which charge cut-rate prices.  These companies rent private telephone  <tag key="phone"/>  and spread the costs among thousands of computer users. 
</sentence>
</body>
