<body>
<sentence>
 Mr. Marasek has been known to sew a loaf of bread together to prevent the cast from tripping over a fallen slice.  Eating itself poses a risk to actors, who may swallow more than their  <tag key="text"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "Planter's is giving us cashews for 'Broadway Bound,'" says Mr. Marasek.  "The cast goes through a pound a show, even though there's only a  <tag key="text"/>  about one nut in the script. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Macbeth is crowned king, but he is consumed by guilt.  Experiencing gradual disintegration, he utters the  <tag key="text"/>  that signal the futility of his existence: 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Mr. Boesky  whose prep-school education presumably included an introduction to Greek and Shakespearean tragedies  may have been less surprised than others by his own downfall.  Perhaps he remembered the  <tag key="text"/>  from Shakespeare's "Henry VIII": "Cromwell, I charge thee, fling away ambition, by that sin fell the angels." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "First of all, I can't stand movies with titles I can't pronounce," says one.  He shows us actors trained in Shakespeare stumbling over such tryout  <tag key="text"/>  as: "I ain't be got no weapon." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Indeed, it is rumored that some firms in New York at times dispense entirely with lengthy bills and detailed per-hour calculations.  Clients reportedly get a one-page bill on which is written a single  <tag key="text"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Not until he got to Emerson College, where he majored in directing, did he learn to speak fluently.  As he recalls his college days, he interrupts himself to rattle off the first six  <tag key="text"/>  of Moliere's "The Misanthrope." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 No one questions Mr. Dole's mastery of the details of government and his quick wit, but it still isn't clear whether he will be able to project vision, to talk less about committee action and more about conviction.  The entreaties to add a broader vision and a rhetorical lilt to the candidate's appeal  to force a speaker accustomed to the Senate chamber to project his voice to a national audience  are plainly jarring to Mr. Dole, who is uncomfortable with the touch of Tennyson that crept into the political speeches of the Kennedy brothers or with the  <tag key="text"/>  from Lincoln that are the staples of Republican speeches. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The agency is trying to determine whether a unit of Giant Group Ltd., a Beverly Hills, Calif.-based cement concern controlled by Mr. Sugarman, and other entities with TRE holdings failed to disclose that they were acting in concert, sources said.  Because of a production error some  <tag key="text"/>  were dropped in an earlier edition. 
</sentence>
</body>
