<body>
<sentence>
 The speech largely was written not by the usual team of White House speechwriters, but by an outsider to the administration, Landon Parvin.  Mr. Parvin has written some of First Lady Nancy Reagan's anti-drug speeches as well as gag  <tag key="text"/>  for a number of well-known Washington officials, including former Chief of Staff Regan. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 I wish I could remember who  wrote, "There's no sport righter than a sportswriter."  It's a cute  <tag key="text"/> , but untrue. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Three months later, when the tune was given the song-slide treatment, "Take Me Out to the Ball Game" became a big hit.  Twelve to 16 colored transparencies were usually necessary to illustrate a song, one slide for each  <tag key="text"/>  of lyrics. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The brief shot opens with him saying: "When I said I never knew a thing about the Watergate break-in, you probably didn't believe me, did you?"  That  <tag key="text"/>  is followed by a description of Mr. Ehrlichman as "an unbelievable person for an unbelievable product." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 As it stands, awkward as a boy who walks naked into the "Y" pool and discovers a crowd gathered for a swim meet, "Ishtar" provides embarrassment, but also laughter.  Ms. May has written some great jokes and clever  <tag key="text"/> : for example, the way Jack Weston, who does a brief but amusing stint as the low-level talent agent who represents the duo, sums up his clients' career prospects. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The news provides a lot of the jokes.  About a half hour before the show, the cast of six gathers backstage to brainstorm about new  <tag key="text"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Although a former Democrat and teachers-union activist, he earned a reputation as a fiscal conservative during his two terms as mayor of Tampa, Fla., by slashing property taxes.  As a gubernatorial candidate, Mr. Martinez, the grandson of Spanish immigrants, mocked his Democratic opponent, Steve Pajcic, with  <tag key="text"/>  such as: "He never met a tax he didn't like." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 People go about finding one in different ways.  The industrious will buy the Daily Racing Form and peruse the long  <tag key="text"/>  of tiny numbers that constitute the horses' biographies. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 But "The Bronx Zoo" sweats and strains all the same, regaling us poor understimulated viewers with oodles of lip-moistening, hip-grinding dirty talk.  While Harry and Sara talk a good game, the action is less convincing  perhaps because the two actors, David Wilson and Kathryn Harrold, can't conceal their boredom with the stupid  <tag key="text"/>  they have to recite. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Mr. Werner, a 27-year-old litigation specialist with Kirkpatrick & Lockhart, also described how a firm might review the work of a young associate named Abraham Lincoln: "About your work habits: You can't turn in your speech on the back of an envelope. . . .  And this first  <tag key="text"/> , 'Fourscore and seven years.' 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Their shortsighted commitment to quarterly figures skews the market and can be addressed only through new federal legislation.  Their testimony reminded me of the  <tag key="text"/>  in the comic strip "Pogo": "We have met the enemy and he is us." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 A local minister forbade his congregation to see "Hamlet"  presumably because of cuss words added by the company.  And there were mishaps, as when Gus Watson, the grocer, forgot the  <tag key="text"/>  "How now Lord Hamlet" and settled for "Hi." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Telephone  <tag key="text"/>  linking home terminals to the company's central computer weren't always reliable.  "We'd lose a line in the middle of transmission, and many times have to redo the work," says Raymond Howell, who helped oversee Hartford's yearlong experiment. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 NATURAL LIGHTING, subdued colors, extreme close-ups and a grainy film quality all contribute to the true-to-life feel of cinema verite ads.  Also, people in the ads speak with a natural cadence, using colloquial phrases and punctuating their  <tag key="text"/>  with pauses and an occasional "uh" or "you know." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 We have only four teeth.  Bayles: ALF, you used that  <tag key="text"/>  in a recent episode! 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "He's quiet, not particularly argumentative, and he knows what questions to ask.  If a lawyer forgets any of his  <tag key="text"/> , Nate is the first to prompt him." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Behind the scenes, however, another battle was brewing within Congress itself.  The budget resolution contains a  <tag key="text"/>  that is likely to create a furor in the oil industry and between lawmakers from different regions of the country. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "The way I always cast is, Would I want to sit next to him in a bar?" he says.  Adds Michael Forman, a Hollywood talent agent, "We have models that can't for the life of them deliver a  <tag key="text"/> ." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 IBM is expected to spend $30 million advertising the new products in the next three months.  The barrage began with a full-page newspaper ad yesterday that carried no company name and ended with a single  <tag key="text"/> : "Here we go again." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The decisive "no" vote was cast by an executive who thought the novel was an adolescent fantasy, and said the author would do well to consult a therapist about his problem.  The  <tag key="text"/>  found its way into the novel. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Her own marriage is an even richer source for the strip.  Mrs. Johnston often interrupts a marital argument to jot down a particularly good  <tag key="text"/> , says her husband, Rod. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The success of the cookies led her to team up with Deborah Kaufman, an arts administrator, to form Divines Inc.  The company's first product, called Divine Poetry in Chocolate, is a hand-folded, chocolate-dipped fortune cookie containing  <tag key="text"/>  from a poet, such as Oscar Wilde or Gertrude Stein. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Percentage figures were slightly off in one  <tag key="text"/>  of a table accompanying Warren Brookes's article on yesterday's editorial page. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 One reads far too much about cocaine addiction these days for either reaction.  What caught my eye were a couple of  <tag key="text"/>  in which McLain explains why he felt he was above the kind of constraints that might have led him to think twice about using the illegal and harmful drug. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Mr. Resnais compares the melodrama to a Puccini opera.  "I wanted it to be like a drawing you make without lifting the pen off the paper  I wanted the audience to be moved by the  <tag key="text"/> , the simplicity of the line." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Agreement even on relatively trivial matters, such as common safety standards for forklifts or children's toys, takes years.  So many tedious Council of Ministers meetings end without real progress on major issues that reporters joke that there is one opening  <tag key="text"/>  that serves for 90% of their stories. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 As a Wall Street Journal reporter, I'm often asked for advice on good investments.  I respond with such old  <tag key="text"/>  as: "Want to make a small fortune in the markets? 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 GABELLI EQUITY TRUST INC. had a net asset value of $9.36 and a closing price of 8 7/8 as of Friday.  In the listing of publicly traded funds in an earlier edition, the  <tag key="text"/>  were reversed. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "Oh, what a tangled web we weave, when first we practice to deceive," recited Assistant U.S. Attorney Sheldon Light, citing Sir Walter's 19th-century poem "Marmion."  Moving ahead 100 years, he closed with Mr. Dylan's immortal  <tag key="text"/> , "You don't need a weatherman to know which way the wind blows." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Although there's no plot to speak of, the cast includes the title character, a seer who talks to the birds (and they to him, natch); numerous believers and skeptical passers-by; a host of gods and goddesses; the personification of sorrow; and the personification of laughter.  There are also  <tag key="text"/>  for "A Thousand Voices" (muffled) and "The Distant Mountains" (which say "MOGOOOO! 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 She could be a young mother or a career girl," he says.  "But when you read the first two  <tag key="text"/> , she isn't that way anymore. {She is} out sleeping around." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Virginius Dabney, now 85, adds a prefatory note about the inception of this selection from his books and newspaper writing.  Occasionally he inserts a few  <tag key="text"/>  of comment at the head of a chapter. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 No one, least of all Mr. Hall, would say that the answers are all in on the future of the DTC.  But for the moment he can afford to take a deep breath and maybe even sing one of Randy Newman's  <tag key="text"/>  from a song in "All the King's Men": I'm all right now. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 America is the land of the Norman Rockwell small towns of his Hollywood youth.  Doubtless Ollie North's deeds remind the president of his own intrepid exploits in films like "Desperate Journey," where he helped Errol Flynn escape from a Nazi POW camp; the famous last  <tag key="text"/>  was, "now for Australia and a crack at those Japs!" 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Charles Boyer didn't say it to Hedy Lamarr in the 1938 film "Algiers."  But the famous  <tag key="text"/>  that never was has lent the oldest section of this capital an image of glamour and romance  and not without justification. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 He never grew up and his verse is bogged in his Swansea childhood."  But in writing such  <tag key="text"/>  will you allow yourself to think you are not paying off Dylan for his inimitable verbal talent? 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The big question about him is whether he can excite voters on the stump.  Seemingly anticipating this problem yesterday, he delivered  <tag key="text"/>  that echoed John F. Kennedy. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 But there must be something between overstylized video imagery and this lifeless stuff; beer commercials carry more of a wallop.  Ms. Jett makes something out of Patti despite the  <tag key="text"/>  Mr. Schrader has given her. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Nobody else made any impact, and not much was gained by chucking the opera's traditional spoken dialogue in favor of some recently discovered recitatives penned by Massenet after the 1884 premiere at the Opera-Comique.  On the other hand, the Met forces its "Carmen" cast to speak the original French dialogue instead of the traditional orchestrated  <tag key="text"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "Who knew the market would go up so far, so fast, this early in the year?" says Greg Confair, the president of Sigma Financial Inc., an Allentown, Pa., investment adviser.  "It's proof of the old  <tag key="text"/>  that the market will always act in a way to frustrate the greatest number of people." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 It started out with a  <tag key="text"/>  in Ronald Reagan's 1986 State of the Union address asking a member of his cabinet to come up with a program in which "the private sector and government can work together" to protect Americans hit by catastrophic illnesses from financial ruin. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 How many but-for arguments, "res ipsa" claims and 1,000-word footnotes can our culture absorb?  How many more federal judges can get by with  <tag key="text"/>  like, "We write, therefore, on a relatively "tabula rasa," despite the burgeoning field of securities law." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Mr. Iacocca has repeatedly said he doesn't want the nomination and appeared eager to send that message again following the board meeting.  "I'm stealing a  <tag key="text"/>  from the president and going for four more years, but I'm doing them in Detroit, and not in Washington," he said. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 However it is also rearranged and out of context to suit Mr. Billingsley's contention.  The very next  <tag key="text"/>  of my statment made it clear that I had been speaking satirically and that those views did NOT represent my own attitudes.  Mr. Billingsley did not see fit to quote that line. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The Postal Service said it will modify its contract with ElectroCom Automation Inc. of Arlington, Texas, in order to acquire more sophisticated mail-sorting equipment.  The new contract will mandate design changes so the equipment will be able to "read" several  <tag key="text"/>  of a typed address on a business-size envelope.  The original ElectroCom contract, valued at about $200 million, was for the delivery of 406 mailsorters capable of reading only one line. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 In the famous final scene of the 1939 film "Gone With the Wind," Rhett Butler, free at last from Scarlett's spell after being led around by the nose for three hours and 40 minutes, responds to her ultimate tirade with a sad, debonair: "Frankly, my dear, I don't give a damn."  Even today, audiences greet the  <tag key="text"/>  with cheers and applause. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 He stomped around Tampa threatening to molest the Skins in various ugly ways, including tearing off their lips (ugh!).  Alzado also got off the best pre-SB  <tag key="text"/>  I've heard. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 American Express officials say the company received a standing ovation at the rally when one of their marketers told the crowd, "We're mile-high on the Broncos."  Adds the company's Mr. Freeman, "How could you pass up a marketing  <tag key="text"/>  like that?" 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "Lorillard won't publicly admit it made a mistake, even though the people there are concerned about the controversy and will be altering the ads," says a source close to the company.  But Sara Ridgway, a Lorillard spokeswoman, asserts that the campaign won't be killed and that if there are any changes, "the essence of the ads, including the  <tag key="text"/> , 'The experience you seek,' will remain the same." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 A preface of a single page or less accompanies each play.  There is a glossary, and for the "Sonnets" an index of first  <tag key="text"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Sure one day to enter standard books of quotations was Sir Robert's admission that sometimes in his role as chief mandarin he had to be "economical with the truth."  That  <tag key="text"/> , says Peter Hennessy, a British political commentator, "could have come straight out of Sir Humphrey's mouth in 'Yes, Prime Minister.' " Sir Humphrey Appleby, in the TV show, holds the same job as Sir Robert holds in real life under Prime Minister Margaret Thatcher. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The House and Senate committees investigating the Iran/contra affair are trying to work out an agreement to meet on alternate days.  That way neither will upstage the other as each new revelation is milked, like a fine  <tag key="text"/>  from Hamlet, for all it's worth. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 But what, exactly?  Beyond memorizing the  <tag key="text"/>  and moving about in an appropriate way, what does an actor do? 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "I play the friend of another psychiatrist, who is perplexed because her patient, a compulsive gambler, wants to commit suicide," says Miss Skala.  "But a lot of my  <tag key="text"/>  were difficult to understand. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 In one instance, Miss Skala was able to tone down some raw dialogue by suggesting a substitute joke she remembered from her acting career in Austria, where she was born.  In a scene with Miss Crouse, she added a  <tag key="text"/> , "You need joy." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Charles Lindbergh's historic words were, "I made it."  Neil Armstrong uttered the neatly crafted "one small step"  <tag key="text"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "They are intrigued," adds Ms. Emmons, "because never has the technical mattered so much.  In other productions you kill yourself to make a chair and the director will just throw it out if they cut the  <tag key="text"/>  about the chair. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 But the API, joined by some groups professing concern for "national security," has begun suggesting that another energy crisis might develop sometime in the near future, probably by the mid-1990s.  Where have we heard that  <tag key="text"/>  before? 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 As it happened, much of the oil industry fared very well under controls, mainly because of the system of "entitlements" that acted as a subsidy to companies that depended heavily on imported oil.  We wonder to this day whether the Shell and Exxon executives who peddled the "impending shortage"  <tag key="text"/>  back then had foreseen how well their private interests would be served. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 At one point last week, the jurors sent word to Judge Cook that they were deadlocked on the loan issue, but Judge Cook sent back a note telling them to "continue to deliberate," Mr. Bryce said.  He said the instruction that most confused the jurors as they continued to deliberate was one  <tag key="text"/>  on a special verdict form that read, "Without such unanimous agreement, you must find the defendant not guilty of count one"  a racketeering charge. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 He said the instruction that most confused the jurors as they continued to deliberate was one  <tag key="text"/>  on a special verdict form that read, "Without such unanimous agreement, you must find the defendant not guilty of count one"  a racketeering charge.  Mr. Bryce said the jurors asked the judge for a specific clarification of that one line. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 If you're not abusing me, you're embarrassing me."  I didn't fully appreciate this  <tag key="text"/>  of dialog until the movie was over. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The Rev. Pat Robertson has good ideas, "but I don't think we're ready for him."  There's "something about" Rep. Kemp "that makes it impossible for people to understand what he is saying," and when a fellow GOP candidate told her Mr. Kemp reminded him of the Strategic Defense Initiative  about 60% effective  she asked whether she could borrow the  <tag key="text"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Mr. O'Neill may be the sort of man who watched "General Electric Theatre," but even retirement has not mellowed his view of Ronald Reagan, who entered politics in a fashion alien to Mr. O'Neill and who dominated Washington in the years of his speakership.  "Most of the time he was an actor reading  <tag key="text"/> , who didn't understand his own programs," Mr. O'Neill writes. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The command to shoot escapees has been made into law.  Even their national anthem is no longer sung because a  <tag key="text"/>  in the text says, 'Germany, united fatherland.'" 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 These are the kinds of answers that could come from children in any school in any stable, decent community, and for a moment it is possible to forget that the moral and physical blight of the ghetto is just outside.  But suddenly it intrudes in a single  <tag key="text"/> , tortuously written and full of misspellings, produced by a 15-year-old girl. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Mr. Abbott arrived here in early April, and after two grueling days of auditions set to work with the 20-member cast.  At first the actors were put off by Mr. Abbott's practice of telling performers exactly how to say a  <tag key="text"/>  and where to move. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 But gradually I added schoolboy stuff: a tug at the forelock, digging my shoe in the carpet.  Three weeks into the run the laughs were gone, and George said to me: Just say the  <tag key="text"/>  flat without those curlicues. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 MOVIE BUFFS remember the  <tag key="text"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The same arrangement will be used to portion out $12,000 gifts from next week's dinner, preceded by cocktails at Mr. Gorog's home in McLean, Va.  The invitation includes 15  <tag key="text"/>  of fine print explaining, "in accordance with Federal Election Regulations, 11 CFR 9034.8(c)(3)," how the money will flow. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 It is appropriate to ask whether, in our contemporary, deregulated transportation environment, the law promotes or encumbers public-interest considerations; whether nothing more is needed than to transfer the two industries to the other law; or whether, in an attempt to change, the collision of special interests in Congress might reshuffle the deck in some unpredictable way that would not serve either the public or the industries.  For people who have invested their careers in one or the other of the Railway Labor Act industries, these are profound questions that deserve more than a throwaway  <tag key="text"/>  in what is otherwise a constructive editorial. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Richard Lederer writes in Verbatim, the Language Quarterly, that a version of the song in early French had the suitor offering only a partridge, or une pertriz.  A 1718 English version combined partridge and pertriz so that the  <tag key="text"/>  came out sounding like a partridge in a pear tree. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 That Smart was a native of nearby Baton Rouge, La.  a mere set shot from his Superdome heroics  added piquancy to the show.  The truth-is-stranger  <tag key="text"/>  was stronger at the Masters, where winner Mize, a longtime also-ran, was a home-town boy who had cut his spikes at Augusta Country Club, just across the fence from the august Augusta National course where the tourney is held. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 For the taping, he brought together the scores of politicians who have appeared on Agildo in Wonderland over the past nine months.  All they had to do was wave beer glasses and sing a wish for the New Year, including these  <tag key="text"/> : 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Pennzoil further caved in when it dropped its demand for interest totaling about $1 million a day until payment of the settlement.  Mr. Kinnear stationed himself at Weil Gotschal with his battery of attorneys as the draft plan was examined  <tag key="text"/>  by line. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "At night, before we'd go to sleep, Jack liked to play some records; and the song he loved most came at the very end of this record.  The  <tag key="text"/>  he loved to hear were: 'Don't let it be forgot, that once there was a spot, for one brief shining moment that was known as Camelot.'" 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Newspaper editor Francis P. Church became famous for a 1897 editorial, addressed to a child, that included the  <tag key="text"/>  "Yes, Virginia, there is a Santa Claus." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Dawn Upshaw did not become the hot new soprano overnight, just almost overnight.  Three years ago she was a graduate student making her Metropolitan Opera debut with "three  <tag key="text"/>  and a great costume" as the Countess Ceprano in "Rigoletto." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 But he sees little reason to believe that its measures to decentralize economic decisions will achieve their goal of inspiring greater productivity and creativity.  One joke Mr. Birman hears from friends back home reverses that old Karl Marx  <tag key="text"/>  about capitalism being a necessary stage on the road to socialism. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Federal Reserve Board Chairman Alan Greenspan borrowed a  <tag key="text"/>  from his predecessor, Paul Volcker, and called upon the Reagan administration and Congress to take further steps toward closing the budget deficit. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "Wall Street Casualty," says another, followed by ads headed "Post Black Mon Value" and "Crash victim anxious for immed sale."  Some of these  <tag key="text"/>  may be just attention-getters. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Possibly still lacking is a sense of whimsy.  Some nutty  <tag key="text"/>  fell flat. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Reporters from Miami staked out his house and discovered Donna Rice.  And Sen. Biden, the Democratic Demosthenes, unhorsed for borrowing class-conscious  <tag key="text"/>  from a celebrated speech by Neil Kinnock, long-winded leader of Great Britain's socialist party. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 It turned out, too, that Mr. Biden really wasn't the student at college and law school he had said he was.  "I exaggerate when I get angry," said the senator, in a  <tag key="text"/>  that would have sent H.L. Mencken running for his trusty Corona typewriter. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 You've landed in the '50s, taking in still another earnest, angry melodrama about the failures of the system to recognize that eccentrics aren't necessarily crazy.  You're hearing  <tag key="text"/>  such as: "A divorced woman is a target. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Nevertheless, the composer called his "Desert Song" a romantic operetta and it was staged as such at the 1926 premiere.  Society having made a few small advances since then, director/choreographer Robert Johanson staged the piece as a parody, apparently revising parts of the libretto though I wouldn't own up to it if I were he since no  <tag key="text"/>  uttered suggested a modern mind at work. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 A British scientist is risking his life to get it out.  I am hooked from the opening  <tag key="text"/> : 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The movie's only bona fide star is James Earl Jones as "Few Clothes" Johnson, the impromptu leader of the black scabs.  Though his  <tag key="text"/>  are few, the sheer bulk of his body and that resonant voice make his presence felt throughout. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Next week, however, a tiny Silicon Valley firm will introduce a new reader that appears to provide a price breakthrough in reading technology.  Closely held TransImage Corp.'s $2,600 hand-held reader can be swept along a  <tag key="text"/>  of text in a book or magazine and instantly turn it into computer code for editing, altering or inserting into letters or manuals. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Will he try to take her home?  "You are putting me in a very delicate position," he says, in what seems to be a stock  <tag key="text"/>  for August bachelors. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The last two  <tag key="text"/>  are probably the most familiar: 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 And even though he's led us to believe that we were in for an evening of sentimental comedy, we let him get away with it.  But when he brings all the survivors onstage to weep disconsolately at their loss, and then, with a single mean  <tag key="text"/>  of dialogue sets them all laughing again we won't buy it. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The networks say they have to police commercials, because ads encourage people to imitate them, while programming is merely meant to entertain.  Typically, advertisers send to the networks storyboards of planned commercials; then the networks examine every  <tag key="text"/>  and nuance, often sending commercials back for changes and sometimes rejecting them altogether. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The group catches his enthusiasm.  "In a thousand years I couldn't come up with a  <tag key="text"/>  like this," says Mr. Gross. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 In numerous flashback scenes, we see him brutalizing his wife, his son, and his daughter, Elena.  Since it's impossible to judge the literary quality of a play when its  <tag key="text"/>  are being simultaneously translated via headphones, it's hard to know if "Renidero" is really as didactic as it seemed to me. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 This time, however, the formula flounders.  Oh, there are funny  <tag key="text"/>  and antic scenes: For example, Mr. Gently, the holistic private dick, promises to "solve the whole crime" and to "find the whole person," and a university don's nose is described as bearing a striking resemblance to "the controversial keel which had helped the Australians win the America's Cup in 1983." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Globe editors say Mr. Taylor's hand is light.  "We talk over major things, but Bill doesn't look over every  <tag key="text"/>  of copy," says Martin Nolan, editorial page editor. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 This latest "Jaws," the fourth in the series, is doing good business, though the audience I saw it with didn't seem very scared, or very involved in any way at all.  No one gasped when the shark (was it always so obviously fake?) chomped human snacks, nor did anyone boo or hiss at the silly  <tag key="text"/>  and generally awful performances. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 According to one current school of opinion, love is no longer compatible with female self-respect.  This opinion is reflected in the scene where Molly fails to get a rise out of her psychiatrist until she blurts out the  <tag key="text"/>  about still loving Fred. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Then the doctor pricks up her ears; clearly, here is evidence of a serious disorder.  And the same  <tag key="text"/>  is quoted in this week's TV Guide article about Blair Brown, the actress who plays Molly, as evidence of the contrast between the fictional Molly and the real-life Ms. Brown. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Paul Maslin, poll taker and political strategist, says he can predict now the single  <tag key="text"/>  that will set off the biggest ovation at next summer's Democratic National Convention. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Most virtuous of all is Ritchie, played by Lou Diamond Phillips, who with his sweet face and delicate carriage already looks frozen into sainthood.  He walks around the camp, his guitar tucked under his arm, exuding goodness and  <tag key="text"/>  like: "My dreams are pure rock and roll." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 With his eyes darting and intelligent, Adm. Poindexter had a professorial demeanor and a wonderful prop, his pipe.  He had some good  <tag key="text"/>  too, including the climactic words the whole plot had been building toward: "The buck stops here, with me." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The instrumentalists managed to cover the voices without much trouble, but Mr. Levine and the orchestra never summoned the full-blooded sound and the energy that Schoenberg's huge score wants.  Among the soloists, Tatiana Troyanos made a marvelously affecting Wood Dove; Philip Creech was expert as Klaus the Fool, and Mr. Castel handled the  <tag key="text"/>  of the Speaker most effectively. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "Blacks talk to their stars on the screen.  If they hear a clever  <tag key="text"/> , they'll say, 'Get down.' 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Those brief  <tag key="text"/>  tell much about the history of farming in this area. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 To help doctors and medical students sort through the thousands of pills and potions on the market, another computer program called McDope, written at McMaster University in Ontario, allows the user to administer drugs to a variety of patients and immediately witness the likely results.  Until it was revised, the program included this  <tag key="text"/> : "Your patient just died; do you have a good lawyer?" 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Joan Rivers provides the voice of a robot lady-in-waiting.  Her  <tag key="text"/>  are disappointingly dull but there's great pleasure in hearing that voice come out of a shapely, skinny body that looks as though it's been dipped in gold lame from head to toe. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Besides that, fashions in marriage change as in other things.  That  <tag key="text"/>  in the wedding ceremony about "until death do us part" seems nowadays a tie less binding than in former times. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Conductor Paul Nadler controlled the ebb and flow of Tchaikovsky's score with an expert hand.  Baritone Mark Pedrotti delivered Onegin's haughty  <tag key="text"/>  with a sneer as wide as Siberia, but his singing was considerably more detailed and refined. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Sometimes he stops to review a detail.  He's dissatisfied with a couple of deliveries, and Mr. Kosberg notes the  <tag key="text"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 He vowed to combat unfair trade practices overseas, create an agricultural policy that works, help the homeless, build strong families with strong values, and fight crime and violence.  And in a  <tag key="text"/>  that seemed to puzzle the Carthaginians, he said that "the ancient practice of human sacrifice, once commonplace throughout the world, is now obsolete." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 He has, after all, been writing familiar essays for a long time, and he has his moves down pat.  Perfect titles ("They Said You Was High-Class") and perfect opening  <tag key="text"/>  ("How do things stand with you and the seven deadly sins?") are standard equipment. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Pennzoil last week purchased advertisements in 35 U.S. cities and in the International Herald Tribune.  The top  <tag key="text"/>  read, "On November 13, 1987, The Wall Street Journal refused to run, unedited, this Pennzoil ad." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "I like to feel comfortable with doing good while I go about doing what I do well," he asserts.  Mr. Delfin, who has the born salesman's easy grin and smooth  <tag key="text"/>  of patter, is now focusing on raising money for the Red Cross's disaster relief fund, which totals about $30 million a year. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "The study shows the extent to which the most privileged in our society have reaped tremendous benefits from Reagan administration tax policies," said Senator Mitchell, invoking the ancient theme of class warfare.  We wonder if the senator bothered to read the study, because if he had he might have recalled the famous  <tag key="text"/>  about damn lies and statistics. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 An exquisite little painting by Jean-Jacques Hauer shows another French lady friend of Wordsworth who did not: Madame Rolland sits in her drawing room with her harp, pet dog and Lafayette.  Plucky to the last, she managed a much-quoted  <tag key="text"/>  before tied down to the plank: "Ah, Liberty! 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The 1923 classic Mr. Feshbach touted once again is making the late, legendary Jesse Livermore a cult figure.  The notorious stock-market speculator from 1891 to 1940 probably is best remembered for the  <tag key="text"/> , "I never argue with the tape." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Those men who, like me, have been removed for some years from the ceaseless bird-dogging of their college days will enjoy Ms. Hite's listing of "pickup  <tag key="text"/> " now popular in college watering holes.  For every line that employs the tools of the New Age  "I've been taking all these women's studies courses and I'm so confused about my sexuality"  there's one that counterbalances it with time-honored male logic: for example, "I bought you a beer!" 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 When the schoolkids put on their end-of-the-year concert in "Sarafina!" it's capped by a galvanizing number called "Bring Back Nelson Mandela."  The afternoon I saw the show, a small knot of South Africans in the audience shouted "Yes!" each time a  <tag key="text"/>  of the song invoked the name of a South African martyr. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Either way, Mr. Cavett is ill at ease  shifting uncertainly from foot to foot, fidgeting with his hands.  Under the time pressure, he botches  <tag key="text"/>  and says inane things (of a mid-match 200-200 tie he commented, "I can't help noticing the score is fairly even"). 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 And occasionally, the love-struck Vincent even rises above scriptwriter banality.  Instead of mouthing  <tag key="text"/>  like "I really care about what we have together, Maddie," he has the sense to quote Shakespeare. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 And a successful trip blighted only by boring banquets and ballets isn't the stuff of a dramatic opera.  "Nixon in China" unfolds like a sappy picture book, once we stop being mildly amazed seeing familiar-looking politicos turning into tenors and delivering such  <tag key="text"/>  as: "Your flight was smooth, I hope?" (Chou En-lai) "Oh, yes, smooooooother than most" (Nixon). 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Proponents of this view were abetted by NHL administrations, including the current one, that held that fighting is "part of the game."  If you had a dollar for every time a league or team official mouthed that silly  <tag key="text"/> , you could restore all of the money lost in the recent stock-market decline. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 There was no money in poetry, however.  Milton, for example, earned about a farthing a  <tag key="text"/>  from "Paradise Lost." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 In brief, the story about Marc Connelly is one of those transfers of jokes that always occur when a joke is good.  The man really responsible for the  <tag key="text"/>  attributed to Connelly was, in fact, Nicholas Longworth when he was speaker of the House.  Furthermore, his position gave the line its real point  the point being that the speakership in Longworth's day was not the dingy partisan and money-raising post that it has now become. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 He trusts his cops, and he likes them tough.  Another of his famous  <tag key="text"/> : ". . . the way to treat criminals is "'spacco il capo.'" 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "People tuned in and saw the old Rizzo," says Mr. Oxman, the political consultant.  His most notable  <tag key="text"/>  that night? 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 If Al Gore is sincere in distinguishing his views from that of the other candidates, he will have to lay out his case for a stronger defense in much sharper and more convincing detail.  Otherwise, voters will be justified in borrowing a  <tag key="text"/>  from a previous candidate and demanding to know of Al Gore, "Where's the beef?" 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 If Siegfried Jerusalem was an unusually agile Loge (Wotan's chief counsel), the chief god himself was unusually inert.  James Morris delivered his  <tag key="text"/>  with a penetrating baritonal glint, but he has not yet finished growing into this significant role, and his oddly tatty costume did not help him look important. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The allegations against Mr. Zaccaro hadn't yet been made when his wife, herself a former Queens prosecutor, was making her vice presidential bid.  Mr. Zaccaro's attorney, Robert G. Morvillo, borrowed her former running mate's  <tag key="text"/>  "Where's the beef?"  itself borrowed from a Wendy's hamburger ad  in criticizing the state's case. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 There is a Dadaist nonsense letter entitled "The," in which that word has been replaced by an asterisk.  Thus, the epistle's opening  <tag key="text"/>  reads: "If you come into linen, your time is thirsty because ink saw some wood intelligent enough to get business from a sister." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Real lawyers do not enjoy pseudo-courtroom thrillers like "Jagged Edge."  They endure such drivel by finding fault with every  <tag key="text"/>  of courtroom dialogue, objecting through their popcorn. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 You've got to make your character LIVE.)  Then executive producer Toby Hubner gives me a real role with three  <tag key="text"/>  of dialogue, to be shot a few nights hence.  "Wow, three lines?" says the sarcastic sound man, Antonio Arroyo. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Rosalie is played by Carissa Channing, 23, a bleached-blond breathtaker. (Orville is played by John MacKay, age 39.)  As I study my  <tag key="text"/> , Ms. Channing worries that the tight white dress she wears in the scene is too sheer. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 I say no, but this convinces her I am.  The camera is rolling into place, and my three  <tag key="text"/>  vanish from memory. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Take two.  Adrenalin pumps, and I dare to ad lib, changing the  <tag key="text"/>  from "I don't think so, Madame," to "Nah, don't think so, lady, ALL RIGHT?" 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Ms. Browne is quite effective, and doubly so to those who remember her as she appeared 10 years ago in "The Turning Point," when she was the naive newcomer who won Mr. Baryshnikov's heart.  You can see that Tony is a playboy, with his leather jackets and his red sports cars and the kind of come-on  <tag key="text"/>  only teen-agers and internationally celebrated dancers would dare try even on gullible junior ballerinas. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 In this, his first play, he takes the role of the obnoxious, abusive host of a radio call-in show, and lets other actors play the obliging colleagues at the station and the lonely, sometimes demented listeners who call in.  This looks like a real play, with David Jenkins's equipment-filled radio studio; with actors, under the direction of Frederick Zollo, walking on and off delivering  <tag key="text"/> ; and with a possibly dangerous, certainly deranged fan bursting into the studio for a face-to-face confrontation. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Joe Biden was an early exponent of the character issue, using it as a tool to undermine Ed Meese's nomination to attorney general (Mr. Meese's past acts, he intoned, were "beneath contempt").  But character came back to destroy Mr. Biden as a plagiarist, who even as he was withdrawing from the race claimed as his own Robert Kennedy's "bend history"  <tag key="text"/> , a borrowing Mr. Biden had admitted days earlier. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 But as part of PBS's wonderful "American Masters" series, "The Ten-Year Lunch" is least successful at what other shows in the series (notably the season opener on Isaac Bashevis Singer) have done so well  profiling their subjects.  We are introduced to a cast of characters, we hear a few of their famous  <tag key="text"/> , but we get only the vaguest sense of them as people. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 There's something decadent about the Algonquin Round Table  so much partying, so many arch word games, such desperately cynical style consciousness.  After all those funny  <tag key="text"/> , why should you end up feeling sad? 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 If your muse isn't up to it, no matter.  The bard of Les-Loges-en-Josas, France, Stephen Powelson, stands ready, able and more than merely willing to pour the first 14,300  <tag key="text"/>  into your ear, from memory  and in classical Greek.  Soon, he hopes, he will have committed the final 1,393 lines to memory. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 He has returned to the U.S. at least 40 times in the past 10 years to do the "Iliad" thing, usually for not more than an hour or two, at schools and colleges.  At these exhibitions of mnemonic prowess, a resident classicist randomly picks a  <tag key="text"/>  from the epic, and Mr. Powelson takes it from there. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 At the age of 10, he says, he memorized in one week an entire year's homework in Sunday-school Bible studies.  In prep school, he memorized the first 100  <tag key="text"/>  of the "Iliad," took three Greek courses in his senior year and won a national prize for his Greek. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 He has performed at the Universities of Arkansas, Colorado and Massachusetts and at Tulane University, among other places.  His wife of 47 years, Esther, says that Mr. Powelson is constantly mastering new  <tag key="text"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Although its amalgam of recipes, crafts, fashion, advice and homemaking tips will sound familiar  "Free In This Issue!  Complete chicken cookbook and 8 recipe cards to save," reads a cover  <tag key="text"/>  from the prototype  First promises a cleaner, more readable package with less ad clutter. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Time and again he had rehearsed an answer referring to the victims in his family and asserting to Mr. Bush, "I don't need any lectures from you about crime."  He didn't deliver the  <tag key="text"/>  or even refer to his father or brother. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 I am that man."  He never used the  <tag key="text"/> , although  like the planned answer to the question about crime  he used them in subsequent speeches. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 That's not to imply that he doesn't do well with Lucky's long, chaotic meditation on meditation.  But even before he utters a single  <tag key="text"/>  of dialogue, Mr. Irwin astonishes with his eloquence. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Before you even arrive at a party, of course, you must  according to Ms. RoAne  "practice your handshake."  Then deliver your opening  <tag key="text"/> , which you have practiced beforehand as well. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 They were well-supplied with blue-and-white Bush-Quayle signs, red-white-and-blue pompons and miniature American flags.  High school cheerleaders leaped at many applause  <tag key="text"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 And without a budget deal, business leaders, economists and even some of Mr. Bush's own economic advisers agree with Mr. Greenspan that financial instability could quickly follow.  Wall Street and foreign markets discounted the vice president's tough anti-tax rhetoric during the campaign, assuming he would drop his "Read my lips; no new taxes"  <tag key="text"/>  after the election. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 A Pentagon spokesman says, "We have no specific solutions for DOE."  The  <tag key="text"/>  at the NSC is, "DOE has the lead on that right now." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Horses are run to win purses and bets, not break records.  The race track, where the talk is saltier than the french fries, has a stock  <tag key="text"/>  for everything, and "time is only important in prison," covers that. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The consumer products giant sought to become a much bigger force in the cookie business, developing a Duncan Hines soft cookie meant to challenge Nabisco's dominance in the market.  Nabisco responded ferociously, with its own "Almost Home"  <tag key="text"/> , and Duncan Hines' market share ended up being miniscule. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 He has been twitting his opponent for not knowing a dairy goat from a mountain goat.  His favorite  <tag key="text"/> : "I'd like to see Leo try to milk that sucker." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 This  <tag key="text"/>  has been moving sharply upward as more people crowd it from below.  To steal a line from Alan Reynolds of Polyconomics, so many people have been getting rich there isn't room for them all in the top fifth. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Here as elsewhere, Mr. Bush's attacks on Gov. Dukakis over such issues as crime and defense have hurt the Democrat, but the poll shows that the economy is one area where voters were more likely to react favorably to the governor as they learn more about his positions.  Perhaps for that reason, Mr. Bush this week has been seeking to appropriate Mr. Dukakis's own applause  <tag key="text"/> , telling supporters in Wisconsin and Michigan that "George Bush is on your side." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 In this era of media-bashing, Mr. Sohmer was shrewd to make his investigator-hero an FBI agent (Robert Loggia) rather than, say, a Washington Post reporter.  As for TV news, it gets bashed in the person of a brunette-bombshell producer (Stepfanie Kramer) who curls her ruby lips around  <tag key="text"/>  like: "Get me a closeup of those stiffs!" 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 It is Ms. Diggs's contention, though, that Florence was no plaster saint, and in her skillful dramatization the playwright illuminates the many sides of this complex, driven woman.  Ms. Diggs makes her point of view clear in the opening  <tag key="text"/>  of the play, when someone comes on stage reciting Henry Wadsworth Longfellow's laudatory poem about the "Lady With the Lamp," and another character calls the poem "sentimental drivel." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Washington, Mo.: Another high school filled with teen-agers yelling as he steps out on a stage draped with so many flags I thought he might wear one.  While he clears his throat to launch into his drugs, death and defense speech, reporters, a beat ahead, whisper his familiar opening  <tag key="text"/> : "With all this excitement, I can feel what it'll be like on election night." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Augusta, Ga.: Thomp.  Two motorcycles, nine cars and vans, and two buses are rolling resolutely to the next stop, the Regency Shopping Mall next door to a muffler shop  and, please, we already thought of the "Midasize him!"  <tag key="text"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 It was just weird, in the sense of popular culture finding a bizarre way to express its racial ambivalence.  One of the last minstrels was Al Jolson, described by his biographer, Pearl Sieben, as a man who "needed applause the way a diabetic needs insulin"  a  <tag key="text"/>  that might also describe Michael Jackson. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Stump appearances are chosen to highlight the message visually and to look good on the night's network television-news shows.  Snappy  <tag key="text"/>  are inserted in the speeches, some of them tested in advance, that are almost guaranteed to become "sound bites." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Soon, right on schedule, the Bush message will switch to taxes.  The positive  <tag key="text"/>  will be that Mr. Bush won't raise taxes; the negative one will be that taxes have gone up faster under Mr. Dukakis in Massachusetts than they have in the nation generally. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Even with all this going for it, however, "Reckless" doesn't measure up to Mr. Lucas's previous play, the excellent "Blue Window."  The playwright still shows a deft hand with dialogue  I especially like the way his off-speed  <tag key="text"/>  make you laugh first and wonder why later. (For example, when Lloyd asks Rachel if she sees her parents, she answers, "Not since they died." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The confusion is symbolized by the differences between two former Kennedy speech writers now working for Mr. Dukakis.  Theodore Sorensen, the architect of "Ask not . . ." and other soaring John Kennedy  <tag key="text"/> , recalls an earlier liberalism of civic obligation and popular community goals. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The young Michael Dukakis was inspired by the party of Jack, but built his career in the party of Teddy.  And this year he has borrowed some of Mr. Sorensen's  <tag key="text"/> , but more of Mr. Shrum's message. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The chain quibbles with the way the ad is promoted on the cover, which says "Free Condom Inside" in prominent type.  "Spin's intentions may be honorable," a Waldenbooks official says, "but the way the cover  <tag key="text"/>  is presented, it appears as though they're using the feature of the free condom to sell the magazine." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 And effective last July, the state started putting all license-plate proceeds directly into its treasury  instead of allowing the ruling party to skim them first.  The 52-year-old Mr. Mutz, borrowing a  <tag key="text"/>  from Ronald Reagan, argues that Republicans "are the change." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "We're just not getting our return on investment," Mr. Bayh argues.   <tag key="text"/>  like that please the Republicans who show up, sometimes rather furtively, at Bayh fund-raisers. (One GOP attorney in Fort Wayne blanches visibly when a reporter asks him his name. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 You knew one thing: Good pitching, which the Dodgers had, beats good hitting, which was the A's previous long suit.  That  <tag key="text"/>  ought to go over the entrance at Cooperstown. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 A Chemical spokesman said, "This transaction is consistent with Chemical's anti-apartheid South African policy in every way."  He noted a  <tag key="text"/>  in the bank's policy statement: "We have a policy against making loans to private non-banking corporations for their operations in South Africa." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Justices Liacos and Abrams have also objected to the "good faith" exception to the U.S. Supreme Court's "exclusionary rule."  In one murder case, for example, they excluded from trial evidence from a search conducted by police in good-faith reliance on a warrant issued by a magistrate who, it was later noticed, had not struck through certain  <tag key="text"/>  on the printed warrant form. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 I became rather fond of M, a casually self-deprecating fellow played by Patrick O'Connell.  He keeps humor and horror nicely in balance for 90 minutes and lets the terror palpitate through his  <tag key="text"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The big institutional investors aren't buying Wall Street's  <tag key="text"/>  about now being a great time to jump back into the stock market with both feet. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 As bedtime approaches, the Xus sit together on a worn sofa and entertain their visitor by singing their favorite music, a Chinese opera called "Marriage of a Goddess."  Mr. Xu stumbles occasionally reading his  <tag key="text"/>  and has to ask his wife for help. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 For high British, it's always, "Oh, no"  or "oew noew."  Sometimes, it's a  <tag key="text"/>  from the script. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Neatly printed on the wall was: "I ain't never gonna love nobody but Cornell Crawford."  The  <tag key="text"/>  stuck with her  "so funny and dear, and who's Cornell anyway?" 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 All of punditry is treating Lloyd Bentsen's crack that Dan Quayle is "no Jack Kennedy" as the best  <tag key="text"/>  of the campaign, but for the wrong reasons. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 (At least the aides appreciate the absurdity.  The prize for best  <tag key="text"/>  of the night goes to Bush pollster Robert Teeter. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Bentsen and Quayle polished their  <tag key="text"/>  for tonight's 90-minute vice presidential debate in Omaha, Neb. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "I don't believe it," said Judith Penniman, the ABC producer, "we got a reader!"  Translation: ABC anchor Peter Jennings read the Bentsen  <tag key="text"/>  himself, with no accompanying pictures from his troops in the field. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 It closed Friday at 4, down 5/8.  The Regina lesson may be that glowing stories about companies should be read more for the one or two  <tag key="text"/>  of caution than for the positive comments. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Then the women make their first major mistake.  Instead of leading their quarry  <tag key="text"/>  by line through the rows of questions on the registration form, they depart. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 DUKAKIS STRATEGISTS believe that their man won the first debate but that they were outgunned in the "spin patrol" claims afterward.  They say their mistake was in reacting to the debate itself while the Bush crew stuck to a prearranged  <tag key="text"/> , and they vow to emulate the GOP tactic in next month's final encounter. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 All of these productions were excellent  funny, well-acted, with good stories.  Yet,  <tag key="text"/>  after line of the dialogue was loaded with gratuitous and explicit profanity. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The bank took out an ad in the Times of London last week, which ran opposite excerpts from Mrs. Eliot's edition of the letters.  The ad reprinted a  <tag key="text"/>  from a letter written in 1917: "I am getting along nicely in my work at the bank and I like it." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Silence."  And then the president remembered a  <tag key="text"/>  he had used years before, something about how he wouldn't make age an issue in the campaign, he wouldn't exploit his opponent's youth and inexperience. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Perfect, Mr. Ailes told him, and the president suddenly seemed to grow in self-confidence.  Mr. Reagan used the  <tag key="text"/> , and it was a zinger. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The rhetoricians in the socialist camp have gotten so full of themselves lately that some had come to doubt this point.  In a much-quoted  <tag key="text"/>  she said it would be folly to try to fit the European countries "into some sort of Identikit personality." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "We did consumer research before we made a pricing decision on 'Good Morning, Vietnam' and were a bit surprised to find such a high desire for ownership," says Carole Black, a Disney video executive.  "Some people were big Robin Williams fans; others didn't get all the funny  <tag key="text"/>  the first time and wanted to view it over and over again. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Mr. Scala and his boss, Mr. Hohorst, who is 33 years old, both say they are too busy to read lengthy economic news stories and analyses.  They rely mainly on the frantic financial wire services, and often they read only the headlines  a single  <tag key="text"/>  of shorthand that appears on the very bottom of their computer screens, in whatever space isn't taken up by a long list of currency price quotes. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 He knew, we knew, that the Ayatollah would not live forever, and that Iran is one of the most important countries in the Middle East.  We knew opening some  <tag key="text"/>  to Iran was in the national interest; now that the war is winding down nearly everyone agrees. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 As a young man he had turned out comic stories for cheap magazines and newspapers at the rate of one a day; this work got him through medical school and kept his impoverished family  his parents, a sister, four brothers  alive in their cramped Moscow apartment.  At the end of his life, the celebrated playwright and author of 588 stories could barely write four  <tag key="text"/>  before collapsing in fatigue and pain. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Mr. Irons turns in a pair of bravura performances as the twins, but neither of them redeem this somber piece of work.  Poor Genevieve Bujold, the drug-snorting, authentically Canadian actress who comes between them, is required to say  <tag key="text"/>  like this, with a straight face: "I've been bad, I need to be punished." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 But as sure-footed as this production's dramatic scenes are, its choral passages are lame.  Which is not to say that the 12 elders in the chorus can't project their  <tag key="text"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Antigone is played as a feminist, inveighing against "the laws of the male sex."  Every  <tag key="text"/>  about Creon's cruelty is rendered in the language of the police state, every reference to Antigone's sex cloaked in feminist rhetoric. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 We didn't give John-John the award for all time, but just for 1988.  Take a look at the cover  <tag key="text"/>  again, and take comfort from it. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "The children come to school in plastic."  One of their favorite songs has the  <tag key="text"/> : "It rains and rains/Until the stones will break." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Thus, when Mr. Dukakis went to Annapolis Wednesday for a statehouse-steps rally to taunt Mr. Bush for backing out of the presidential debate that was to have been held there, access was controlled by issuing tickets through Democratic leaders for the best viewing area, which was roped off.  The Bush campaign, meanwhile, has taken to distributing cases of air horns to supporters that can be sounded whenever the vice president delivers an applause  <tag key="text"/>  so there will be a din of enthusiastic cheering on television  and also can be used to drown out the chants of any Dukakis supporters who might materialize. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Mr. Bush does sometimes address substantive issues, as he does today in a well-received speech to San Francisco's conservative Commonwealth Club attacking Mr. Dukakis' record in managing the Massachusetts economy.  But the speech, one of the most effective of Mr. Bush's campaign, illustrates its careful style: The vice president reads it from a Teleprompter, sticking carefully to his prepared text and thus not risking any distracting ad libs like his Pearl Harbor Day gaffe of last week, or fumbling any of the  <tag key="text"/>  designed for television consumption. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Marilyn Quayle, defending her husband's mediocre academic record, told an interviewer last weekend that FDR "failed the bar exam seven times."  Yesterday, Sen. Quayle picked up the same  <tag key="text"/> , saying that Roosevelt flunked "a number of times." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 But then again that may be difficult.  It used to take a minute on television and one or two  <tag key="text"/>  in the newspapers to give a weather report. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The New York Shakespeare Festival's summer production of "King John" has given many theatergoers  myself included  the chance to be virgins again.  It's not often we get to see a Shakespeare play whose plot, characters, famous  <tag key="text"/>  and legendary interpreters aren't rattling around our brains before the curtain goes up. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 It doesn't seem to matter if you'd been the economic adviser to a president under whom the economy failed, or are affiliated with a consulting firm that can't come close to an accurate economic forecast.  With a snappy  <tag key="text"/>  about how Mr. Bush would need to reinstitute child labor, annex other countries or tolerate 20% inflation, you could get your lick in. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 In my best imitation of Ethel Merman, I sang a few choruses about being tired, and then drifted into a noisy sleep on Ms. Raiken's shoulder.  She elbowed me and I awoke with a start, belting out a few more off-key  <tag key="text"/>  about fatigue and life. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 When he said he had left behind "things you can't put in a suitcase," the audience members wept unabashedly.  They cheered Yoli's  <tag key="text"/>  about the Yanquis and roared at the jokes about "weepy Argentines"; they turned this astute but modest play into an occasion for a communal catharsis  which is exactly what Aristotle said theater was invented to be. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Officials here vigorously dismiss any parallels between the reforms they opposed with force in Czechoslovakia and the Soviet changes now being pushed by Mr. Gorbachev.  Despite glasnost, the new official openness about controversial topics, there were few articles in the media about Sunday's anniversary, and the ones that were published repeated the old official  <tag key="text"/>  about "rendering internationalist assistance" to a grateful Czechoslovak people. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 But the convention isn't seen boosting Senate prospects; Republicans have no sure pickups to offset likely losses in Virginia and Nevada, and say they will do well to maintain the 54-46 Democratic edge.  Candidates will adopt Reagan's "We are the change"  <tag key="text"/>  to address voters' desire in the polls for a new direction. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Ms. Richards had them rolling in the aisles with her lacerating jibes at George Bush's silver foot in the mouth, etc.  Not to mention the best and the brightest of them  the Ginger Rogers  <tag key="text"/>   which brought down the house. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 She just did it backwards and in high heels.'"  One woman in particular won't forget that  <tag key="text"/> : the woman from whom Ms. Richards lifted it  TV journalist and author Linda Ellerbee. (It's part of her lecture repertoire.) 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Ms. Ellerbee also reports that she spun around and warned the woman she was going to steal that.  This is, needless to say, not exactly the same as appropriating a  <tag key="text"/>  and then delivering it in tones brimful of the pride of authorship  in a keynote address.  Ms. Ellerbee learned in advance that Ms. Richards was planning to use the line, whereupon she inquired as to whether Ms. Richards was planning to cite the source. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 After all, if Ann Richards and Co. had been old-fashioned enough to say, "As Linda Ellerbee tells us" or even "as I heard in a lecture somewhere," why then the New York Times columnist and a great many other citizens probably wouldn't have gone around talking about the formidable wit and wisdom of Ann Richards.  In the days following the speech there was a certain amount of to-do about another  <tag key="text"/>   the famous silver-foot-in-the-mouth comment, which a Washington writer claimed came from his book. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Nor is Ms. Richards alone.  Recall that Walter Mondale and speech writers, without batting an eye, filched and offered as Mr. Mondale's own a  <tag key="text"/>  from a speech given by Lane Kirkland only a day earlier: i.e., "Where's the beef?" (Flashing epigrams have changed some since Stevenson's time, you'll note.) 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Recall that Walter Mondale and speech writers, without batting an eye, filched and offered as Mr. Mondale's own a  <tag key="text"/>  from a speech given by Lane Kirkland only a day earlier: i.e., "Where's the beef?" (Flashing epigrams have changed some since Stevenson's time, you'll note.)  Among Republicans, Barry Goldwater has the best reason to know the price you can pay for appropriating lines.  Presidential contender Goldwater would have been a lot better off in 1964 if he had only seen fit to credit the real author of what turned out to be the most self-destructive lines ever uttered in a campaign speech: "I would remind you . . . extremism in the defense of liberty is no vice." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Presidential contender Goldwater would have been a lot better off in 1964 if he had only seen fit to credit the real author of what turned out to be the most self-destructive  <tag key="text"/>  ever uttered in a campaign speech: "I would remind you . . . extremism in the defense of liberty is no vice."  The real author, whose line Sen. Goldwater changed slightly, was Cicero.  Had the senator not neglected to mention this fact, the line, needless to say, would have been treated with the respect usually accorded the wisdom of the ancients rather than as the extremist frothings of the candidate of the lunatic right. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 But my fellow Americans, this is not a crime-does-not-pay story.  Being caught out lifting  <tag key="text"/>  doesn't mean there's no profit in it. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 After all, despite a few rumblings here and there, the millions who heard Ann Richards continue to credit her as the wit who said that about Ginger and Fred.  Ms. Richards seems to know it, too, for on a Sunday talk show a few days after the convention, she did allow as how she had taken a  <tag key="text"/>   the silver-foot-in-the-mouth one  from Lily Tomlin's co-author in "Signs of Intelligent Life in the Universe." (She made no mention of Ginger and Fred). 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 All the same, the vice president continued, Mr. Dukakis represents "the failed liberal ideology of the past."  "Some say this isn't an election about ideology," Mr. Bush said in his address to the convention, mocking a  <tag key="text"/>  from the Dukakis acceptance speech. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "It's nothing new," says Peter Teeley, an old associate and former press secretary to the vice president.  He recalls, with tender sentiment, a Bush  <tag key="text"/>  from the 1980 campaign. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Some of these names are dropped for a reason, but most are there primarily to show off Mr. Wilson's own literary breadth.  The technique reaches a level of distracting absurdity when, to elucidate Tolstoy's increasing contempt for his wife, Mr. Wilson quotes three  <tag key="text"/>  of a poem by Philip Larkin, an English librarian born 12 years after Tolstoy died and who could not be more remote from Yasnaya Polyana in sensibility than a Martian. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 In a warmly received speech that seemingly sought to distance him from Reagan administration civil-rights policies, Mr. Bush outlined what he called a "positive civil-rights agenda," and promised to have "minority men and women of excellence as full-scale partners" during his presidency.  One winning  <tag key="text"/>  from that speech: "Whenever racism rears its ugly head  Howard Beach, Forsyth County, wherever  we must be there to cut it off." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Every bell and whistle in the orchestral bag of tricks is heard.  Sometimes, the large cast, 13 or so depending on how you count the extras and the offstage alto voice, sing all at once but with different  <tag key="text"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Meanwhile, Sen. Domenici, a longtime backer of deficit-reduction measures, works himself into a "no tax increase" posture to help his own cause.  GOP strategist Eddie Mahe suggests Bush errs by delaying his choice until the last minute: The convention is a stage show, and "you ought to figure out who the stars are so you can write their  <tag key="text"/> ." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Indeed, his strategy seems to be not to say very much at all about foreign policy.  His "well-received" Atlantic Council speech in June was little more than a routine defense of NATO, while his acceptance speech in Atlanta devoted all of seven sentences to U.S. security. (His boldest  <tag key="text"/>   that drugs are more of a threat than the Sandinistas  was a rewrite of Jesse Jackson.) 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 It's a bizarre idea: "Leave It to Beaver" with a new cast (say Tom Selleck and Suzanne Somers as Ward and June, and Emmanuel Lewis as the Beaver).  Think of "Gilligan's Island" as America's "Macbeth," a show you'd want to see again and again, with different thespians giving their own personal interpretations of immortal  <tag key="text"/>  like "Gee, Skipper." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 A magazine ad for Lee has a grainy appearance and shows a nighttime scene in which a blonde in tight-fitting jeans leans against a 1950s-vintage covertible.  The copy  <tag key="text"/> : "Places to go. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "We believe the yield on the long-term Treasury bond could fall below 7% in late 1989 and perhaps decline significantly in later years," says Martin J. Mauro, manager of research.  But to many analysts, the Yardeni outlook ends with the last  <tag key="text"/>  of a nursery rhyme  "and the dish ran away with the spoon." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 If he's looking for other ideas, there are Republicans who might have some.  Sen. Ted Kennedy of all people actually stole a GOP  <tag key="text"/> , in Atlanta, when he said Democrats "are committed to the ideal that all of us can advance together  and none shall be left behind."  The man who has said that for years, who calls it his "Good Shepherd line," is Jack Kemp. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "It makes us sound inferior," Mr. MacKenzie says, "and yet Diet Coke has been reformulated at least as many times as Diet Pepsi."  Coke says NBC has asked it to delete the controversial reformulation  <tag key="text"/>  from any future taste-test ads and that it will comply with that request. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Over a plate of red, white and green pasta  the colors of the Italian flag  he explains how mass-market retailing fits in with these schemes.  Advertisers on his three national television networks could add  <tag key="text"/>  like "available at the Standa," to their sales pitches, he says, sharing the ad costs with the department store. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 But Congressman Richard Gephardt of Missouri, a rival for the Democratic nomination, once charged that the Massachusetts governor's foreign policy experience was limited "to negotiating with New Hampshire Gov. Sununu over a nuclear power plant."  In an otherwise strong performance, Mike Dukakis did little last week to prevent George Bush from stealing that  <tag key="text"/>  during this campaign. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The gimmick?  He has no voice, so he won't have to speak any dumb  <tag key="text"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The intention is to blur ideology, contrasting the Massachusetts governor's ethnic past and his record as an executive with Mr. Bush's elite upbringing and his recent service in the shadow of President Reagan.  Each  <tag key="text"/>  the Dukakis campaign etches into its portrait of the candidate is supposed to produce a contrast with Mr. Bush. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Ads for Pro Penns emphasize they're more durable than regular Penns.  For instance, beneath a print ad featuring a shot of a doghouse is the  <tag key="text"/> : "Pro Penns go to the dogs 30% slower." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "It is time for America . . . to reassert progressive values and reinvest in its people," it says, but only "within a strong commitment to fiscal responsibility."  The Democrats do take a rhetorical bow to the Rev. Jackson's stump-speech  <tag key="text"/>  about "economic violence against poor and working people," but they reject his proposals to raise taxes on "the very richest Americans" or to freeze defense spending. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Who would have guessed women and wit were part of the Democratic Party of 1988.  "George Bush was born with a silver foot in his mouth" is the only memorable  <tag key="text"/>  to come out of this convention so far. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Its share of the bar-soap market slid to about 11% from 17%.  It has rebounded a bit to 13.5%, however, since the company returned to the "Aren't you glad you use Dial?"  <tag key="text"/>  a few years ago. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 It has rebounded a bit to 13.5%, however, since the company returned to the "Aren't you glad you use Dial?"  <tag key="text"/>  a few years ago.  Sara Lee Corp. walked away from the line "Nobody doesn't like Sara Lee" and experimented with other jingles that never quite caught on with consumers. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Anybody who knows anything about political conventions knows that the affair cannot truly move forward until a single, wry  <tag key="text"/>  from David Brinkley defines it, as he has since the beginning of time (meaning, of course, since the beginning of television). 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 It also claimed to have scored a market share victory in the intensifying orange juice wars.  Tropicana, a unit of Seagram Co., brought suit against Atlanta-based Coca-Cola over a  <tag key="text"/>  used in advertising for Coca-Cola's new Minute Maid Premium Choice orange juice that described the pasteurized product as "orange juice straight from the orange." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Some say 70%.  As the reader ponders these  <tag key="text"/> , at least three out of 10 boat people just setting out to sea will most probably not make landfall. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Divided up among various members of the cast in what seems a deliberately random fashion, it is used to suggest meanings without ever stating them.  Much of it is spoken by a pair of narrators (Sheryl Sutton and Phillippe Chemin), who, from a place at the side of the stage, intone their  <tag key="text"/>  in voices that, at once expressionless and intimate, have less to do with explanation than with ritual. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Tropicana Products Inc. fired another volley in the orange juice wars, accusing Coca-Cola Co.'s Foods division of false and deceptive advertising in a lawsuit filed in U.S. District Court in New York.  At issue is a  <tag key="text"/>  used in advertising for Coca-Cola's new Minute Maid Premium Choice orange juice that describes the pasteurized product as "orange juice straight from the orange."  Bradenton, Fla.-based Tropicana, a unit of Seagram Co., claims the line violates an earlier appeals court ruling in favor of Atlanta-based Coca-Cola against Tropicana. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Ms. Keeton says her marketing department designed the ad, but she was the one who made the decision to sustain the suspense throughout the ad.  Originally, she says, the first  <tag key="text"/>  of the ad was, "Of course she's not really 70." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 But she thought, "Why waste it?  So I got rid of the  <tag key="text"/> ." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The "three weeks of stagnation," as the period between the two articles is now known in the Soviet Union, showed perestroika for what it truly is: a party  <tag key="text"/>   no less but no more either.  A better line, to be sure, a line one can support with greater sincerity than most other lines  but a line nevertheless. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The three weeks of stagnation indicate how far Mr. Gorbachev may have to go in eradicating the curse of Soviet and Russian reformers.  That curse is best expressed by Pushkin's immortal closing  <tag key="text"/>  of "Boris Godunov": "The people are silent." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The texts are often shortened to make the books cheaper to produce, leaving a skeleton of the original story.  Mr. Lang notes that there are at least 10 heavily illustrated editions of the Snow White story in which the whole tale is told in 12 pages, with only a few  <tag key="text"/>  on each. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Newspaper editors only seem cavalier when they dump your favorite comic strip  the one you've been following faithfully for 23 years  and substitute some dumb cartoon with stupid gag  <tag key="text"/>  and chicken-scratch drawings. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 It is the world's leading corporate raider talking, addressing the crowd on finance.  One almost expects, at some point, to hear that unnerving  <tag key="text"/> , Greed is good. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Fighting back, Texaco managers have adopted a slogan: "We've got the energy."  It sounds more like a  <tag key="text"/> , some say, that a TV network would use to tout its fall lineup. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Others think the Texaco boast is a rather bold claim for a company that's running out of oil.  In any case, Mr. Icahn has his own  <tag key="text"/>  for Texaco: "Catch a Falling Star." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 According to a new study by Michael Cunningham, a University of Louisville psychologist, the magic formula is a simple "Hi," followed by something equally innocuous, such as "What do you think of the band?"  Although few men realize it, calculatedly clever come-ons turn most women off, Prof. Cunningham says. (He notes that when it comes to women pursuing men, however, just about any opening  <tag key="text"/>  will do-except, perhaps, "You remind me of someone I used to date.") 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 To gather this wisdom, Prof. Cunningham first sent operatives out into the field to test a variety of conversation starters on the patrons of Chicago singles bars.  Then, in a lab setting, he gauged the reaction of 40 men and 47 women to specific  <tag key="text"/> , including "Would you like to listen to my compact disks?"  Participants were asked to rate one another according to 13 criteria as they used the lines: Did the speaker seem shrewd or naive? 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Would the speaker make a good parent or not?  "People really do make almost instantaneous judgments of a person's personality" based on opening  <tag key="text"/> , maintains Prof. Cunningham. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Leslie Thomas, a junior at Pennsylvania State University, agrees that a straight approach is generally best.  "I don't think  <tag key="text"/>  work," she says. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Somewhat tamer than the previous Midler-Disney collaborations, "Big Business" is still peppy enough.  As City Sadie, the corporate queen, Ms. Midler gets the most pointed, and the funniest,  <tag key="text"/> , which she delivers like the seasoned pro she is. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Though Della Femina is only a fraction of the size of giants like Young & Rubicam and Ogilvy & Mather, Mr. Della Femina's flair has garnered the agency more than its share of headlines.  Mr. Della Femina became a fixture on TV news reports about acquired immune deficiency syndrome, for example, after his agency created the  <tag key="text"/> , "I enjoy sex, but I'm not ready to die for it," for LifeStyles condoms. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The Dukakis people are going to need all the help they can get.  Instructive is an Ailes  <tag key="text"/>   a bit of hyperbole, no doubt  that Mr. Goodman says he will never forget. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Mark Twain got a laugh when he called rumors of his death "exaggerated."  The  <tag key="text"/>  wouldn't have been nearly so good if he had simply labeled them untrue. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Shakespeare's famous  <tag key="text"/>  about killing the lawyers may have been superseded. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Take, for example, the subject of this week's discussion  the hero's adventure.  In one elegant  <tag key="text"/> , Mr. Campbell links the Celtic knight, wandering in the forest, to Telemachus, setting off to find his father, to Moses, climbing the mountain. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Mr. Sullivan didn't return calls seeking comment.  Ms. Bruck apparently added a  <tag key="text"/>  stipulating that female Drexel employees, as well as other women, were present, but she didn't retreat from her other statements on the subject of call girls. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Neither the program nor the critic's review mentioned the name of the young woman who turned the pages for the piano accompanist.  She, too, was superb, performing a most difficult job; there were several passages where she had to turn the page back for a repeat of several  <tag key="text"/>  of music. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 And I can tell you that I'm an absolute nervous wreck every time she performs.  I have her practice the last two  <tag key="text"/>  on each page, so I can learn exactly when to turn the page  just one of the tricks to this trade that I've learned the hard way. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 There is something to be said for experiencing Shakespeare's view of the kings who ruled England between the 1390s and 1485 as a unit, watching the same actor grow from the layabout Prince Hal into the heroic Henry V, the same actress move from the blushing bride of Henry VI to the embittered hag who curses Richard III.  It's interesting to hear the  <tag key="text"/>  summarizing events of the past while they are still freshly imprinted on your mind by the play you saw just a few hours before. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The plays are not so much updated as they are de-dated; and although Mr. Bogdanov is clearly trying to make this old news seem fresher to contemporary audiences, they nonetheless tend to snicker when they first notice the computer terminal or the plastic shopping bag that has cropped up without warning.  The fact is that audiences don't need such gimmicky "relevance" if they are given clear, carefully thought-out  <tag key="text"/>  readings coinciding with carefully planned stage movement. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 In a follow-up show, he points to two addicts and says if they tried to rob his house, "I'd blow their heads off."  Both  <tag key="text"/>  get wild applause from the audience. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The SEC said that the DeBartolos have been uncooperative, and had heavily redacted documents that the SEC requested.  Among the exhibits attached by the SEC is one full page labeled "Bilzerian-Hammermill closing" in which all but three  <tag key="text"/>  were deleted by the DeBartolos or their lawyers. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Most of his Republican colleagues are cowering wimpishly before organized labor's TV-ad onslaught.  This bit of demagogy features a  <tag key="text"/>  about golden parachutes for the bosses and nothing for the workers  as if there were somewhere a law mandating golden parachutes, or prohibiting labor from seeking whatever notification and severance procedures it wants through collective bargaining. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 She's best with the minor actors, who have the best parts.  Ms. Brennan gets the funniest  <tag key="text"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Everyone jumped on Larry Speakes for his confession that he put words into the mouth of President Reagan without even bothering to tell him.  One can certainly jump on Mr. Speakes for his apparent unawareness of the enormity of his transgression, at least to judge by the throwaway  <tag key="text"/>  in which he described the dirty deed. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Instead, government officials threw up their hands and claimed indirect trade was beyond their control.  The new official  <tag key="text"/>  is that once Taiwan products leave the island, the government has no say over where they go. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Nice, clean American kids will be free of this foreign imposed evil.  The Mexican who writes these  <tag key="text"/>  has been accused of being a gringo lover. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "I see no reason why this course should not be followed," Rep. Ted Weiss commented predictably.  Consumer advocate Sidney Wolfe recited a familiar  <tag key="text"/>  from memory: "American families are too important to be left to a Reagan administration that seems to give deference to the drug industry." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Last fall, before most of its experienced players ran out of eligibility, it won three major competitions in a row, losing finally to Texas A&M in November at the Super Bowl of meat judging, the International, held in IBP Inc.'s meat cooler at Dakota City, Neb.  That got Illinois some good press in trade publications like Meat Plant Magazine and Drovers Journal, but nary a  <tag key="text"/>  in the Daily Illini, the school newspaper. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The page shows the elegant interior of an expensive car.  There, just slightly to the northeast of the leather-covered steering wheel, and west southwest of the burled walnut dashboard trim, are six  <tag key="text"/>  from the second verse of the Marvell poem. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 There, just slightly to the northeast of the leather-covered steering wheel, and west southwest of the burled walnut dashboard trim, are six  <tag key="text"/>  from the second verse of the Marvell poem.  We know that these lines are by none other than Andrew Marvell because the name of the poet appears at the end where the author's name is customarily found in poetic quotations. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 It is just one interpretation of many."  He goes on: "If, in the  <tag key="text"/>  from Marvell's 'The Garden,' the car manufacturers had determined that this line is imperfect in their own view of what was necessary, then they could argue that indeed they were merely perfecting the poem and that Marvell would see that this was a better version for this particular purpose than the one he had in fact written. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 It's certainly not an unprecedented condition.  Many famous texts have been changed in the transmission in order to give more meaning to the original  <tag key="text"/> ." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Aileen Ward, Schweitzer professor of the humanities at New York University, also was enraged.  "Changing the word 'innocence' to 'comfort' is a dreadful comment on the trade-off between the real inspiration of Marvell and the debased standards that his  <tag key="text"/>  are being twisted to uphold." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 But I don't really consider it a very grave infringement of morality."  All the critics, however, seem to believe that the  <tag key="text"/>  "transmitted" by Mr. Macdonald in his advertising campaign are somehow inferior to the version that appears in anthologies. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Surely, for Soviet audiences, Jim is even more of an exotic character than Amanda, since young men of 24 here tend to be frighteningly cynical about their prospects.  Moreover, Jim's  <tag key="text"/>  about power and money being the point of democracy got a huge appreciative laugh here, as it is the very stuff of Mikhail Gorbachev's "perestroika." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The exchanges are disjointed, quirky, vivid, filled with Harold Pinter pauses and emotions as genuine as the blacktop.  And  <tag key="text"/>  by line, bit by bit, the characters of the cops develop (even if it is in super slow-mo, requiring weeks of watching). 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 He even talks like the other policemen: The ANC, he says, is controlled by communists and manipulated by Moscow, which wants to turn South Africa into a Marxist state.  But Peter and his fellow ANC defectors can go beyond that standard rhetoric with a  <tag key="text"/>  that is much more valuable to the police: "If I would see my younger relative joining the ANC," he says, "I'd tell him to go back home, that he shouldn't go through the same things I did." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 And if you don't, Larry Speakes will."  A White House aide (anonymous of course) says the president ad libbed the Speakes  <tag key="text"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Fans of the first season will recall a similar scene in which Cliff instructs Theo on the value of a dollar by handing him a roll of play money and then taking back a few bills every time Theo lists another necessity of his proposed bachelor lifestyle.  To compare these scenes is to conclude that Theo is still brash, the  <tag key="text"/>  are still clever, Mr. Cosby can still clown his way through worthwhile parental lessons, and the show still has a drolly astute tone. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 She was just "discovered," delivering her actor boyfriend's resume to a talent agent.  Now she is supposed to read two  <tag key="text"/> : "I'm the new cleaning lady" and "I can't work here  this place is a mess." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Now she is supposed to read two  <tag key="text"/> : "I'm the new cleaning lady" and "I can't work here  this place is a mess."  Unfortunately, Ms. Schroeder forgets first one line, then the other. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The fabrics have been around for years, but have "slipped into low profile" and lost ground to Minnesota Mining & Manufacturing Co.'s better-known Scotchgard treatment, according to Cynthia Gray, a Du Pont publicity specialist.  Du Pont believes women today care less about having a spotless sofa  the old promotion  <tag key="text"/>   and more about carefree living styles, she says. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 In early 1987, Mr. Steinhardt badly lagged the market.  Then, he bought the bulls'  <tag key="text"/>  that overvalued stocks could go higher. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Oklahoma basketball coach Billy Tubbs likes a good straight  <tag key="text"/>  as well as he does running up scores on opponents, so at a press conference the day before his team played Kansas in the NCAA championship game here Monday night he brightened when he was asked if he thought God might be on Kansas' side in the showdown to come. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Listen to the left itself cheer.  In The New Republic last month, Barbara Ehrenreich, co-chair of the Democratic Socialists of America, quoted approvingly a  <tag key="text"/>  that what the Democrats need is "a little class warfare." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Speaking from the Chicago offices of Centel's lawyers, Mr. Frazee said his company adopted a shareholder rights plan last August that basically gives the company time to consider takeover proposals and also protects against two-tiered offers.  Borrowing a  <tag key="text"/>  from corporate raiders, Mr. Frazee said: "Our goal is to increase shareholder value, and we believe we have an outstanding record in that regard." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Philip Reiss, an attorney for WPP, said the memo was found late Tuesday in the files of several of the departed directors.  The document, which appears to be a computer printout and isn't dated, has a  <tag key="text"/>  at the top stating it is from Ed Yaconetti, the former chief operating officer of Lord Geller, to the agency's management committee. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Journalist Linda Ellerbee recalls in her book, "And So It Goes," reading news on television about the collision of two jumbo jets on Tenerife in the Canary Islands.  She writes that she ended the report "with a poignant  <tag key="text"/>  about 576 people whose vacations had ended in death." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 In frustration, Mr. Wanniski says, he and a few allies raised $10,000 on their own to buy a four-page newspaper spread in Charleston, S.C., before last Saturday's primary.  The spread stressed Mr. Kemp's optimistic vision of lower taxes, more jobs, opportunity for the poor through greater choice, and "moving America forward but leaving no one behind," Mr. Kemp's "Good Shepherd"  <tag key="text"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 He also has created two attractive, articulate characters and he has been most fortunate in having them brought to life by accomplished performers.  As Andrey, Robert Prosky, a consummate character actor, has the lion's share of the good  <tag key="text"/>  and he delivers them with easy relish. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 When East Germans erected the Berlin Wall in 1961, the Social Democrats' Willy Brandt, then Berlin's mayor, compared their action with the creation of a Nazi-style concentration camp.  But today many Social Democrats are welcoming Gorbachev socialism with a  <tag key="text"/>  that sounds, to American ears, as if it were written from Moscow. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 But uglification is rampant, water shortages loom and suburban traffic is gridlocked, as a crazy quilt of 42 municipal governments does little to control growth.  In the South's smaller boom cities, like Nashville and Charlotte, the standard  <tag key="text"/>  is, "We don't want to be another Atlanta." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 In the aftermath of his victories in the South Dakota primary and the Minnesota caucuses, Mr. Dole says the campaign might now be able to put the "P" back.  "We have a whole new case of bailing wire," he explains, in the kind of humorous  <tag key="text"/>  he simply can't resist. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Mr. Robertson is not the only modern exponent of crackpopulism; Democrats Jesse Jackson and Richard Gephardt have made serious bids for the crackpopulist vote as well.  Mr. Robertson's attempt to erase his past is understandable. (His latest campaign brochure contains several  <tag key="text"/>  of biographical information but doesn't mention his career as an evangelist. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 When Sir Geoffrey asked me that, I said it was all there in our statement.  But he asked me "What's your best point?"  he asked me that repeatedly, until I got fed up with him, and I said this is not fair, it's not the sort of thing you can answer with one  <tag key="text"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The Gore tactics limited Mr. Hart's opportunity to seize the stage.  Though more forceful than in last week's Iowa debate, the Colorado Democrat went on the defensive early when NBC newsman and debate moderator John Chancellor characterized his re-entry into the race with the old song  <tag key="text"/> , "Will you love me in December as you do in May?" 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 And of course he could always simply start vetoing bills on explicitly procedural grounds, rejecting those with non-germane riders even if it means closing the government.  It would be a much less radical act, Stephen Glazier observes, simply to cross out a  <tag key="text"/>  of some bill and let the courts decide whether a president already has a line-item veto. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 As for "Strange Interlude" being more "detailed" than a soap opera, I wonder.  The play is famous for having its characters speak their "thoughts" along with their  <tag key="text"/>   a device that succeeds technically in the film, due to the skill of the cast and a soundtrack filter that distinguishes between their speaking and "thinking" voices. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 In a meeting on how to trim fat from the budget, OMB Director Miller downs an entire two-pound bag of M&Ms. . . .  Jokesters suggest this opening  <tag key="text"/>  for Sen. Biden next week when he meets Neil Kinnock, the British politician whose words he cribbed: "Stop me if you've heard this one." . . . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The job of vice president, he says, "is inside work with no heavy lifting."  His biggest  <tag key="text"/>  these days goes this way: "When Ronald Reagan wants his program passed  when he wants action on his legislation  he doesn't call George, he calls Bob." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Warner also was co-author (with Mark Twain) of a famous book entitled "The Gilded Age," a label later affixed to a whole generation.  And he wrote other memorable  <tag key="text"/>  for which almost nobody credits him. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "It's time for the opposition to come out of the streets and into the system," he was fond of saying.  Now his  <tag key="text"/>  is, "I tried to come into the system, but the Roh administration seems to want to push me back into the streets." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The jerky camera, the sliding in and out of focus, the jiggles and off-center shots that once were considered mistakes now are the basis for a style.  And the scenes aren't shot and re-shot: Even flubbed  <tag key="text"/>  are kept in. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 It shows a back view of two young women running along a beach and practically falling out of their swimming suits.  The copy  <tag key="text"/> : "He loves my mind. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Those familiar with Mr. Rudolph's work and the actors he frequently uses will be glad to know that Keith Carradine, still weary and handsome, shows up as Hart.  Genevieve Bujold does an amusing turn as an unscrupulous art dealer who says  <tag key="text"/>  like "You vex me" as only she can. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Perhaps the most memorable  <tag key="text"/>  in modern car advertising isn't about big engines or sleek styling, but about upholstery.  The line: "rich Corinthian leather." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "We thought we'd get a lot of factory shift workers," said Robert Wunderle, Supermarkets General's economist and vice president for public affairs.  "The reality is we found out that the majority of shift workers were white collar" and included transportation workers, medical services personnel, journalists and "just plain citizens that find shopping at 11 or 12 at night is a lot quicker than dealing with crowds and  <tag key="text"/> ." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Perhaps Mr. Brinkley means his story as a sort of allegory on how the world may end in a whimper.  If so, the moral lies in a  <tag key="text"/>  by Tennyson: "To strive, to seek, to find, and not to yield." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
  It never aired a television advertisement in New Hampshire that might have inoculated Mr. Dole from an image as a big taxer in a state where opposition to taxes is almost a prerequisite for election.  One reason the ad never appeared: Mr. Dole flubbed a vital  <tag key="text"/>  in a taping session. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Impoundments weren't subject to possible override by Congress, so they were a far greater presidential power than a  <tag key="text"/> -item veto.  Presidents didn't need to veto budget bills, line by line or otherwise, so long as they could impound. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Later, he introduces "Oliver Stone, the Academy Award winning writer of 'Midnight Cowboy'"  who, in fact, had nothing whatever to do with that movie and who happened to be on his celebrated tour of duty in Vietnam while Waldo Salt wrote the script.  Most surprising of all, but altogether typical of the avalanche of errors contained in his work, is the plot summary of "Network," in which Mr. Christensen describes anchorman Peter Finch crying out those deathless  <tag key="text"/> : "I've had enough and I'm not going to take it anymore!" 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 It's weird to see a great actress thrust into the middle of a sitcom, and you keep rooting for her to rise above it.  From time to time there are little flashes  a toss of the head, a hand on the hip, a  <tag key="text"/>  delivered with vintage Hepburn sarcasm. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 They can only hope that his friends will defend him, and that those who might criticize will heed his last request, wrenching for his family, and urgent for his country.  In his closing  <tag key="text"/> , Jimmy wrote, "Please try to understand." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Mr. Campbell, the head of Pillsbury's restaurant businesses, is well-known by insiders for an unflattering imitation of Mr. Stafford sitting stiffly at his desk and making a point by waving his glasses in a predictable pattern.  At a generally hostile meeting with securities analysts last month, Ronald Morrow of Smith Barney, Harris Upham & Co. introduced Mr. Stafford by using the Ricky Ricardo  <tag key="text"/>  from the "I Love Lucy" television series of the 1950s: "Lucy, you got some 'splaining to do." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Tommy is an arbitrager, meaning that he seeks to exploit small differences in the  <tag key="text"/>  at different books, or a favorable shift in the line over time.  Not long ago, for example, he found that the opening line had West Virginia University favored over St. Joseph's University by 8 1/2 points in basketball. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 But in each segment there's too much history and not enough incisive commentary  especially for a program that's trying to be "definitive."  Narration  <tag key="text"/>  like "comedy makes us laugh" don't help the cause much. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "They don't brag about their kids or make you watch slides of their vacations" says the headline of one ad, which shows two couples partying together.  Another ad features a photo of a father and his adult son and the  <tag key="text"/> , "You used to hate it when he told you what to do. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 He's been grousing about the theater throughout his career.  This began in earnest in 1970, when he spoke his first  <tag key="text"/>  on a New York stage  something unprintable about a tulip. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The suit also says the men circulated sexist literature, like "The Smart Man's Creed, or Why Beer is Better than Women."  One  <tag key="text"/> : "After you've had a beer, the bottle is still worth a dime." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 In 1985, in an "NBC Nightly News" report, he disclosed that W.R. (Buster) O'Brien, the unsuccessful Republican candidate for Virginia's attorney general, hadn't played football for three professional teams as Mr. O'Brien had contended.  For that portion of the story, NBC showed tape of Mr. O'Brien at the state prison, including standing behind bars, with a Bode voice-over saying "a politician who adds a phony  <tag key="text"/>  to his resume could wind up with an all-expense-paid visit to a place like this." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The objects of Mr. Hendra's considerable rants (I stopped counting at 163) range from those unlucky enough to have worked with him at National Lampoon, or to have done favors for him, to those humorists guilty of what he sees as insufficient artistic purity, the entire Republican Party, "stinking-rich fundamentalist scum," the sinister institution of television, the military, the rich, assorted journalists and political commentators, the middle class and the Roman Catholic Church.  With such a startling array of enemies, one might expect author Hendra, who during the '60s did stand-up comedy routines on the Ed Sullivan show, among other places, to get off a few good  <tag key="text"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 A more balanced comparison rises from Sir Isaiah Berlin's modern distinction between foxes and hedgehogs (the European equivalent of our porcupines).  Sir Isaiah based his scheme of classification on a  <tag key="text"/>  from the Greek poet Archilochus: "The fox knows many things, but the hedgehog knows one big thing." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The pop-up "Sleeping Beauty" illustrates another flaw in children's books: No one ever proofreads them.  "Several year past and the princess was still asleep," reads one  <tag key="text"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Yesterday, both politicians swapped jokes about their speeches "that they had been storing up," said Tony Beeton, the Labor Party's chief broadcasting officer.  Some in Washington had lightheartedly speculated Mr. Biden would greet Mr. Kinnock with this  <tag key="text"/> : "Stop me if you've heard this one." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 It takes a little getting used to, this TV adaptation of the lengthy Eugene O'Neill play.  The characters not only speak their  <tag key="text"/> , they also speak their thoughts. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Mr. Cathcart says he has had "a lot of fun" at Kidder, adding the crack about his being a "tool-and-die man" never bothered him.  "It was an absolutely marvelous  <tag key="text"/>  and one I used many times," he says. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Its symptoms include a cold sweat at the sound of debate, clammy hands in the face of congressional criticism, and fainting spells when someone writes the word "controversy."  As one unidentified official clearly in the late stages of the disease told the Times: "Baker just felt that there were some  <tag key="text"/>  in the speech that could be misinterpreted and seized by the press." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 On an office wall of the Senate intelligence committee hangs a quote from Chairman David Boren, "Don't hold your ticket 'til the show's over."  He once used that  <tag key="text"/>  in a closed-door meeting on Panama, meaning don't shrink from taking action against Manuel Noriega. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 For the second time, in a movie called "The Bear," French director Jean-Jacques Annaud demonstrates just how powerful pictures can be. ("Quest for Fire" was the first time.) To be sure, one wonders what kind of man is this, who feels compelled to try to understand the most primitive longing and instinct in a way that requires the most sophisticated appreciation of visual storytelling.  Supposedly, he proposed the movie to his producer, Claude Berri, in four  <tag key="text"/> : "An orphan bear cub. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Finally, of course, the boss gives in, but he's still yelling: "I find myself explaining anything to Teddy Kennedy, you'll be chasing stolen cars in Anchorage."  In fact, throughout "Mancuso FBI," we don't get words or  <tag key="text"/>   we get speeches. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 You're the real criminal here . . . and what you did wasn't just a murder  it was a crime against humanity."  And, at least once a show, someone delivers the  <tag key="text"/>  "Get off that soapbox." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 For now, defense attorneys are tight-lipped about their plans.  Max Gitter, another GAF defense attorney, said yesterday, "As we go in for the third time, Yogi Berra's famous  <tag key="text"/>  is apt: `It's deja vu all over again.'" 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 After a slick redesign, the two-year-old magazine has been relaunched this month by its parent company, Keizaikai Corp., the Tokyo-based company with interests that include financial services, book publishing and a tourist agency.  Printed in the U.S. and carrying the  <tag key="text"/>  "The Insider's Japan," Business Tokyo's October cover story was "The World's No. 1 Customer"  Japanese women. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Rep. Garcia, on trial for bribery and extortion, puts statements in the Congressional Record attributing missed votes to "scheduling conflicts." . . .  A GOP Senate fund-raising letter from Sen. Burns of Montana is made to appear personally written, and its opening  <tag key="text"/>  is, "Please excuse my handwriting." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 It works.  Mr. Bartlett managed to more or less maintain Moliere's Alexandrine verse form, 12 syllable  <tag key="text"/>  in rhyming couplets. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The new beer, introduced this week at a liquor industry convention, is imported from Switzerland's Cardinal brewery.  Heidelberg's first ads for the brand, which Sibra says will compete with imported light beer leader Amstel Light, feature the  <tag key="text"/>  "The best tasting light beer you've ever seen." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Whether a cash crunch might eventually force the company to cut its quarterly dividend, raised 36% to 75 cents a share only a year ago, has become a topic of intense speculation on Wall Street since Mr. Stookey deflected dividend questions in a Sept. 29 meeting with analysts.  Some viewed his response  that company directors review the dividend regularly  as nothing more than the standard  <tag key="text"/>  from executives. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "An L.A. solution," explains Mr. Friedman.   <tag key="text"/>  by line Mr. Friedman's weary cynicism can be amusing, especially when he's riffing on the Hollywood social scheme  the way people size each other up, immediately canceling the desperate ones who merely almost made it. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Harry has avoided all that by living in a Long Island suburb with his wife, who's so addicted to soap operas and mystery novels she barely seems to notice when her husband disappears for drug-seeking forays into Manhattan.  But it doesn't take too many  <tag key="text"/>  to figure Harry out. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "When Wall Street turned around shortly after the opening, there was panic buying in Paris."  Brokers said that as the news spread that Wall Street was moving up, traders who had called to place sell orders changed their  <tag key="text"/>  in mid-conversation, ordering buys instead. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 That issue, like racial tensions in New York City, will have to cool down, not heat up, before it can simmer.  But I am suggesting that they stop requiring Mr. Mason to interrupt his classic shtik with some  <tag key="text"/>  about "caring for other people" that would sound shmaltzy on the lips of Miss America. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Marubeni hopes the movie, "China Shadow," which will be about Hong Kong's return to China's control, will become a box-office success all over the world.  To make international success possible, the film is in English  even the Japanese actors deliver their  <tag key="text"/>  in English, whether or not they understand what they are saying. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 His voice is hoarse and his spurs drag in the mud, but "George Dickel" slogs through the drizzle and cold wind, bravely shouting his  <tag key="text"/>  in a staged shootout with a dastardly gunfighter, archrival "Jack Daniel." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Fatimata Sanga, the elderly woman cast as Yaaba (which means grandmother), is stringy, bald and toothless, yet she carries herself with an ethereal gracefulness.  At a news conference, Mr. Ouedraogo said the script  which is credited to him  had to conform to Ms. Sanga's inability to remember  <tag key="text"/> , or much of anything else. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The U.S. Customs Service provided you with enough facts to produce a balanced and fair article.  The opening  <tag key="text"/> , "It sounds incredible, even for a boondoggler like Uncle Sam," set the stage for the act to follow  a play, in our view, with no substance. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Pinned to the wall of a large reception room in the Soviet Embassy here, not far from a heroic portrait of the father of Soviet communism himself, hung a poster heralding the arrival in Washington of the Moscow Circus.  At the bottom in bold print was a  <tag key="text"/>  smacking unequivocally of free enterprise: "Brought to you by Snuggle." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The roaring of the sea and wind  fiery meteors flying about in the air  the prodigious glare of almost perpetual lightning  the crash of the falling houses  the ear-piercing shrieks of the distressed, were sufficient to strike astonishment into Angels.  Actually, the pen writing those  <tag key="text"/>  was that of Alexander Hamilton. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 For CBS Evening News, Juan Vasquez reported that "the residents of St. Croix are overjoyed to see the soldiers (1,100 military police dispatched by President Bush) from the mainland."  The word "residents" is loaded and Mr. Vasquez's wrap-up  <tag key="text"/>  were also unintentionally revealing: "For . . . tourists the nightmare is ending. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "Mountain, I want to be in you.  Together we could grow wild and natural things," Belinda wrote, among other, much  steamier,  <tag key="text"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 To communicate the "break-the-rules" ad series, Burger King hired 10 musical acts  including Paul Shaffer and the World's Most Dangerous Band, crooner Mel Torme and blues singer John Lee Hooker  and let them write their own songs for radio spots.  While abandoning the standardized jingle, that part of the campaign will be tied together with the  <tag key="text"/> , "Sometimes you just gotta break the rules." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 But the mystery behind that failure is one reason Mr. Hatch loves junk mail so: It's both mathematically precise (results of a mailing can be measured to the hundredth of a percentage point) and completely unpredictable.  When Historical Times Co. was soliciting customers, in a so-called dry test, for Civil War-related products that didn't yet exist, the company's lawyers insisted that the package include a microscopic  <tag key="text"/>  noting that the offer was contingent on receiving enough orders.  That line, the only difference between the new mailing and earlier ones, increased response by 15%. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 That  <tag key="text"/> , the only difference between the new mailing and earlier ones, increased response by 15%.  From then on, the company put the line on all its offers. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Foreign trade played a very small role in the U.S. economy.  Stories about U.S. exports in this newspaper would carry an apologetic  <tag key="text"/>  explaining that the subject really was worth discussing even though exports accounted for only about 4% of the gross national product. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 As an attempt to link decadent, dying Weimar with L.A. pool culture it was an astonishing failure from a talented director.  With the exception of the energetic Marvellee Cariaga as Mrs. Begbick and Jonathan Mack as Jack, who gorges himself to death on raw meat, the cast delivered its  <tag key="text"/>  without emotion or energy. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Underneath the slick production, the smoky grays and blues, lurks some rather unstylish racism.  As cop stories go, this one (written by Craig Bolotin and Warren Lewis) dredges up many cliches of the genre and invents many new ones, mostly vulgar  <tag key="text"/>  spit out by Michael Douglas with a reasonable amount of fervor. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 And Japanese star Ken Takakura admirably carries the burden of being the human Japanese, the cop who joins up with the visitors from New York.  Oh, yes, there's a girl, played by Kate Capshaw, whose  <tag key="text"/>  seem to have been cut drastically, but not nearly as much as the backs of her dresses. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Con men and charlatans are so thick and so persistent that they make camel drivers at the Pyramids look like Swiss maitres d'.  Typically, the hustle begins with a  <tag key="text"/>  reminiscent of the pickpocket in the movie "Casablanca," who warns a bar patron, "This is a dangerous place, full of vultures"  just as he's relieving the mark of his wallet. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 But after Kodak's second-quarter profit plunged 85%  and shocked Wall Street  only a tantrum, a vivid demonstration of how he wanted to cut costs, would suffice.  "There's no working the middle course in wartime," Mr. Chandler asserted, borrowing a  <tag key="text"/>  from Winston Churchill. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Your Aug. 17 editorial page contained "The Poem Heard Round the World," with Richard F. Barrett's comment on Edwin Markham's poem "The Man With a Hoe," inspired by Millet's painting.  The theme is in these stirring  <tag key="text"/> : 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 -  In regard to questions concerning the changed  <tag key="text"/>  in Markham's poem: My source was "The Britannica Library of Great American Writing," edited by Louis Untermeyer. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Not just after McFour o'clock."  The ad carries a  <tag key="text"/>  describing it as "a public service message." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 It offers bits of technical information.  It shows the writer teetering at the tip of the  <tag key="text"/>  of words. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 It would present, by way of "a dispatch from the desk," something more than dimwitted illuminations.  Of these, there are many in this book: "When you write, you lay out a  <tag key="text"/>  of words"; "Putting a book together is interesting and exhilarating"; "How we spend our days is, of course, how we spend our lives. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 His research, moreover, is sloppy.  For instance, he passes along without comment the  <tag key="text"/>  that Jim Jacobs, the fighter's late co-manager, was born wealthy. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Wanting her film to have the aura of objectivity, Ms. Franklin-Trout begins by adopting the pose of the network anchor.  She delivers opening  <tag key="text"/>  that presuppose a reasonableness, a fairness, a balance: "Tonight, we take you inside the territory to look at the realities that led to the rebellion." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "The on-air promotion schedule is the most aggressive it's ever been," says Tom Remiszewski, director of advertising and promotion at ABC Sports.  In the past week, the network has run a spot promoting tonight's kickoff, playing up the 20th-season theme and featuring Mr. Williams singing the  <tag key="text"/> , "Are you ready for some football?" 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "We set off little comedy bombs that go off later," years later, he explains.  So he put in  <tag key="text"/>  like "Make my doggie day," introduced a pretentious Francophile pooch and, when a dog is having puppies, slipped in a joke about Lamaze breathing. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 -  You quoted Ford's old  <tag key="text"/>  that the Edsel was the first "all-new" car from Detroit's Big three in 18 years and that Ford spent $250 million to develop it (Ford's propaganda always said a quarter of a billion  it sounded bigger that way). 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Unlike "Imelda," Donizetti's "Maria Stuarda" of 1834 is a steadily inspired, brilliantly theatrical opera.  Donizetti's imaginary encounter between the two queens, Mary Stuart and Elizabeth Tudor, slowly heats up into an insult match that culminates with Mary's great  <tag key="text"/> : "vil bastarda]" It needs no translation, which is just as well since the album doesn't offer any. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Mats Wilander, the defending champion and No. 5 seed, was ambushed by 91st-ranked Pete Sampras in round two.  Then fourth-seeded John McEnroe, tennis's perennial bad boy (that's English for enfant terrible), was mugged by 115th-ranked Paul Haarhuis, a player so obscure he rates nary a  <tag key="text"/>  in the game's media guide. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 But for the upscale retailer Barneys New York, which is outfitting comedian Joan Rivers for her new talk show this fall, the wardrobe credit couldn't have come at a better time: Barneys is in the midst of a big expansion beyond the New York area.  Designers often get more than a  <tag key="text"/>  zooming by as the credits roll. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 But for all the then-and-now charm, each story has to be shoehorned into little yesterday, today and tomorrow boxes.  The fit is often awkward: In their search for a tomorrow to throw in, the producers give us such half-hearted  <tag key="text"/>  as, "In a future war, My Lai could happen again." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 He recalls with amusement the time he literally locked the office doors and dispatched all his marketing people to the field for three days.  Mr. Sharer says he even plans to print up signs for himself and his subordinates with novelist John le Carre's  <tag key="text"/> : "A desk is a dangerous place from which to watch the world." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 To emphasize the surprising speed with which the charioteer is about to be served, the ads' signature is, "the Pizza you won't believa."  In some ads the  <tag key="text"/>  is sung, opera-style. (Burnett used opera singing to memorable advantage in its current ads for Cheer detergent.) 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 At a news conference, General Electric Co.'s NBC also described the structure of its previously announced nationwide sweepstakes that will award $2 million in cash and prizes and give four people one-time appearances on new NBC prime-time series.  "We'll see how well they can talk, but the goal is to give the winners at least one  <tag key="text"/>  {of dialogue}," said John Miller, senior vice president, NBC Entertainment. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "But he's not a corporate animal, so this is perfect for him."  Mr. Gordon himself produces this  <tag key="text"/>  to sum up: "As a career move, this is my field of dreams." 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Some contributors, however, are eager to associate themselves with the patriotic and educational aspects of their participation.  Says Mr. Armour of American Express, echoing the  <tag key="text"/>  of other sponsors: "We love to be patriotic. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 The author was Edwin Markham, a hitherto undistinguished poet who became famous when Bailey Millard, the editor of the San Francisco Examiner, accepted "The Man With the Hoe" for publication in 1899 and it was immediately reprinted all over the world.  The poem was inspired by Jean Francois Millet's famous painting of the same name, and it became a prophecy, when Markham ended it with these  <tag key="text"/> : 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 Markham died in 1940 at the age of 88.  "The Man With the Hoe" cannot be said to have had the impact of the "Communist Manifesto" of Karl Marx and Friedrich Engels, but it did precede the Russian Revolution of 1917, which seemed to answer the question Markham posed in the poem's closing  <tag key="text"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 At about the same time, Sen. Wallop also carried the argument personally to Mr. Bush during a flight aboard Air Force One with the president, who was traveling to Yellowstone Park to make a speech.  But Mr. Bush seemed preoccupied with other concerns; back in Washington several days later, reading a  <tag key="text"/>  inserted in a speech by an aide, Mr. Bush said he looked forward to Mr. Fiske's arrival. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 But no one has the same vacation."  Another spot's  <tag key="text"/> : "What's Club Med? 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 BBDO serviced the account for more than 30 years.  It was there that copywriter Jim Jordan wrote the well-known "ring around the collar"  <tag key="text"/> . 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 In North Korea, the propaganda  <tag key="text"/>  still contains heavy doses of "anti-imperialism" and other, well-worn revolutionary themes.  The line that draws the biggest cheer from the ever-cheering crowd at the stadium is, "U.S. 
</sentence>
<sentence>
 "That was hilarious, that was so cruel," says Chris Kreski, the show's 26-year-old head writer.  Backstage, Mr. Kreski struggles to come up with a "mom  <tag key="text"/> ," the nightly joke in which Mr. Ober is interrupted by the voice of his mother asking him to do some gross chore, such as trimming her mustache. 
</sentence>
</body>
